https://www.youtube.com/live/_K-02fqfa3Y?si=-zP4l_adbSP_2SjJ&t=1398
All right, y'all. Uh, we are live on
this beautiful Wednesday morning. God
bless everyone. I hope you had a great
Tuesday evening.
It is Wednesday and we are live. We'll
be looking for some Bitcoin trades. So
man, what can we say besides
um
you know we shorted from here, we longed
from here and where did we got short
somewhere? I I forget exactly where
I mean we pretty much shorted the top
again. Okay, those three trades are the
three big money makers.
And the rest are just kind of, you know,
smaller wins, right? Or losses.
That's kind of how the trading works,
right? You get small losses, small wins,
and then eventually you catch one of
those big moves. Those are your money
makers, right? So, let's uh start our
analysis
on the daily.
Um, look, I'm pretty agnostic. I'm we're
always agnostic when it comes to the
price action. We don't know. We're
without knowledge. But I'm pretty um
unbiased right now. I could I could make
a bullish case and get myself ultra
bullish and bearish. In fact, I was kind
of half dreaming about it this morning
about whether I was bullish or bearish.
I had dreams I woke up and the price was
like back down to 65. I had dreams I
woke up and we were like 78.
Um look, we've closed a daily below
value area high.
Next major target going to be PC. All
right, so let's go ahead and just mark
some key levels. Come up with a plan.
We know we're at the local golden pocket
786 support right now.
Um, yeah. So, this is our daily chart.
Let's put our daily open here.
And let's go ahead and put on our PVP.
All right, this naked daily is no longer
neaked.
And other than that, man, we got nothing
here. All right,
let's go down to our TPO. See if we have
anything. I I doubt I doubt.
Yeah, we got nothing, guys. So,
let's go ahead and uh we'll stay on our
half hour chart for now.
We've got our volume range. We've got
our key levels. We're going to go ahead
and pull our fibs. So, we pull from low
to high.
And
we've got this.
Just make sure that our high is actually
high.
382 should be 69,400.
All right.
There we go.
Um,
then we're going to pull another fib
from this last low
to the high.
Oh wow, we did bounce from 786. I
thought we front ran.
Okay, so we are bouncing from a key
level here to be honest.
Um, okay. That's something to keep on
the back burner.
Yeah. So essentially, I mean, we are
bouncing from our 786 and this does look
pretty dang squeezable. I'm not going to
lie. Like we have this channel here.
We'll talk about the channel in a
second,
but we have this channel, right? This
could be a reversal pattern coming in.
But I would say that um you know long
one from yesterday,
where was long one from yesterday?
I mean this is still valid.
We'll remove that. This is still a valid
long trade here
from the daily. I mean, I I would highly
doubt we get another rotation back to
the top of the range, but you never
know.
That obviously no more.
That is the trade we took, I think.
All right. So, we got long one. All
right. That trade is a nogo.
Uh, okay. So, we don't have that long
anymore on the chart, which is strange.
I'll put it on again. We're basically
looking for a move down. Take the
liquidity from uh Monday
and back test that PC invalidation 786
and look for a new high basically,
right? Long one.
All right. Um, yeah, it's going to be a
long one.
All right,
that's going to be long one.
Long two would be from the daily in the
value area low. All right. CDW of the
CDW of our weekend low basically, right?
That is possible. It is a Wednesday,
guys. A lot of times crazy stuff could
happen on a Wednesday. Is there Hang on.
When is FOMC
next week. Okay. Okay. All right.
All right, Bitcoin is at daily open. If
we reclaim daily open, we could see some
upside here. If we reject from daily
open, uh maybe we come down.
Um
man, [music] this 786 for some reason
this morning I thought that we had not
um tapped into it.
So let's go to our lower time frames
here
or 12.
We don't have divergence.
Um,
let's go to our six. Do we have
divergence there?
Not particularly. It would be really
nice to get another drive to the
downside and get get some divergence
there. Um,
man, I I I for some reason I must have
had my fib pulled wrong, but when I
looked this morning, I didn't see that
we had tapped the 786. So, my first
trading plan was actually come down and
tap 786,
but uh obviously we haven't we've
already [music] we've already done that.
The trades missed, you know, the trades
missed. Um
so, yeah.
Um
let's take a look at the volume here.
This would be like our our potential
sideways range.
Okay. So I, you know, on a very low time
frame, it would be really nice and juicy
to come down with some bullish
divergence, just take that pre-new york
open low into the value area low of our
range for a potential long. Right? If
we're looking at this as our sideways
range, potential scalp. All right.
Where we look up toward here.
Okay. Um, now let's talk about short
trades.
Hey,
hey, hey.
I mean technically we got a a valid
short level here as well from PC GP and
all that of the range.
Let's check out our one minute market
cipher.
H it doesn't look so bearish to be
honest.
5-second looks decently bearish. Um,
this is interesting volatility that
we're getting here.
Yeah, I mean, New York's going to open
in 10 minutes. If New York wasn't open,
I'd say like a DGEN long like lowrisk,
super low risk,
you know, potentially could be could be
a move honestly
cuz we're playing PC,
you know,
DJ move.
I'm real curious to see we are pumping
up.
Make sure if you're short to take some
dang profits here or you know the short
from yesterday. Make sure to close that
thing in a in a win.
You know, another um another another DJ
move here would be if New York pumps us
and we get like a back test, something
like this,
the back test of the CDW. I I would
probably go for a long there as well.
Let's see what happens as New York
opens. You know,
we got about 9 minutes. While we're
waiting, let me share my chart and all
that stuff.
All
right.
Oops. Made my thing too big there.
Curious to see what the order flow is
doing here. Like, is that actual buys or
is that a squeeze?
Probably a squeeze from everyone who's
been short. No,
it's pretty bunch. Yeah, I mean, yeah,
it's a squeeze, but interesting. Very
interesting. Like, look at this. We had
a whole bunch of longs open at the top
and then close right out.
So, by didn't quite take that high yet.
This is interesting stuff, guys. Like,
honestly, uh 7 minutes until New York
opens. Let's see if we have any
questions in the Discord here.
How do you do a multiple divs at the
level?
And uh shout out to everyone in here by
the way guys.
Um
so dial yes to mark daily open. I'm just
going off the level that the daily
candle itself opened. Yep.
Did I leave the homestead? No, I still
have the homestead.
Um, yeah. I don't I don't know if I'll
ever sell that homestead. I put so much
time, blood, sweat, and tears into that.
I I probably
I mean, I took it I I made it fully
off-rid. I I cultivated 2 acres of soil
to grow food. I built a barn. I built a
chicken coupe. I built fences. I built
pastures. I put a whole solar farm on
there. We're totally off-rid. Um, I got
a wood stove in there, you know. I got a
I got a a well pump that you can pump by
hand. Um it's basically like amazing.
It's on top of a mountain. Like you
can't see anybody. It's amazing. I would
never want to get rid of that place.
We're missing a pecker on the daily
candle. The wick.
I do have a discount code for market
monkey. I'm pretty sure I can probably
get that to you. Um,
yeah, shout outs to everybody in the
chat. Uh, how do I deal with multiple
divs at a level? Uh, the more the
better. The more the better. Sometimes
it's not going to the level and just
reverse by the div with no level. Um, I
uh I like to wait for the trade to hit
the level. You know, you can take it if
it's not at a level, but I much rather
prefer
to let the trade come to a level.
[music] All right? It's
trading non-levels is probably not all
the time if if you if you have here's
the thing. You could have a level there.
You could have a level there that maybe
is not um as big of a level. But don't
take trades on no levels. Here's why.
Let's say this is your level, right?
This is your level and you know you're
waiting for it. Price does this gets
reversed. You're like dang. So you like
FOMO in here, stop loss and then you get
stopped out. Then it comes up again.
This time it'll hit my level, right? No,
it doesn't. Right now you're FOMO again.
Stop loss. You get stopped out. This
time it hits your level, right? And
guess what? You get in. Awesome. I got
in. Right. Wh Stop stop loss. You just
took three losses in a row instead of
one. just wait for your level because
here's the thing. A lot of times if you
have a key level on a chart and price
doesn't hit and it gets a reversal
first, it usually means next time whoop,
right? So wait for those key levels,
trade the levels. Your losses will be
less and your wins will be more. All
right? Your losses will be less and your
wins will be more.
That's that's non-financial advice for
you. All right?
How many solar panels do I have? A lot.
I don't even know the exact number. I
have a lot. I have a whole like field
full of them. And it's it's it's way
more power than my house even needs. But
I don't know. I like I go overboard with
everything I do. Like even the
gardening. Like I I I go pretty crazy
with the gardening. It's like I always
am planning as if like
I'm an extreme person. Everything I do
is extreme. All right. [music] So,
all right. New York's going to open in 3
minutes.
Is shorting gold here a good idea? You
know, I I had a friend who was looking
to short gold. Let's take a look at gold
here. I I don't know. I haven't really
been keeping my pulse on gold.
because I've been so like into the
Bitcoin chart lately. Um,
I mean, we're not at a golden pocket
locally.
We are rejecting from a macro 786.
Um,
I I don't know. I mean, maybe we got a
trigger wave and we we we're losing the
range here,
right? We're we're come back under this
range. We got a few candle closes below.
We got a daily candle close below CDW
confirmed on the daily.
You know, technically it is a valid
short entry.
It is a valid short entry. We we have
taken the liquidity of of the high of
the range and close the candle below.
Um,
you know, if we're going to short gold
here, we got to make sure our risk is in
check.
We're going to need a 1.5% stop loss,
give or take, and we target back down to
the lows of the range for a nice two to
four 2.4 to1 riskreward. Or we use a
tighter stop, we could probably squeeze
a three to one, right?
So yeah, you could, right?
All right, New York about to open.
We've got our local range
here.
And New York's going to open. Let's see
what they do.
Man, this song gets me emotional. It's
like my best friend just like moved away
to a different country and I'll never
see him again from like a movie in like
the 90s [music] or something.
Think of all the memories we've had
together.
All right, New York's open.
Wow. New York's opening immediately.
We've got uh shorts
opening up here.
Now we got longs coming in. Now we got
more shorts. It's pretty even. It's It's
like a pretty It's pretty like a pretty
fair fight in this fiveminute candle.
Right now we've got uh
you can see it moving here in real time.
Wow. 20 million. Big long. Big long just
came in here. Big longs coming in. Big
longs coming in.
50 million longs on one candle. Wow. 60
million. 70 million longs
here. 77 million longs popping in on
this one condal.
All right. So,
if we lose 7438
um would be a short trade.
Um,
value area high.
If we come down, if we if we come down
here, I'm I'm going to short it, you
know,
but looks like we're not yet. So, no
trade for me.
All right, we back tested the CDWS
support. We didn't lose it. No trade for
me.
Front run the 618. like that typically
means we will come through
you know
so you know
these are the types of instances where
you know if you're a high-risisk
personality you long resistance with
your stop loss below
um
let's see here
the 1 or big green dot.
You know what?
Let's wait and see if we get a little
bit of a pullback here.
Wow. 100 million longs right in one
candle. New York open. People are ultra
bullish right now. That's crazy. All
right, we hit golden pocket.
See if we get a pullback from the golden
pocket.
Looks like we're going to get a pullback
from the golden pocket here, guys.
We've got one minute divergence here.
Once confirmed, could probably take us
back down.
Looks like no. My goodness.
Man, this this daily candle actually
that wick is a nice wick. Look at that
beautiful
filling of that uh fair value gap that
yesterday's candle made.
Is the Is the um full launch and token
generation event close for Antarctic?
Yeah, it is close. Yeah. Is Donald Trump
the man of sin? I don't know. Probably
not. KMAC, I think the man of sin is
going to have to be everyone's going to
have to love the man of sin.
Um,
but who knows? We'll have to wait for
time to develop. And honestly,
you know, I wouldn't die in any
escalological hill.
Shoulder press or lateral raise.
Definitely.
I am unique because I don't really train
shoulders very much. I'm very
deltentant. So like my delts which are
very like well-developed,
right? Look at that. I pretty much don't
train them. Okay. So I would prefer an
overhead press. Uh [music] you got to
find what works for you. Most of my
shoulder work gets done through just
normal incline pressing.
Um, boy's looking for a short here.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, this is a
resistance, you know. I um
this is a resistance. [music]
It does feel like a trappy move, but
also it feels like one of those times
where Bitcoin just doesn't stop, right?
We've seen that happen before. And we do
have a bullish green dot in the weekly.
So, let's wait and see what can happen
here. Um, are we still in that short
trade? Okay, we're still in.
We're still in.
We are still in. Man, this was Talk
about cheesy squeezy.
Talk about cheesy squeezy. My goodness.
That is insane, man. That [music] is
insane.
Yeah. So essentially guys like right now
what I am waiting for is any kind of
pullback
to get long. Um
hopefully it comes from around this area
here.
All right.
Do I like your char Satoshi Yeah, man. I
do. That's funny, bro.
Am I still macro bearish? Yeah, I'm
still macro bearish. Yeah,
just chase it. I mean, I I'm trying to
chase it, but I need a little bit of a
pullback first, bro. You know, um
I mean, all things do look pretty
bullish here. I wouldn't be surprised if
we have just a an upward trending day
like like we've seen like historically
here. Um but eventually like the
pullback will have to come. So what we
do is we wait we wait for a level. Right
now I would say in a very bullish
environment
looking at our 382
coming in here which uh confluence with
the local golden pocket like the CDW
level. Let's also put on VWAP here.
Yeah, the best long trade right now
would be from VWOP obviously coming down
to back test daily open
you know
but also we do need to be aware of uh
the CDW right
Yeah. Come back down to CDW zone for a
back test.
I'd get interested. Let's see if we can
do it.
Of
course, we might trap, you know, 200
million longs,
in which case we would
we could come up much lower, you know,
back to the daily open here. So, let's
keep our eyes on these low time frames
here.
Heat. Heat.
All right. A lowrisk like long I guess
could be here, you know.
H. What the heck?
H.
For some reason, I'm not able to open a
position here. Give me one second. It's
a good thing, too, cuz we just fell
through that like a hot knife through
butter.
Just test this out here. Can I open any
positions?
Oh, I got to reconnect my wallet.
Well, dang. All right.
All right.
That's the one thing that's not the best
about uh
Well, it's fine. I just You got to
connect your wallet to AX. All
right.
All right. Let's see. Let's see what's
going on here.
All right. the the next place I'd look
for a trade here would be
honestly maybe maybe like coming for
this low here but better yet would be
the daily open the VWAP and the golden
pocket that would actually be a really
nice area also got the PC there so
let's wait and see
I'll wait for a one minute as Oh,
Daily open hit to the dollar. Couldn't
make for a scalp, but
the it would have to be like super scalp
scalp if you were like literally there
to watch it happen which we are but you
know you got to be you got to be super
quick like if you're in you got to make
sure if we lose that you're out
immediately right um
kind of deal and then the best place
is going to have to be this All right.
The VWabinator
I'll let you guys know if I decide to
pull the trigger on something. All
right.
Yeah. So if you scalp daily open
honestly
This is like the time where you would
TP1
if you're really scalping like the
5-second strategy, which did give us a
valid
valid entry there. You know, this is
where you got to be hitting TP1 on it,
which is possible on Antarctic blow
finex. You know, you can mark it in and
mark it out and make money in moves like
that if you're right there to watch the
dang price hit and you like hit the
button as soon as it hits.
You know, that's how you got to do it.
You know, someday AX is going to have it
so you can change a trade from split to
merge on a single trade, which would be
nice, you know.
All right. So, I do have to head out
soon. I'm actually going to do a collab
with Floppin Grober. Um, [clears throat]
right now I am interested in the VWOP
for a long scalp trade. If we come down
a bit lower than that then we're going
right to the trades that we have we have
given already
today. So let's just re quickly let's
just re um
analyze these because excuse me
no everything's still the same. We
haven't made a higher high. Yeah. So
honestly guys uh I have to say as far as
like actual trades go more than scalps.
We got 67861.
We've got our VWAP. Uh, and then we have
the CDW of the low. All right.
Um, wow. We're we're at VWOP already.
We're already at VWOP.
Let's see if we dip down a tad bit into
deep VWOP.
Oh man,
look at that.
Man,
I wasn't paying attention. That could
have been a nice scalp in of itself. you
know, from these little levels, the
daily open, ZVOP, Zevop
Man,
that's a bummer,
you know. Missed missed a few trades
today. Missed the 786 bounce. Missed the
bounce from the WiiW. Missed the short.
That's okay.
That is okay. But yeah, guys. Um,
we don't have a lot of divs here, but
assuming that
we are going to continue up. Ah, it's
really not the best risk-to-reward
anyway, but it could be from here. I
think we might come lower, but the money
flow looks nice.
Uh,
that was a nice level for a scalp at
least. But anyway, guys, I have to head
out. All right. So, I will see you guys
later. And if I do decide to take a
trade, I will let you guys know. All
right. I'll do my best if I'm there at
the computer to let you know. Um,
I think
if we can come down a little bit lower
here, it would give us a nice entry.
Um, if we got a nice one minute bullish
dive and we dipped a little bit under
VWAP, that could give us a nice entry.
But yeah,
unfortunately the move is missed in my
opinion for for a scalp. You know, we
already got a 6% move. Enough to make
good money on a scalp,
but uh way too late to enter for a
scalp, unless you're convicted that this
is going to be [music] the beginning of
a bigger move to the upside, which it
very well may. All right,
so
we'll have to we'll have to wait and see
how it goes.
All right.
Um, yeah, I have to head out. I'm going
to take a long and put my stop loss
under daily open right here. Small risk.
All right.
I have to head out, guys. God bless you
all. Thank you so much for being here
and I will see you guys next time.