https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=it13lxPtK4w
all right y'all so people always ask me
when do you add or do you even add to
open trades
and the answer is yes i do and so here's
how i do it basically if i'm in a long
trade i will trade it up and take
profits out and then i'll open a short
trade if i see we're going to get a
retracement now when we come down to key
areas of support like we are right now
to this fibonacci golden pocket i can
add to this long trade and still keep my
entry underneath that golden pocket so
for example we can see i've taken
profits on the short trade stop loss to
entry have a portion open i've taken
profits on the long trade stop loss to
entry have a portion open as we're
coming down to this fibonacci golden
pocket we can see that we are getting a
bounce from it with some both signs on
market cipher b which means i can still
add to my position and keep my entry
underneath this low totally risk free
it's pretty cool