https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=clST2NsJFAQ
All right, y'all. Welcome to part two of
the complete trading guide where we are
going to cover the one critical element
that will make you or break you as a
trader. In fact, every single profitable
trader I've ever met in my life uses
this one thing to become profitable.
Now, sad story. Most traders start out
and they learn this first, but then they
actually throw it away when they don't
see immediate success. and they get into
the mindset thinking that the more
complex they can make their trading
system, the more likely they are to be
profitable. When nothing could be
further from the truth. In fact, the
more you simplify your trading process,
the more likely you are to be
profitable. Now, the one thing I'm
talking about right now is support and
resistance. The most foundational thing
to becoming a profitable trader is
support and resistance. What is support
and resistance? These are areas or price
levels on the chart where the price is
very likely to have a reaction. If the
price is going up, the price is very
likely to reject from that level and
turn back down. If the price is coming
down, the price is very likely to bounce
from that level and turn back up. Now,
I'm going to be showing you exactly how
to identify these key levels in this
video. And not only that, I'm going to
show you how to set up your trading
plans around these levels so that you
can put the probabilities in your favor
to actually start winning more trades.
So, make sure to like the video, guys.
And if you have not checked out part one
of this complete trading guide, I highly
recommend you go check that out because
that is going to lay the foundation for
everything else I'm going to talk about.
So, make sure to like, subscribe, click
the bell, all that YouTube stuff. Let's
get into it. So, what is support and
resistance and how can we actually
utilize this for our trading? Well, very
simply put, if we're going to look at
any trading chart, support and
resistance are areas on the chart where
price has historically found a sticking
point. Now, I want to tell you something
that is very, very important.
Everybody's always looking for that big
move. Everybody's looking for those
large moves on the chart where the price
goes straight up or the price comes
straight down or something like this to
catch those massive moves. But if we
take a few steps back and we just
objectively analyze the chart, we can
see that most of the time things are
trading sideways. In fact, more times
than not, we can see that the price is
bound within a sideways range. These
sideways ranges are areas where we can
identify levels of support or
resistance. Now, I just want you to look
for a second here at this box that I've
drawn on the chart. In general, we can
say that if the price comes up to this
area, it found a sticking point and
actually got a reversal. And if price
came down to this area down here, it
found a sticking point and actually got
a reversal. And so what we want to do
when we're identifying levels of support
and resistance is we want to go
backwards and to the left on the chart
and ask ourselves where are places
historically where price has found a
sticking point and has gotten a
reversal. And these are going to be
areas of support and resistance on the
chart. Now I just want to point out
something very important to you. When
you have a support, which is an area
that price comes down to and gets a
bounce, when you actually lose that
level of support like we did right here,
it then becomes resistance. Resistance
is where the price is going up and we
find a sticking point and get a
reversal. Notice this. We had resistance
once here. We had it once here. We had
it once here. We had support down here.
We had support down here. We had support
down here. Once we lose that support and
it no longer gives us a bounce, guess
what? That area now becomes our
resistance. And guess what? When you
have a resistance and that area then
gets reclaimed, that same area then
becomes support. We see this happen all
the time. And so without having to know
any fancy tools, any super complex
technical analysis, really just coming
to a chart, and believe me, there are
many tools that we will learn to use in
order to zero in more and more on these
zones of support and resistance. But
essentially, all you need to do is look
at a chart and ask yourself, where has
price historically found a sticking
point and gotten a bounce? Or to the
upside, where has price found a sticking
point and gotten a rejection? Notice how
this works. We see this all the time. As
soon as we put our first area of
resistance right here, it was resistance
the second time. It ended up being
resistance the third time. And honestly,
that third time is how we were able to
take the short trade literally from the
exact top. I was short on Bitcoin from
the exact top and we locked in tens of
thousands of dollars simply by
understanding that this was resistance.
All right, so that is the basics of
support and resistance. If we are
looking for profitable trades where
we're looking to make more than we are
risking, you can see how advantageous
support and resistance is because
essentially you're looking to enter the
trade at the support or resistance and
close the trade at the support or
resistance. If we're in a long trade, we
would look to long the support zone, put
our stop loss below the support zone,
and take profit at the resistance zone.
This is giving us a 3:1 risk-reward
ratio, which indeed that did hit. And if
we're looking for a short trade, well,
we look to short the area of resistance,
put our stop loss above that area of
resistance, and take profit at the
support, giving us a beautiful 4:1
risk-reward ratio. Both of these trade
setups, you can see, ended up being
profitable. In fact, both of these trade
setups are trades I actually took in my
private trading group. But that's
besides the point. My point here is that
if you're identifying the sideways
range, as soon as this uh area is
identified as resistance, well, you
could take one trade from there, two
trades from there, and because this was
already identified as support, well,
when we come down there, you could have
taken one, two, and then really this
third trade from there was a profitable
trade. I actually did hit a TP1 on half
the move there before it was eventually
lost. Now, contrast this style of
trading to people who are always trying
to predict the next big breakout or the
next big move. Those people would have
been wrong every time I was right.
Because if they were expecting the
breakout here, well, they were wrong. If
they were expecting the breakout here,
well, they were wrong. If they were
expecting a break down here, they were
wrong. A break down here, they were
wrong. A break down here, I mean,
eventually they were right, but they
probably would have gotten stopped out
or liquidated first. So, you always want
to identify those areas of support or
resistance. And after you identify those
zones, what you can do next is zero in
on lower time frames to add more layers
of confluence to your support and
resistance. Now, there are many tools
we'll talk about later within this
series, but for right now, especially if
you're new, what I want you to do is I
want you to go to a blank chart and just
go ahead and ask yourself, where has
price historically found support or
resistance? If we just start looking at
this chart, I we could clearly see this
was major resistance and you can see
that it is right now being respected as
support, which is why I'm currently in a
little bit of a long trade that we took
in my trading group as we came down to
this area. What are some other areas? If
we're on a major time frame right now,
we can say for Bitcoin at least the
$13,000 to $15,000 level, this is going
to be a major support. Now, I'm not
saying that we're going to come down
there, but I am saying if I woke up
tomorrow and the price just so happened
to be down here, I'd say this is major
major support. What's another area?
Well, look at this around $30,000 for
the Bitcoin price. This was a major
support resistance flip. It was support
through the bull run. It was resistance
through the bare run. We broke out. If
we wake up tomorrow and we're back down
at $30,000, well, we could say that is
going to be a very major support. Look
at this. There's another very, very
major level. If we're just going to be
looking at the high that we made here in
2022 spring, and then the high that we
made in January 2024, coming to the low
that we made in August 2024, it's going
to be around the $50,000 level. You can
see price found a sticking point here
many, many times. In fact, this was
support all the way back here in March.
It was resistance in August 2021,
resistance in December 21, resistance in
March 22. It was resistance in January
2024, support in August 2024. If I woke
up tomorrow and the price was down here,
I'd say, "Wow, that's a beautiful area
of support. Let's take a look at this
key level around $100,000." This was a
key psychological level. It was our
resistance all throughout the beginning
of 2025. Our support in the summer of
2025, and then our resistance right here
in the fall of two, I'm sorry, the
winter, beginning of 2026. We are right
now identifying these key levels. And if
we're swinging traders looking for
trades, this is where we want to look
for trades. In fact, this zone, the
$98,000 level, I'm currently short from
that exact price, right? From the
$98,000
uh entry that I have right here, 96.7.
This was an area of resistance we were
prepared for, right? The 96 to $98,000
level. We were prepared for this
resistance, saying, look, if we come up
to this area, we should look for a trade
because we have a very, very good
risk-to-reward ratio coming up to this
trade. We could potentially come back
down to the low70s from this area simply
because we're looking at support and
resistance. And what do you know? As we
came up to this area right here, we
rejected and we came down to below the
low70s to our next area of support. So
go and practice this. This is the weekly
time frame. We could do this down on
literally the six-minut time frame.
Let's just go to our six-inut time
frame. Let's clear off the chart here
and let's just go ahead and see
everything that we could see right here.
I mean, this is this is something you
can do on any time frame, you know. I'm
just going to go ahead and look and see
that this area right here on the 6-minut
time frame is very obvious support
flipped to resistance. And so, we could
take this all the way through here on
our six-minut time frame. And look at
that because it was support all the way
back here. It was support again here. It
was support again here. When we lose it,
it's resistance 1, two, three times. We
break up above, it's support, major
support. And then we lose it and it
gives you one, two, three rejections. Of
course, this zone of support right down
here. Look at this. We wick down to the
area. It gives us a big bounce up to
resistance. This is how it works. And
when you can identify these levels
where, you know, price is likely to have
a reaction. Then we can start to stack
confluences. We can say, I know we're at
a support, which means we're likely to
get a bounce. And then if I see X, Y,
and Z on the chart, I know I have a very
good trade setup on my hands. One of the
ways I like to trade a support or
resistance is say if I see Whoa, we got
a cell phone buzzing over here.
If I see the price coming down to a key
support or a key resistance, I then say
I want to see certain indications on my
chart and that's what's actually going
to get me to pull the trigger. So guys,
that is it for this session, support and
resistance. And we're going to expound
on this as we go on. And if you want to
join my trading group, you can go to
jasonaspertrading.com.
Also guys, if you want to become a
funded trader, check out Bitfunded. Bit
funded right now is the easiest way to
become a funded trader. If you know how
to trade but you don't have capital and
you want to get funded by proving your
skills or testing a new strategy link in
the pin comment in description. I'm also
trading Bitcoin on KSEX and Blofin.
Lowest fees out there guys. So if you're
interested in that, check it out in the
pin comment description. That's it for
today's video guys. May God bless you
all in the name of Jesus Yeshua the
Messiah. I pray you and your family are
super blessed and I'll see everybody in
the next video. Peace.