https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bvXRKqqvy5o
all right y'all so here I am driving and
trading right now I almost got hit by a
truck oh my goodness now I'm not
actually driving right I've got my wife
Big Bus 28 driving but I want to talk
about a scalping strategy that you can
use on a very low time frame currently I
am in this uh long trade right here as
you can see up 37 I want to talk about
how I was able to get into this trade
okay now this is something that you can
do on very very very low time frames and
it really just comes down to this okay
what you want to do and you can do this
on the one minute the six minute I like
to use the 12 minute and down what you
can do is if you notice that an asset is
trading sideways like it is right here
with clear lows and clear highs just
draw a box of round
the highs and the lows in general and
what you can do is you can look
literally to take trades whenever we
come up to the top of the box you can
look to take shorts and whenever we come
down to the bottom of the box you can
look to take Longs and what I like to do
is I like to use Market Cipher to tell
me when
there is a good opportunity to get into
a trade and the way we're going to do
that is using divergences it's a very
simple strategy people over complicate
their trades all the time don't you
agree Big Bus 28 yes she agrees people
over complicate things all the time all
you need to do if you see a sideways
range is I like to pull some volume
through the range so what that means is
this right
we are going to come over here to the
prediction and measurement tools come
down to fixed range volume profile and
we are simply going to drag that through
the entirety of the price action and
once we do that
hang on one second here
once we do that this now gives us a
framework where we can look for trades
and this will also give us our take
profits and our stop losses so
we can then after we have this larger
box we can then make smaller boxes and
say okay whenever we come up here we can
look for shorts and whenever we come
down here we can be looking for launch
now this morning in the VIP Discord I
did it put this exact level here that
19462 level right here as an area where
we are going to be looking for long
trace and also this morning when I was
giving my potential trade setups in the
VIP Discord
I was saying that this box is the zone
to look for Longs because we are coming
down to this lower portion of the
sideways range so when we get there
here's what we're going to look for
we're going to look for divergences okay
I did actually take a scout this morning
from up here because we had come up to
the higher region of the box and when we
take a look at our indicator of Market
Cipher B we can see that we are getting
bearish divergences we can see that
price is making a higher high as
momentum is making a lower high and
something else that I really like to
look at is the money flow okay the money
flow on Market Cypher B is very very
important not only do we want to see
bearish divergences where we have a very
juicy left butt cheek over here full of
Ravioli and then a skinny butt cheek
over here not so much ravioli in there
probably vegan eating lots of celery
okay but we also want to see the money
flow getting lower and if we come over
here to Marcus Cipher B and we just turn
off our momentum here
okay we can see I'll turn off the V wob
I'll turn off everything except the
money flow we can see that the money
flow was getting lower
as we were
getting higher in price okay we can see
that literally the money flow ways are
getting lower okay this is very very key
now when we come down to the long tray
that we just took we can see the exact
same thing on the higher term time
frames a 12 minute time frame the money
flow is actually getting higher as the
price is getting lower and so that is
what gives us the entry for the trade
now the stop loss is always going to go
above or below the last high or low okay
the last higher low
um
so in this case our initial stop loss
goes below this Wick after take profit
one we move that to the entry and if
we're shorting initially the stop loss
goes above this way okay this gives us
really good risk to reward ratios
because if we're taking shorts from the
high targeting the low right like this
that is a good four to one risk and
reward ratio and if we're taking along
from the bottom and we're targeting the
high let's just say from here that is
also giving us a nice
um well hang on this is not correct this
trade is now giving us a three to one
reward ratio right so they're good risk
reward ratios if we constantly are
trading this way over time we will be
profitable now what about the take
profits where do they go well I like to
use these areas of volume for take
profits okay this is giving us a fair
value for this little sideways range
where these candles are shaded on the
fixed range volume profile anything
below is considered oversold anything
above is considered overbought and
pretty much we're looking at this as a
sideways range where these levels are
going to be take profits so a take
profit one would be right here a take
profit two would be right here and then
we can let the rest ride now why did
take profits there it's because this is
establishing a fair value if the price
is unable to now come back inside of the
fair value we can expect actually lower
so if we take profit one here and then
move our stop loss to our entry then
we've guaranteed a win and then we don't
really have to worry about getting
stopped out at our entry because it's a
small win but we we don't want to close
the whole tree here because we know if
we come back inside of here it's very
probable we'll make it back up to the
highs right look at the trades that we
could have taken in this range so far
now today I've taken two trades in this
range
but you know we could have literally
after establishing the low and the high
taking one short one long one short one
long one short and now one long we've
literally had one two three four five
six profitable trades in this tiny
little range here that only spans about
you know 1.5 percent now the reason I
say this is a one minute strategy is
because literally you can use the very
low time frames here
um for example like the one minute look
at this on the one minute as we come
down to here we are getting money flow
getting higher and the momentum getting
higher down here okay and when we were
up here we could see the money flow and
the momentum getting lower when we were
down here we could see the momentum
waves getting higher money flow not
getting higher down here but even still
we had our divergences it's always best
if the money flow agrees okay this short
right here we can see money flow getting
lower but momentum not you can still
take trades if only one of the two is
working but if both are giving you the
same signal then it's a very very high
probability trade setup if we're looking
at sideways ranges so we can see now
we're back inside that value area
the trade is now up 50 percent in
profits and so now that we're inside of
here we're looking now to take our next
take profit up at this area okay at the
1975 area now here's the thing you can
front run these and I front run these a
lot because you know we we might not
exactly come up right to here right we
might just come up a little bit before
it and then lose it so you can
manipulate your take profits but in
general this is the outline that you
want to be using here
okay this is the outline that you want
to be using here so I could take another
little profit out now uh maybe in
another little profit out right there
if it ever loads I don't know kind of on
the road as you can see trading and
driving and yeah guys that's that's it
for today's video
um just a quick little scoping strategy
hope you found that helpful and if you
did make sure to like the video make
sure to subscribe to the channel if you
want to join the VIP Discord where we
give these levels in advance you can go
to patreon.com forward slash Jason
Casper also if you want to learn how to
trade this way where you know what
you're looking for how to have a plan in
advance you can check out the course
jasoncastmortrading.com this will give
you the knowledge and the skills you
need to become a confident profitable
Trader because not only does it teach
you how to read the charts and feel
confident in your trades it also teaches
confident in your trades it does not
teach you how to proofread your website
to avoid putting the same thing twice in
a row but it will teach you how to stop
fomo trading and trading with emotions
so that you can have a plan come to the
charts every single day and be
profitable doing this God bless
everybody in the name of Jesus the
Messiah make sure you're always wearing
your Market Cipher merch guys make sure
to keep your biceps nice and big make
sure to always Skip Leg Day make sure to
trade and drive speaking of trading and
driving I have tried doing it behind the
driver's wheel before and that did not
work out well peace