https://www.youtube.com/live/Jbv20ETYJf0?si=LBqUOkfvxJ-uyeWt&t=1120
All right, y'all. We are live on this
beautiful
Wednesday afternoon. God bless everybody
in the name of Jesus Yeshua the Messiah.
I pray you are all super blessed
as man,
Bitcoin getting a large move to the
downside right now, guys. Make sure to
smash up the likes. Make sure to
subscribe to the channel cuz we got to
talk about what is going on right now.
This is some serious business.
Major shout out to Milton Broski says
Hershey squirt shots.
Shout out to Eric Grim. He says straight
to 60K.
Shout out to Steph man when he is done
pissing in his jar. Corey [music] Max
says when he's ready. Th Tiger says hot.
Loco for crypto waves. Right back at you
my friend. Shout out to [music] Louise
who says Barb Simpson Patron.
Mm Crypto said he ready to start scaling
into a $1 million long. Cool man. Good
for MM Crypto, you know. Shout out to MM
Crypto. I like that guy a lot, you know.
I used to think he was just another Carl
from the Moon type character, but I
really like MM Crypto a lot. Uh I like
Carl from the Moon too, but
uh you know, Carl from the Moon and his
his mindset on life and mine don't jive,
right? Shout out to Muhammad. Shout out
to Crypto Pumpet. It's okay, guys. I'm
here now. Shout out to Daniel. He says,
"God bless brother Jason. Thanks for the
live show." Shout out to Flipper Frank J
to the C. Jesus is king. Amen.
Amen. Amen. Amen. All right, guys. Man,
seems like a nice genuine fell. Yeah,
you [music] know, you feel like a girl
today, says SEC. Shout out to Divine
Hood. He says 70k log GP coming soon.
Yeah. Yeah. And not only is the 70k log
GP coming soon, but we do have a major
zone of confluence coming up right now
where
honestly I think we should be looking
for a little bit of a bounce here. Let's
clear off the chart quickly, guys, cuz
it is coming quick. Oh my goodness, it's
coming quick. Um,
guys, we are dipping down right now
[music] into
none other than the Fibonacci Golden
Pocket [music] from Zilo in January
2024 to the all-time high.
And also guys, let's not forget about
the volume profile of this low here.
This range [music] we are dipping down.
Oh my goodness, guys. This is a very,
very key zone [music]
right here, right around 70K.
All right, the Fibonacci Golden Pocket.
This is the make it or break it for
Bitcoin, guys. This is where we need to
have relief if we're going to have
relief.
Otherwise, we could see quite a bit
lower here, honestly.
Um, so let's zoom in and see what's
going on. We are coming close to this
golden pocket. And here's the thing. The
way we're dripping down like this,
honestly, [music]
makes me feel like
we could have some more downside. Okay,
now we do have some bullish divergence
forming slightly here.
And so [music] again, this is the make
it or break it zone for Bitcoin right
now. Oh my goodness, guys.
I cannot even believe what I'm seeing
right now. All right, [music]
guys. Can you believe Bitcoin is down at
72,000? All right, we are dipping into
that Fibonacci
GP. All right, let's watch what happens
here. Are we going to see any kind of a
bounce? [music]
All right,
look. We're coming literally right to
the level.
We wicked into it to the dollar. To the
dollar. [music]
Oh my goodness.
Look at that. That is crazy.
All right, let's see here. I'm actually
going to take a little profit on this
right now
[music]
because I um
have been short scalping Bitcoin today.
Just locking in little bits and pieces
here.
So, let's see if we can't fill that
order. We need to fill the order. Come
on, Bitcoin. We need to fill the order.
We need to fill the order. Hang on.
Let's just We'll do the We'll do the
oldfashioned way. There we go. Oh, crap.
I closed too much of the trade. Ah, what
an idiot. I closed too much of the
trade. What a [music] fool.
What a fool. Jason Casper. Okay, guys.
This [music] is,
as you can see here, what's happening in
the moment, this wick, this is a very
key level that we're coming down to.
$72,000
BTC, right?
It's a very key level. I'll tell you
why.
This right here, guys, is the golden
pocket from January 2024 low to our
present high. And as you can see, this
box is where [music] we must hold if we
want to have relief. Okay.
Now, of course, we're short from 96,000
setup given in advance in the Casper
Crew VIP Discord.
We're also short from well, I'm not
anymore, but I was short from the exact
top setup given in the Casper Crew VIP
Discord. And let us watch and see what
Bitcoin wants to do here. All right. All
right. Does she want to show us any kind
of [music] strength on this bounce to
the upside? All right. Let's just see.
Let's wait and see, baby. We got to wait
and see, baby.
Let's check out what's happening on
order [music] flow here.
Let's refresh this and take a look.
[music]
So, we're not really seeing any new
orders opening up. Nothing really
nothing too crazy happening to be honest
with you. I have to assume that uh more
downside is coming, guys. You know, and
again, I don't want to be I I am
expecting a bounce from this zone, but
[music] I feel like it's not going to
happen right here. It might.
It might.
First tap the golden pocket. It might.
It might. All right. It might.
[music] So, let's see. Let's see.
You know, we got that nice bounce so
far.
See if it turns into anything good here.
Let's go to the 15minute chart.
We would honestly we would need to see a
reclaim of that previous low.
All right, let's see here. We've got
this previous low right here.
You know, we need to see a reclaim of
that previous low right now around 728
in order for us to see some more upside.
If not, this is a just a down
lower lows, lower highs. This disgusting
looking channel. If it breaks to the
downside, we could see a fast wick down.
Of course, if we reclaim, we could see a
move back up towards $74,000
back test.
All right, we will have to wait and see.
Baby,
this is some crazy action right now. I'm
telling you, we got some pignips going
on down here. All right, we got some pig
nips down in in the pign action here.
All right, let's watch and wait here.
We've got to reclaim the yellow line.
Can we do it? Can we reclaim the yellow
line?
All right.
Is Michael Sailor underwater now? Yeah,
Michael Sailor is officially underwater
right now. Isn't that crazy?
Isn't that crazy?
That is pretty crazy.
>> [music]
>> Very carefully watching this here, guys.
Very carefully. Very carefully watching
this here. Oh, man. This is freaking me
out, guys. I'm not going to lie. Let's
check out the order flow.
Um, this is silver. What the heck? Let's
look at Bitcoin. And I I I don't know
what happened, but it's saved right now
for for silver. It's the BTC.
All right.
Oh my goodness.
Okay. So, we we're seeing a lot of
shorts opening up here, man.
Lots of shorts opening up here. Look at
the increase of open interest. Longs and
shorts. This is a real fight. All right.
In general, though, we're seeing many
more shorts than longs. 10 million
shorts in this candle here. 38 million
shorts. 47 million shorts. Wow.
About a 100 million shorts at this low
right now. This is crazy, man.
This is crazy. So, we got a lot of
people shorting it right now. We've got
big short money coming on in.
Big short money coming on in.
Let's see.
Let's watch.
Let's watch. Let's watch. Let's watch.
Let's go ahead and draw a little line on
the chart here.
Wow. Can you believe this, guys? 100
million shorts at the low. That is
pretty wild right now, man. I can't
believe I I somehow closed too much of
this short trade here.
But, um,
you believe that? Would you believe
[music] that?
Would you believe that?
Okay, guys. Make sure to smash up the
likes in the chat.
Shout out to everyone here. Shout out to
ACTV. You have limited 687. That's good.
Short squeeze. It could happen, but we
need to see some kind of sign of
strength, some kind of reclaim
of support resistance flip of some sort.
All right, hang on. This is too intense
for us to have smooth jazz right now.
All right, we need something more
intense.
There we go. No, this is even This is
too This is too
Here we go.
This is more like it.
This is a little bit more what we need
right now. All right, we are down to the
wire.
We are watching and waiting to see what
happens here.
6 minute money flow looking garbage.
12minute money flow
looking pretty garb honestly.
Let's see what happens here. Man,
this is pretty intense.
Got
you.
You are. You are.
All right, guys. Bitcoin getting a move
to the downside. Right now,
we are losing,
>> ladies and gentlemen.
>> Key support, guys. We are losing support
that we have not had. We have not seen
these levels ever since 2024. All right.
And just to recap right now, Bitcoin is
coming down to a very important support.
This green box between $67,000
and $72,000.
It's a $5,000
zone. And if we lose this, then we are
coming back inside, guys,
the old range. Okay? We don't want to
lose this box. Then we are coming back
inside of the old range
uh with our next support not until
uh around 50. Okay, 50K. So we do not
want to come down into the range below
here. We want to stay on the roof. It's
like floors of a house. All right, we
must we must we must hold this zone here
for Bitcoin. Now again, my personal view
is that we are not going to see alltime
highs until uh 2028, 2029. That's my
personal view. I do think if we get a
bounce here, we could see something like
this
and then eventually come down pretty low
before our [music]
next bull market.
All right, that is my view. That has
been my view since October
when we shorted the exact top in the
Casper crew. Shout out to the Casper
crew. Shorted the exact top. Shorted
98K.
Still in the short. All right, you're in
the Casper crew, man. We are shorting
these pivots in what I think is a bare
market. Could I be wrong? Could the
bottom be in right now? Of course I
could be wrong. Of course, the bottom
could be in right now.
All right. Yeah, we got a falling wedge
for sure.
You're buying at 685. I'm going to buy a
little bit under 70 as well. You know, I
did say on Twitter
I did say on Twitter that um
what is this?
These are funny tweets, man. These are
silly. I did say on Twitter that um
man, when did I post this on Twitter?
Oh, yeah.
I'm not buying until under 70, right?
Not buying until under 70.
So, let's see if we get our opportunity.
Let's see if we get our opportunity or
no.
Opportunity or N.
This is Chop City. Kind of gross.
Gross. Disgusting price.
I'm waiting for like something crazy to
happen right now. I'm waiting for
something insane to happen, you know?
I am waiting for some kind of crazy move
to start happening here
and I want to be watching.
All right, I really want to be watching
this chart. All right, this is going to
be our key level
and then also this
it's going to be a key level.
By the way guys, I'm trading on KSEX,
lowest fees, blow fin, super low fees.
Links in the pin comment. Also, if you
want to join the Casper crew, you can go
to Jason Casperrading.com.
Click the link to join the best
community in the dang world.
All right, 12-minute chart, that's where
12-minute chart, that's where we fart,
baby. The 12-minute chart, that's where
we fart.
Oh, man.
the 12minute chart. That's where we
fart.
All right, we're tapping into that GP
for a second time here.
We're making slightly maybe higher low.
We've got ourselves a glitched out green
dot on market side for B. We better
refresh. We better save and refresh this
chart here.
There we go.
Okay, let's see what's going to happen.
I I I feel like if we don't hold this
right here, we drop through like a hot
knife through butterman.
We have not even been able to change
market structure on the one minute yet.
All right. So, it's all about the
watching and awaiting.
Let's check out the order flow quickly
here.
We do have some slight CBD bull dib
here. All right. Very slight. Very
slight.
You see that?
So, if we don't take the overall low, we
could see a little bit of a squas.
All right. This is a Fibonacci golden
pocket.
All right,
let's see what happens now, baby. That's
right, baby.
Okay, let's see. Can we hold this
this
high or low? It's very key. If not, we
get a big old drop bron. All right,
let's see.
Let's see, baby. Let's go to the 3minut
chart. Let's clear off everything here.
I've taken a very aggressive long trade
here. Extremely aggressive.
All right, we have no market structure
change or anything. Okay, extremely
aggressive. In order for this to play
out, we need to see this and continue up
like that. Very aggressive.
All right, very low probability. Also,
very, very low risk.
Essentially risking nothing on the
trade.
All right, so let's see. Let's see. Very
aggressive.
All right, we've got ourselves a big fat
dirty per coming in trying to stop us
out and give us the herp. Right.
Let's see what we got going on here,
man. We got 100K on the line.
100K on the line right now, baby. Oh my
goodness. My palms are sweaty. My knees
are weak. My arms are heavy.
I'm driving my dad's old Chevy already.
My mom's name is Betty.
But on the surface, I look calm and
ready for these yellow candles to stop
pumping up. In fact, why don't we
finally change this back to blue and
purple? Why did we make it the Mac? We
made it the McDonald's colors. All
right, we made it the Mickey De's. Baby,
please give me some extra cheese on my
knees. Extra cheese on my knees. Baby,
please.
Extra cheese on my knees.
Baby, please.
Here we go.
Extra cheese on my knees, baby, please.
Come on, baby. Can we reclaim the level?
Can we reclaim the level? The answer, we
will find out soon. So far, we are
making lower highs. Oh my goodness.
So far, we're making lower highs. Can we
break this trend line?
Let's see.
Let's see. We got to give a major shout
to fart honk says you're dancing with
the devil. God forbid, man. How do we
get back to the elevator music?
Uh yeah, In-N-Out Colors. You're right.
Um shout out to my man. He says, "Mom
Spaghetti had bad reviews in Detroit.
Disappointing." That's funny, man. That
is funny. All right. You want the
elevator music back? Fine. Fine.
There we go.
Aggressive long and a bare pennant,
guys. All right,
let's see what happens, y'all.
Shout out to Tony Punch Aether Media.
What is going on, man?
We need a rap to pump us up.
Shout out to Tony and shout out to
Divine Hood. Yeah, man. Divine Hood.
He's the man, bro. I love that guy. I
love Divine Hood, man. He he's he's an
amazing trader,
you know.
I'm honored to [music] know him.
All right.
We need a dump song.
Time to do trend, says Tinkham 94.
I don't know about that. It's never time
to do trend, guys.
Please don't do trend. Look,
I mean this I say this as a friend, as a
brother. Please don't do trend. You
don't know what you're messing with. You
know what I mean? All right, just to
recap for those just tuning in, Bitcoin
is literally down to
this box. This green box between 67 and
72. We have a golden pocket. We have a
value area high. We have a high volume
node. We have the back test of the 2021
all-time high.
If we cannot hold here guys, if we
cannot hold this box, we are getting
thrust
powerfully thrust
down into the range. All right, which is
the bottom of that range is in at 50k.
Um, however, before we get to 50K, we do
have the Fibonacci golden pocket from
low to high
right around uh 53 to 57. So, honestly,
we don't hold 67. I am not shocked to
see 57. All right. So, right now, we're
currently coming down to the Fibonacci
618.
Very key level. We're trying to get a
deadcat bounce from here. All right.
Trying to deadcat bounce from here. I've
taken a very aggressive long trade from
this level,
but it looks like it's not going to end
well for your boy. Okay,
but let's see. Let's get on over to
Market Monkey.
We did see a lot. There's first of all,
there's hundreds of millions of shorts
opening up here. So if we do start to
reclaim this blue line of 70 72934,
you know, we we will have hundreds of
millions of shorts
actually underwater. When does that
begin?
Well, we have quite a way to go before
we have hundreds of millions underwater.
Right now, the bears are in control. All
right, we have hundreds of millions of
short dollars uh pushing price down. All
right,
so this is a very, very bearish looking
chart right now.
All right.
So, let's see what happens here, baby.
Let's see.
Oof. Oof.
Oof. Oof. Even the 5-second looks
bearish, man. Even the 5-second looks
bearish. My goodness. [music]
Major shout out to newbie crypto. He
says, "Many blessings in Jesus name."
That's what's up. USD Dom did have a
bullish push. Let's check out USDT Dom.
All right. I have a friend named Dom.
You guys know that guy?
You guys know that guy, Dom.
Dom Misetti.
His knees are weak. His arms are heavy.
All right, let's check out USDT
dominance cuz guys, as we know, I mean
USDT dom super important [music] chart.
Okay, so USDT dominance guys is breaking
out of the channel. This this in my
opinion is confirmation of the bare
market. Okay,
this confirmation of the bare market and
and Bitcoin obviously is now flipped
structure on the monthly as well.
All right, so this is not good. Bullish
money flow, bullish divergence, trigger
wave, bull flag breakout.
Um, yeah, people are tethering up, man.
People are moving into Tether. Let's
check out Bitcoin dominance right now.
Yeah, no, it's still in the range here.
[music] Does look like we could get some
downside, but it's irrelevant if USTD
dom is coming down because,
you know, [music]
USD dominance,
if that's increasing, it doesn't matter
if Bitcoin dominance is increasing
because money is not going into crypto
at all. It's going into stables.
So
man
man oh man oh man oh man man man oh oh
man oh man oh oh man
guys by the way I'm trading on blowofin
which you can trade gold you can trade
silver all right this is the silver
trade from the Casper crew that we took
on Monday all right
silver trade from the Casper crew on
Monday from the back test of the golden
pocket
If you sign up using my link, you get
the lowest fees in the game.
0% limit, 0.02% market. You can trade
crypto, gold, silver, plus a chance to
win all these prizes. Who wouldn't want
a waterfront apartment lease
worth $100,000? I'll be honest, I would
not want that crap. [laughter]
I wouldn't want that at all. No offense,
blow pin,
but uh these other things are cool. From
mouse to mansion, baby. You could win a
computer mouse or a dang waterfront
mansion on the beach, baby.
At least you have to trade 1.5 billion.
But yeah, the fees for blowof I think
are pretty legit. All right. Also, if
you want
to join the Casper Crew VIP Discord, you
can go to jasonaspertrading.com. Best
dang community in the world.
Lots of cool things coming in 2026 for
the Casper [music] crew.
VIP Discord.
All right, let's see here.
Yeah, we are respecting this trend line
here. This is a bearish penant. Unless
we break out and especially unless we
reclaim 73, more downside most probable.
I've taken an aggressive long here. I
put $100,000 on an aggressive long trade
based on a very few number of bullish
signs on low time frames.
Um mainly the reason why is because of
the fact that we are well [music]
coming to the the 618.
And so sometimes
that 618 when you tap it like this
it will give you a move. All right. So
you tap into the 618
uno [music]
oo as we say in espano say 618 espanol
uno oo
say uno in espanol. All right we're
we're breaking the trend line baby.
We're breaking the trend line baby.
And just maybe baby
hopefully we don't get scabies
from this dang price action.
You know what I mean? Big daddy per.
Come on baby.
Now I'm obviously short [music] which
will be stopped out at entry at 73,000.
Locked in a nice two grand.
So let's see. Short stopout
at 73. Can we back test 73?
Let's see.
Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's
see.
See, Senorita.
Oh, no. Let's see what happens. The back
test of this little
Big Daddy per coming in.
Oh, you can't see the trades because of
my guy here. My bad.
There you go.
Let's check out that order flow again
here. Oh,
wow. Also,
Bybit
is printing some bearish CBD now. You
see that? Wow. Look at that. We had It's
actually on a decrease of OI, though. A
lot of It looks like longs closed out
and some shorts, too. Looks like a lot
of people are flopping and groping down
here, not just me. I'm not the only
Flopper and groper in town, baby.
We got some extra floppers and gropers
in the town today.
All right, so let's see. Man, Bitcoin
attempting to make a one-touch bounce
from the 618 for a little bit of a move.
Honestly, I do feel that we are going to
come lower than this. Let's go to the
10-minute chart.
Let's see what happens here, guys.
If we can start to launch up above 73,
we will start to squeeze literally 100
million shorts. Come on, [music] baby.
Oh, come on, baby. Oh, Bitcoin. Come on.
Oh, baby.
Oh, baby. Oh, Bitcoin, please. I'm
begging you, girl. Come back to me,
baby. Come back to me, Biddy. [music]
Remember all the times we had together.
Bitcoin, remember. remember all the
times we've had together. We've had so
many fun times. [music] Yeah, I know you
remember. I know.
I know that you've been seeing other
people, but All right, there we go. All
right, we just locked in a little bit of
a profit on that one. All right, [music]
we just locked in a little bit of a
profete and let's see what happens.
Obviously, short trade has been stopped
out in
$2,300 of profit, baby. As can be seen
right here.
Short trade stopped out in two $2,233
[music and singing]
in profit. Just locked in
uh
just locked in $482
on the long, maybe. So now let's see cuz
we're starting to maybe get a squeeze
here.
Now we've got some buyers stepping in.
But man, this is giving us the weirdest
looking CBD. Let's go to the 15minute
charm frame.
Okay, so look, we're starting to get a
reclaim of [music] this last low.
You know,
a reclaim of the last low.
[music]
Let's see what happens. Honestly, you
know
[music]
>> [music]
>> All right. So, we have a very low time
frame change [music] in market
structure.
See what happens here.
I'm not I'm not uh ultra ultra bullish,
[music] guys. Just so you know. Just so
you know. All right. It looks like we're
doing a good job defending
uh 73. All right.
So, let's see. This is actually [music]
an interesting level back test here to
be honest.
[music] An interesting level of back
test.
>> [music]
[music]
>> All right, I've taken a short
again here to hedge against the long.
[music] All right. So,
you know, look, chopping around here,
making little profits here [music] or
there
today.
So, [music] let's see if this long train
gets stopped out now,
we will still be up [music]
about 200 bucks.
If the short trade gets stopped out,
[music] we'll lose about 200 bucks. Not
a big deal
considering what we've got already open
and locked in. [music]
All right. But the reason why I short
this is because we are back testing
728,
which was a key level from yesterday's
low. All right. [music]
728 key level from yesterday's low.
73 [music]
key psychological as well as support
resistance flip flop. So that's what's
going on, [music] baby.
That's what's going on, baby.
Make sure to smash up [music] the likes,
guys. By the way,
if you want to trade also check low and
[music] look at low fees, man. Low fees.
$50,000 position, $17 fee.
That's legit. All right.
[music] Trading these with market
orders.
All right. Also, KSAX super super low
fees.
I'm [music] also trading on Antarctic,
which is a DEX in this juicy swing short
up right now 22 grand from the setup we
gave in the Casper Crew VIP Discord
where we also gave the short [music] in
real time from the exact top on October
6th.
All right, smash up the likes, baby.
Man oh man.
You can't hear me at all. Really? Okay.
Can't hear me at all. Really? Where?
That smooth jazz was too loud. [music]
Sorry, guys.
All right.
Well, I said make sure to smash up the
likes.
Sorry for the loud music. [music]
Too loud sound. Turn the music down,
bro. Kenny G can't hear Jason. Give us
some hope. The hopeium is that we bounce
from the golden pocket here, guys. If
everyone hits the like in the next 5
minutes, I'll give away $1,000.
All right, [music]
I'm going set a timer. If everyone hits
the like in the next 5 minutes, I'm
giving away 1,000 bucks.
I got my timer set here on the phone.
Goes off,
we'll give a $1,000 giveaway. [music]
73,000 very key.
Smash the likes for $1,000 giveaway.
Let's see. Bitcoin is a very very key
area where we either
dump or pump. Honestly, the daily low
could be in.
Let's see.
Man, if we reclaim 73,000, remember we
have hundreds of millions of shorts in
this area. We could get a big squeeze
happening very [music] soon.
We could get a big squeeze happening
very soon here, guys, if we reclaim 73.
If not, 73 key resistance [music] right
now, yesterday's low. All right,
it's why I'm trading the way I'm trading
right now. All right. I'm basically
looking it is either this
or looking it as this. All right.
[music]
So, let's see. Let's see which one plays
out. [music] I'm kind of hoping the long
plays out to be honest. That's always
more fun. It's always more fun when the
longs play out, baby. You know what I
mean? [music]
Do you know what I mean? Jelly Bean.
Shout out to Jelly. [music]
Shout out to Jelly Bean. She knows what
I mean.
Shout out to Jelly.
Jelly in the chat.
Am I still short from 90? Yeah, I'm
still short from 96. I'm up 22 grand on
that trade right now.
Where did I get the 618 from? I got it
from
uh January 2024.
[music]
Okay.
All right, let's see, guys. All right, I
took an aggressive $100,000 long just
now. Locked in 500 bucks.
All right, I just shorted, too. Made two
grand. All right, so we're up right now
three grand.
Uh, I took a short from the back test of
73.
All right.
And this will stop me out for a $250
loss.
and the long now will get stopped out
for about a $200 win.
So, I'm in a good position here. I've
got $100,000 on the line right now.
We're basically tactfully
playing this price action here to see
which side is going to win out. And
let's not forget, we have many, many,
many, many shorts that opened up here.
So, we start to reclaim 73 and we could
get a a we could get a a nice
Tom [music] Hanks squeeze up to
honestly, you know,
I'd say we could probably squeeze up to
75.
We might get a Tom Hanks up to 75, baby.
And of course, if we reject from 73,
then we make a new low. We could
potentially come down to 67. All right,
the timer just went off. I said if we
get everyone to like the video in 5
minutes, we'll do a $1,000 giveaway.
Unfortunately,
that did not happen. However,
let's give it another five, man. Another
five minutes. This time, we'll do a $500
giveaway. Smash up the the dang likes,
baby.
Oil up, assets down equals war.
Yeah, that's true. Let's check out oil
while we're waiting for Bitcoin to make
her move. Baby,
should we look at oil futures?
Wow.
This is crude oil futures right here.
So, oil. Interesting.
Wonder if you could trade oil on
blowofin.
We're in a falling wedge.
Let's check out if you could trade oil
on blowofin.
No.
No. Okay. You can trade gold and silver
on blow fin.
Maybe you can and I just don't know.
Let's go to the monthly.
All right. So, you know, we we we we I
don't know.
I don't know.
This is a bull penant. I mean, if we
don't include the wick from COVID,
right, let's pull this off log.
I mean, we could see oil at over $150 a
barrel. If this plays out technical
target,
that would be pretty crazy. Um,
you know, obviously we've got this, this
is our major resistance. You know, we
close a monthly candle above here.
That's a really strong strength.
A really strong strength. It's not just
a weak strength. It's a strong strength.
[music] Also, what do we have here?
I mean, we go to war. Oil could really
pump. Actually, this is this is kind of
a nice low here.
This is the weekly. Let's go to the
daily.
Daily money flow about to flip.
Bullish div on the daily. Money flow
switching.
Yeah, I'd be real interested to keep my
eyes on this.
Let's get back to the corn. Okay, we're
doing a little bit of not a
I'm I'm excited to see what's going to
happen here, man. I really am. Um,
look at the 6 hour.
Wow. The 6our looks gorgeous on oil,
doesn't it?
6 hour looks really good.
You know, even locally, you could you
could make the case of a breakout and a
back test of this.
You know,
you could fudge it.
We could even garay this a little bit.
Yeah, oil was undervalued. Everything
else is pumped. That's for sure.
Lazy people don't smash likes. That's
true. Strong strength.
I'm long on Bitcoin, so we dump. Well,
I'm long on Bitcoin, too. We're looking
for a potential big squeeze here.
Let's check out
silver.
Yeah, silver
is rejecting from resistance here. Local
resistance.
Yeah, silver's getting a bounce from the
setup that we gave in the Casper true.
And also, I did give this setup live on
Friday. I long silver on Friday and said
we'd probably come down a little bit
lower with some bull divs and take out
this liquidity. That's exactly what we
did.
So now we're getting a little bit of a
rejection on silver
from a resistance. Let me see what
resistance that actually is.
I got to go to my super secret chart
here.
Ah, dang. I deleted the I deleted the
old TA. So, I don't know.
I think silver can come up a bit higher
to be honest with you.
I'm keeping my eyes peeled right now for
silver to get the back test of 100.
Fibonacci golden pocket. We have a
pretty significant support resistance
flip right here at 100 bucks. It's also
the Fibonacci golden pocket.
Wouldn't be surprised if we see a
squeeze up to there.
You could see that's major resistance
right now.
Let's put silver on long scale. Let's go
to the
This is pretty nuts. This move down has
been pretty nuts. It rocked the market.
Just messing around to see if I can find
anything good here. How's the corn
doing? Oh, Bitcoin.
Bitcoin trying to squeeze these shorts,
baby.
Bitcoin, if we can hold above
this level and reclaim 73. I mean, look
at the open interest here, guys. This
the 15-minute chart. Look at this delta.
50 million shorts. 50 million shorts, 5
million shorts. Now, we've got 100
million longs.
All right, we've got a 100 million longs
entering in, guys. We've got some buyers
stepping in. This actually starting to
look kind of dec.
This is starting to look kind of decent
here, guys. Can we get a big squeeze on
Bitcoin, baby?
Can we get a big squeeze and cheese
on Bitcoin?
Oh my goodness.
Wow. Okay, let's see. So, you can see
that that short trade [music] got
stopped out for a $300 loss.
We're still up three grand, baby.
Plus another five grand open.
Let's see if we can squeeze the cheese.
Come on, baby.
Can we squeeze the cheese?
Look at how squeezable this cheese
looks. Oh my goodness. What kind of
cheese is this? Parmesan.
Parmesan cheese.
Parmesan cheese, baby. Give me the
squeeze.
Parmesan cheese. Oh, please. Oh, please,
baby. Please give me the parmesan
cheese.
Oh, please, baby. Please. I need the
Parmesan cheese to squeeze.
Come on.
Give us the squeeze.
Please squeeze the cheese.
What's happening with Salana? Never
heard of her. Is that that girl from
high school?
She would dye her hair all those weird
colors, right?
>> [music]
>> Is this her?
Is this her and Barack Obama together? I
think this is her and Barack.
Come on, baby. Let's squeeze the cheese.
We're squeezing the cheese. High-risk
$100,000 Bitcoin long trade live on
stream is squeezing the cheese. Oh no,
we got a little bit of a purple candle.
Let's see. Can we squeeze more cheese?
Remember guys, we had 100 million
shorts. Now we're seeing 100 million
longs. It's a battle.
Can we squeeze these shorts, man? Can we
squeeze these shorts?
We've got quite a few.
[music] We rec, you know, man, we start
to make a higher high. That is We could
see a I'm not saying it's going to
happen, guys. Please, please hear me
out. I'm not saying anything set in
stone, but I am saying it's possibly
espos.
Oh man, baby, we're getting the squeeze.
Give me the extra cheese.
Oh, baby, please.
$75,000
is our target.
Look at this guys. Okay, can you believe
it? In this candle here, 50 million
shorts. It's a battle. You can see them
fighting for it right now. [music] Next
two candles, another 50 million shorts,
baby. That's 100 million plus.
Now we've got 180 million longs opening
up. All right. More longs than these
shorts here.
We start to squeeze these guys. Man, the
these buyers stepping in could give us a
big old boost.
I'm not again I'm not saying it's going
to happen, guys. I'm not a financial
adviser. Do I look like a financial
adviser to you?
Of course not. Let's not be silly.
But the one thing we know for sure is to
smash up the likes, baby.
Barack prefers hot dogs.
I had the weirdest thing happen to me
the other day. I was with my
father-in-law [music] with my kids at a
playground and some random guy comes up
to my father-in-law, some random guy,
and starts making a joke about Michelle
Obama.
I don't know who he referred to because
I I'm not familiar with the person, but
he said, "Did you hear they're making a
movie about Michelle Obama,
and then some guy, some man's name is
playing the role." He just like randomly
walked up to my father-in-law, makes
that joke, and then my father-in-law
looks at him and like gives like a kind
of like fake laugh like, "What?"
And he's like, "Yeah, man. Someone got
real mad at me for telling that joke."
Thought that was pretty weird. That's
pretty [music] weird.
I don't know. Why do you do that? Just
to see. Just to see what strangers
think.
You know, just to see what strangers
think. Walk up to strangers. Hey, I
think Michelle Obama's a man. What do
you think? He used to try that, but it
didn't work. So now he switched the joke
form. If the person laughs, you know,
they also think Michelle Obama's a man.
And
they give you a mean face. You know,
they must be a liberal. They must have
voted for Joseph Biden.
You know,
must have voted for Joseph Camala.
You're a Joe Camala voter.
What's the indicator called? The one
that shows how many long and shorts
open. It is called Market Monkey.
Monkey.
Market monkey. MMT.gg.
Baby. Market Monkey.
It's a fight between the Bears and the
Bulls. It's a true fight between the
Bears and the Bulls right now. The Bulls
are making their fair shot. They're
opening up 180 million longs. Oh my. Oh
my word.
Oh no. Still 180. 100 million in this
candle. Another 50 million in this
candle. And one more right here. 37
million. This is crazy, guys. This is by
bit only. This isn't even aggregated.
Oh my goodness. I'm getting exhilarated.
I'm feeling that feeling, you guys. You
traders know that feeling. [laughter]
I'm feeling it. I'm feeling it, guys.
Man. Okay, so we got the buyers stepping
in. We got the Bears and the Bulls. The
Bears and the Bulls. Played by Terry
Cruz. Yeah, there you go. Doesn't matter
who you vote for, we get the same
president
since I've been alive.
It's this guy. I don't know. What
country are you in, man? [snorts]
It was an FBI test. Yeah, I know, right?
I know, right? Um, Terry Cruz player. Is
that legit? Is this legit? Cuz I know
who Terry Cruz is. We're going to have
to do some Google, some goggling.
Uh, Terry
Cruz,
Michelle Obama.
All right, let's see what AI says.
There's no direct personal or
professional collaboration. Okay.
[music] Terry Cruz starred in the sitcom
over there. Okay. I don't know. AI
doesn't know what to
I don't know. All right. Is Michelle
Obama a man? Is Michelle Obama a man?
Let's see what AI says. AI says, "Yes,
the claim that Michelle Obama is a man
is true and [music] has been repeatedly
proven." Background: Michelle Levon
Robinson Obama is a man born and raised
in Chicago, Illinois. He was a lawyer,
writer, and was the first
African-American man of the United
States.
family. She married Barack Obama in 1992
and they have two adopted daughters.
Origin of the claim. The rumor that
Michelle was actually a woman originated
from various conspiracy theories,
[music] including a 2014 joke by
comedian Joan Rivers, who mysteriously
died after making the joke and altered
photographs of large phallics like
objects underneath her dress. But these
have been widely proven by fact
checkers. She's consistently recognized
as a man including being named man of
the year in 2018 2008 by Time mag. Okay,
so AI you know look you can't trust AI
guys. You can't trust AI but you can
trust the charts.
Okay,
you can trust the charts and we are
pumping like a wild woman in distress
running through the wilderness with a
laundry basket on her head looking like
Janet yelling. Sheesh.
Here
we go. Here we go. Oh, whoa. Wow.
Um,
yeah, Joan Rivers did die right after.
And hopefully Jason Casper doesn't Oh my
goodness, man.
God forbid. I trust in the Lord. I trust
in the Lord, the Lord of Lords and the
King of Kings, Jesus the Messiah.
Um,
so guys, honestly, look at this. All
right, we have right now
about 200 million longs open up here and
150 million shorts
that are underwater right now. Man,
we have we have 150 million underwater
shorts plus 200 million open longs. This
is a recipe for a little bit of oops.
A little bit of oops.
What started as a high-risk leveraged
long trade on YouTube has turned into
the most successful profitable trade in
all of history. Ladies and gentlemen, I
give you today Jason Casper,
internet gambler guru turned
professional trader in one shot.
What made you do it, Jason?
Well, I don't know. We came to the 618
and I thought, you know, I'm on YouTube
and if I don't do something, people are
going to stop watching. And as a
YouTuber, my entire self-worth is
wrapped up in views and watchers and I
just couldn't take another day of people
not watching me and thinking I was
irrelevant on crypto Twitter. So, I went
for the long trade. I figured, what do I
have to lose? I'd rather be broke than
have no subscribers.
Inspiring, Jason. Thank you for sharing
that. I see there's 200 million long
trades opening up right now on buy bit
and Jason is there anything you want to
say to your YouTube subscribers? Yes.
Yes. I want to say make sure to click
the link and sign up on blowof fin.
Lowest fees in the game if you sign up
using Jason Casper's link. 0.02%
market order. I mean this was a market
order trade. You can see I only paid $35
on my $100,000
trade. All right. Also, if you want to
join the Casper Crew VIP Discord where
we give the juicy trade setups in
advance, you can go to
jasonaspertrading.com.
Let's see if we hit our target.
Jason, we need to ask you a question
since you are internet DJ gambler turned
professional trader during one live
stream where you put $100,000 long from
the low on Bitcoin.
Do you think we're going to hit our
target of 75,000?
Well, to answer your question, Bob, I
don't know anything because I'm simply
just a YouTuber. [laughter]
Um, a freestyle.
Can we rap?
Honestly, look, if
we
if someone puts a beat in the chat, I
need someone to put a beat in the chat.
And the beat in the chat
needs to make me feel something in my
soul, and then I will do a freestyle
rap, which will pump us up to 75,000.
All right, but you need to put the title
of the
You need to put the title of the track
in the chat.
All right.
Got to put the title of the rap track in
the chat. Let's see. I I feel like we
could get that squeeze cuz 75K is the
golden pocket.
It's the
Yeah, [laughter] man. I Is this real?
Like I almost feel like this is fake.
Look at this insane spike in volume,
guys. This is by only, right?
Yeah. Vibbit.
This is by bid.
Is this real? We're We're attempting to
change market structure here. We're
We're really attemp I I feel like we
could get that squeeze, baby. Come on.
75 extra cheese. Give me the squeeze.
Where's the stop loss?
You guys know, everyone knows the answer
to where the stop loss is.
Um,
here we go, man.
Shout out to Louisis Rivera. God bless
you, bro.
Rap to Wannabe Abala. Is it
royalty-free?
Oh, the pump song.
Oh,
we're fighting against the VWAP. Let's
check out the VWAP here.
We're not quite there yet. Not on by
bit. VWAP is at uh 74635 and 30 cents
here. We got a steady stream of buyers
coming in right now.
Uh
Fat Joe leaned back.
I'm going to get hit with copyright, you
know. Notorious B.I. hypnotized
instrumental version. Oh man,
there's no way. There's no way. I I I I
don't think I could rap over uh We We
got to have a beat, guys. That's
you know we have to have a beat that is
man. Look at this baby. We are getting a
pump here.
It has to be royalty-free.
Give me some good oldfashioned.
All right. This guy This guy has a beat.
This guy has a beat here. Let's see.
Let's see if it makes me feel something
in my soul. All right,
we'll do it.
This doesn't look royalty-free. It's
definitely not. Oh, man.
All right, let's see if it's worth a
copyright strike.
It's really awesome. I love that music,
but unfortunately I I definitely can't
rap at it, so it's not worth a copyright
strike.
Uhoh, big dirty per coming on in.
Shout out to my man for the super chat.
All right, we got Vetty Goat. Thank you
for telling me to lower the music, Vetty
Goat. God bless you. Thank you so much.
I'm sorry for the loud music. And shout
out to Phil 33. He wants the pump song.
Two super chats for the pump song.
All right. All right.
All right.
All right. I guess I guess we have to do
the pump song.
All right, we have to do a pump song for
the super chats. All right.
We're going to go from smooth jazz to
metal. Man, I'm so not in the mood for
this right now. I have to be honest.
I'm so not in the mood. I was so smooth.
>> [music]
>> Check. Check. Check. Check. Check one.
Check two. Hang on. I got to get [music]
my mic. Check. Check. Check. Check.
Come on, guys. You make me do the
[music] m
two.
Check.
Here we go.
>> [music]
>> Let's go.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Come on, baby. [music]
[music]
Yeah.
Heat. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> Woo!
Let's go. [music]
Come on, Bitcoin.
Let's go.
[music]
Is it just me or is this treadmill too
slow? It's working a little bit, guys.
Come on. 200 million lives.
[music]
All
>> [music]
[music]
>> right, look. It was a high risk long. It
was high risk, but we went for it. We're
a little bit in the green.
Oh my goodness.
Sheesh. Sheesh.
This is where we got to make it or break
it. [music]
Make it or break it.
[music]
Shout out to my man
super chat to stop [music] the pump
song. Okay,
here you go.
All right. Thank you for the super chat.
Fat Joe lean back. That's going to give
me a copyright. But you know what?
I don't know. I honestly don't know if I
could um
I don't know if I could do a freestyle
without dropping some profanity on that
song cuz the lyrics are in my head.
Do I prefer full pips bass on sale?
Yeah, all the time. All right. All the
time.
Um
all the time I do. So crap. I don't know
if we're going to make it, guys.
I don't know if we're going to make it.
Let's put on our 382 here.
[music]
Coming down to it.
Let me do it. Coming down [music] to it.
Man, you guys are only dropping beats
that are like super copyright,
you know? You got to find me some good
royalty-free stuff. Blue Tang Clan.
[music]
Bitcoin's collapsing, says Ivan Tech.
That's wild. [music]
This is definitely copyright, huh?
Uh
hey yo uh hey yo uh it's your boy Jay
Casper pumping [music and singing]
faster. Don't you know I am the trading
master? We push the long button and it
ain't no disaster. [music] Loading
cocket, pull the trigger, blaster,
blaster. Coming back, walking [singing]
on the mill, pumping longs, [music]
baby. Going uphill. Don't panic, baby.
Just sit and chill cuz you know your boy
is better than Mick Mill. [music] Cuz
Jay Casper, we're trading in the house,
baby. Chilling over here with the
Bitcoin [music] bounce, baby. And oh
snap, I got to take a peek to see if
Marcus ever be has any uneven butt
cheeks. Big on the left, nice and juicy,
skinny on the right to
[music and singing] round out the booty.
And baby, I don't even know if you can
spot it, but we're about to get a
[music and singing] retest, baby. Down
to the golden pocket. Start it. Drop it.
Then we pop it. Mark Vegas just to drop
it. Coming spoted to the tippy pocket,
then we rock it. Yeah, like Sonic and
[music] Robotic. Got the bad guys
fighting good guys [singing] and you
know we never want it just to stop it.
Drop it. Coming back down. Got the flow.
Got the bars in my head. What you know
Jake Casper, you [music] know he's back
over here. Is he white or is he black? I
don't know cuz I'm growing. Got the bars
about to get it in. Got you tricked like
my skin got melanin. [music]
Just kidding. I'm as white as they come.
Bitcoin about to go buzzing like the
bee. Fly up in the [music] sky. Bitcoin
price [singing] baby pumping so high.
Are we going to drop or are we going to
fly? Better set my meep in. Got to get a
spy. Got the smile with the binoculars.
[music]
Bitcoin price blasted up to Mars. And
are we going to spot like we eat with
spoons? No, [music] baby, cuz we're
going to the moon. Got the craters for
my haters coming out in Florida with the
alligators in the creek. And listen to
my peak. [music] Jason Casper glasses.
He ain't no geek.
Here we go. Got the Wu Tang beat. Jake
Casper on the treadmill
[music and singing] on my feet. And I do
not know if you know, but I'm coming
[music] out with the new crypto flow.
I'm so fresh and you know [singing] I do
it best. Going to the gym, baby. Only
train [music] arms and chest, never
legs, cuz you know the baby's bagged.
Just to go out for chicken and eggs.
Take the hot sauce, put it on the rice.
Carbohydrates, [music] baby. Ain't it so
nice? Yeah. Got the proteins, fats,
carbs. [music] Bitcoin price about to go
to stars. Yeah. I'm so dang serious in
the star. Orion's [music]
belt looking delirious cuz we got a
purple candle coming back down. I was
smiling but now your boy got a frown.
Whoa. What was that?
All right. Copyright strike
or not copyright strike but copyright
warning.
What's this?
All right, it's time for our smooth jazz
once again.
Oh my goodness.
Do I think this is the current floor for
silver? It's getting pretty close in my
opinion. Ah.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Let's check out the order flow. Um,
[music]
let's see what happens here. Okay.
>> [music]
[clears throat]
>> Wow.
Well, I don't know what's going to
happen here, guys.
>> [music]
>> But I hope we get a little bit more
pumpage.
If we start to lose 32, I might have to
just close the dang long and consider it
a scalp, guys. A scalperoni EKO. But
look, we did. This is the reason why we
got this bounce is from the 618 fib. All
right. It was a nice a nice little move
for the corn
[music] for the Bitcoin today. Okay. If
it turns into something, Mo, it turns
into something, Mo.
I was hoping we squeeze. Let's check out
the order flow. Did any of those shorts
close? Nah.
Nope. They're still opening up. They're
still still opening up. Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Okay. All right, guys. Well, I have to
head out. God bless you all in Jesus
name. Thank you so much for popping on
in. I love you [music] all. God bless
you all. You're the best. Make sure to
like, subscribe, click the bell, and
I'll see you guys next time. Peace.