https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K0tnKP-cg2o
this is one of my favorite easy scalping
strategies that you can use to make a
few hundred dollars a day easily I use
this strategy to take a short trade from
right up here and I also used it to take
a long trade from this Wick right down
here so make sure to like the video
subscribe to the channel and click the
bell for notifications because we are
bringing you the juiciest trading
strategies here on YouTube this strategy
is meant to be used on boring ranging
market conditions so for example going
back now two or three days the Bitcoin
price has literally been trading
sideways we're not in an uptrend we're
not in a downtrend we have a clearly
defined High and a clearly defined low
now when you have market conditions like
this you have to think to yourself that
they're going to be a lot of people
looking at this saying you know what
this is a Bear Flag I'm going to enter
into a short trade I'm gonna put my stop
loss above that last High because if we
start to break up above then it's
probably not a bear flag and I need to
get out of my trade and then you have
other people who look at this and say
you know what this looks like a nice
bounce I think I'm going to enter a long
in here I'm gonna put my stop loss
underneath the last low because you know
if we take out this low here it probably
means we're gonna dump right now what
does this mean this means the market
makers right the big players in the
market are going to be hunting those
stop losses and after they stop out
everybody they're then going to reverse
the price so when you see something like
this you have a perfect storm for a
vault to move up bam stop out of the
shorts vaults moved down bam stop out of
the Longs and then come back into the
rage so if you see this what you're
going to do is you're first going to
Mark out that high
that you see in the sideways range and
then you're going to come and Mark out
that low
okay then what you're going to do is
You're simply going to wait
you're going to set an alert in trading
view maybe right around here maybe right
around here so that if the price starts
to get to move up or down you can come
to the chart and take a look but you're
going to be looking basically to short
if the price takes out the high of the
range and you're going to be looking too
long if price takes out the lows of the
range but only under certain conditions
what you're going to do is if the price
starts to come above the high you're
going to look at your oscillator now I
like to use an oscillator called Market
Cipher B this is by far the most
accurate oscillator you can use for
trading I'm going to show you some other
free indicators if you don't have Market
Cipher but if the price is getting
higher and it's actually coming above
our first high and you see over time the
momentum waves are getting lower that is
called a bearish Divergence all right
also known as the upside down
sandbagment Freed Man boob pattern you
can see here sandbagment freed hanging
upside down by the knees but look at the
man boobs all right getting lower over
time as the price is getting higher this
is called a bearish Divergence and if
you see this it means it's not a real
breakout and we're going to get a move
back down into the range now this allows
us to take a short with a very good risk
to reward ratio because we know that we
can put our stop loss above that Wick
and we know we can Target the bottom of
the range this is a four to one risk
reward ratio and you can see the move
happens very very quick now for the long
trade what we're going to do is
basically just the exact opposite right
as the price is getting lower over time
coming down to take out now our low
level which happened right here at 26454
we actually want to see Market Cypher B
getting higher over time which it
absolutely is here and if we go down to
the three minute we see it even better
this is known as the bullish sandbagment
read man boom pattern whereas the price
is getting lower to the Key Sport the
man boobs are getting higher right he
was a bad guy he did some bad things but
the man turned his life around all right
the man turned his life around that we
can clearly see not only his boobs
getting higher his hair as well this is
clearly a bullish sign and now we have a
really good restaurant ratio risk to
reward ratio trade setup on the long
side where we can actually get in right
here stop loss under the wick and we can
Target the high of the range now this is
something very very important guys make
sure if you are scalping like this that
you take profit you pay yourself
ASAP because if you don't well these
moves although they can happen quick
we might just come back down right or
vice versa we might do something like
this and then pump back up so what I
always do is I take half the profits out
usually after we get a move halfway back
into the range and then I move that stop
loss to the entry and then what you can
do
as you get better at this is you can
even compound these trades so for
example the short trade from the high to
the low we actually came back back
tested the Fibonacci golden pocket
retracement
and that is actually how
I actually was able to compound the
short trade that you saw at the
beginning of the stream which is why my
entry is actually somewhere up in here
okay now this strategy is meant for
people who have been trading for a bit
longer because the moves happen very
fast but it's a great strategy
especially when there's very very low
volatility now if you're looking for the
best exchange to scout Bitcoin and other
cryptocurrencies on I highly recommend
Mexi Mexi is the best deal you will find
on fees zero percent limit order fees
point zero one percent Market order fees
for Perpetual Futures you can long and
short at the same time here so if you
see a good swing short position don't
feel afraid to take a scalp long while
keeping your short open and if you are
looking for a community I highly
recommend you check out Jason
caspertrading.com go ahead and click the
link to join the VIP Discord group this
is where we have multiple instructors
giving their trade setups like we gave
the short from the exact top in advance
we gave it along from the exact bottom
in advance we gave this Trading plan
last week to catch these juicy moves in
advance we're going over the live price
action a great educational resource at
Jason Casper trading.com and if you want
to become educated and actually learn
how to do this the right way with a lot
of different strategies for any Market
condition check out the courses we're
proud to announce our newest course by
white Phoenix one of the instructors in
the Casper crew his smart money approach
to trading this is the most
comprehensive course I've ever seen
whether you're a beginner or been in
this game for a while if you're a member
of the VIP Discord he will take two
hundred dollars off the price all right
guys that is my trading strategy video
for today I hope you enjoyed make sure
to like the video subscribe to the
channel click the bell for notifications
may God bless you all in the name of
Jesus Yeshua the Messiah even if you are
not religious I still pray you and your
family are super blessed and obviously
everybody in the next video peace