https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XlTda4dts9k
all right y'all i want to make a quick
video on how awesome fibonacci is for
getting into trades after you put in the
initial high or the initial low and you
get your first pivot pull out the fib
watch this
we reject perfectly off the golden
pocket retracement to get into a short
when we come to the bottom watch this
we bounce perfectly off that fibonacci
golden pocket to get into along when we
come to the top watch this
we reject again from the fibonacci
golden pocket once again offering an
opportunity to get into a short scalp
fibs are so cool and if you learn how to
pull them and if you learn what
confirmations you're looking for they
can give you some really good trade
entries