https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rNmgY78I3UI
today we're going to be talking about
scalping Bitcoin and how we can do this
with a systematic approach so that we
can take accurate entries and lock in
the profits early so make sure to like
the video make sure to subscribe to the
channel make sure to click that Bell for
notifications because we are bringing
you the juiciest technical analysis and
trading strategy videos here on YouTube
I want to walk you through step by step
how I was able to take these five trades
today these five scalp trays the short
the long the short the long and now
currently another long in fact I am
still holding this long right now a few
things I want to go over guys first of
all when we are scalping let's talk
about what scalping is not this is very
very important scalping is not chasing
price Trying to Catch the Wave when you
see a big purple candle maybe you're
going to try and short it if you see a
big blue candle maybe you're going to
try and long it's not even trying to
catch a reversal if you see a big dump
you're not going to try and long
scalping needs to be approached with a
very methodical systematic plan every
single trade that you need to you are
going to be taking here needs to be
planned out and let's also discuss what
exactly is scalping scalping is a way to
extract money from the market utilizing
small moves also using very very good
risk to reward ratios what I mean by
that is this if you take a look at the
long that I'm in right now I literally
only need a 0.05 stop loss
I've already locked in a profit stop
losses to the entry and now my final
Target for the trade is a 1.14 move this
means right now this is 19 times more
potential reward than risk so scalping
needs to be planned very systematically
taking advantage of small movements in
the market using good risk to reward
ratios we're going to be breaking this
down for you exactly how we are going to
be uh take how we're going to be
planning this but before we do it I just
want to show you guys so that you know
I'm being honest with you here that
these are actual trades that I have
taken myself today the ones I showed you
at the beginning of the Stream
if we take a look in the Discord we can
see that yes the not including the long
that I'm in now but I did take the short
the one you saw at the beginning of the
stream I then I took the first long and
then I took that next short which I'm
actually currently still in as well and
then I took the long and now I'm
currently in this long these are all
trades I have taken so the first thing
that we need to do when we are scalping
is we need to have a plan we need to
come to the chart and the first thing we
need to do at least what I do every
single day when I'm planning on my scalp
trades is I need to identify
the key levels that I am looking for a
trade I need to know in advance where
are the trades that I am already looking
to take for that day if you don't know
the level that you are looking to take a
trade from how in the world are you
going to catch a move like this one
right here where literally we caught it
from the exact bottom and all the long
trades that I've taken today I have
literally caught from the exact box
because I was ready and waiting for that
specific level okay that is very very
key right here and so what I do every
day is I come to the chart and I make a
plan I Mark out my key levels and these
are going to be zones of Confluence and
for me what I like to do is I like to go
into my um
I like to go into my Discord and this is
basically where I make my plan for the
day I come to the chart and I'm going to
be making a plan and for me like some
people keep a journal for me I come to
the Chart I find out where are the areas
I am interested in trading so for
example today I was interested well we
can even go back all the way to
yesterday and say I was interested in
taking this short trade if we reclaim 25
285 right if we come above 25 285 and we
get the bearish Divergence on the four
hour time frame I will be looking to
take a trade but then today when I came
to the Chart I was looking for those
zones of Confluence right so I was
saying to myself where are the levels
where price is very likely to find
support where I can look for a scalp
trade and so we always need to approach
the chart as if we are trading a
sideways range because most of the time
we are trading a sideways range and so
let's look at the chart right now
and I just kind of want to walk you
through this process of how I actually
do come about looking for the trades so
what we're going to do is we're going to
be taking a look at the um the chart
right here and if we come to a blank
chart all right I'm going to actually
clear everything off right now so we can
kind of see
what exactly
we would do if we just came to a blank
chart we are always going to be looking
to identify sideways ranges when we are
scalping we want to identify sideways
ranges why because it goes back to the
most basic thing about trading or
investing which is Buy Low and sell high
right Buy Low and sell high if we can
identify areas of high and low we will
then be able to identify areas where
trades are likely to take place so for
the short trade right this was a very
clearly defined High
so I knew if we were going to come above
that clearly defined high with bearish
divergences that would be the place that
I would look to take a trade now why
this level right here the current long
done I'm still in it's because if we go
down to the Daily time frame we can
actually see that yesterday's Daily
candles close right at this exact level
at 24 283 and that can actually now give
us an area of support where we can be
looking for a potential long trade when
we come back down to these lows okay
we're always looking for sideways ranges
but if we just draw a line through the
middle of this range we can see clearly
we have highs here we have the Middle
Point here which can act as a higher or
low and then of course we have our main
low right down here as well right so
this is what we need to do we need to be
coming through the chart and then we
need to be looking for Confluence so
there's other things we can do like pull
fibonaccis like we could pull a fib from
here
it's right here and see that not only
are we coming down to this daily level
but we're also coming down to a
Fibonacci golden pocket retracement we
can pull Fib from this low
down here
to the high and see that look we have
another potential long to take from
these lows we have a low a low and then
we can see if we come back to the low
not only is it a low that we see with
our eyes but it's also a golden pocket
right so we are going to then be looking
for these levels on the chart where we
know price is very likely to get some
kind of a reaction there right price is
likely to get some kind of a reaction
so once we know what levels price are
very likely to have a reaction we need
two things we need to plan how are we
going to get into the trade if price
comes to the level and then we need to
plan how are we going to get out of the
trade if price comes to the level and
things go either correctly for us and
our plan is actually playing out or
things go wrong and our plan is not
playing out and for this we need a few
things we need a series of confirmations
that are going to get us into a trade
okay we need to have a plan we need to
have the level in advance we need to
plan for what type of confirmation is
going to get us into the trade we need
to have a planned stop loss and we need
to have a planned take profit now let's
kind of walk through how this would work
in in real time or I guess in hindsight
so in my Discord this morning by the way
if you want to join the Casper crew VIP
Discord where we give the trade setups
in advance we do three live streams a
day walking you through this price
action we're constantly updating in here
telling you where our mind is at myself
and other really good traders in here
have our own private ta channels this
morning I was looking after I gave my
general trading plan I was looking for
this potential scalp loan I had an idea
my idea was I see that we're forming a
bearish rising wedge pattern with the
target at one of those key areas of
Confluence I had marked on my chart
so that was my level that was my plan I
was interested in a scalp if we came
down to the level of around
24.5 ish 24 uh 520 to 24 550 right and
what did I want to see to get me into
that trade I wanted to see bullish
divergences on Market Cipher B this is
one of the best confluences you can have
to get into a trade is if you see
bullish divergences on Market Cipher B
so you can see actually for the trade
I'm currently in right now I did say
right before the trade happened that we
have this fresh daily level I will be
looking to long this daily if we get
bullish divergences on Market Cypher B
so what exactly is a bullish Divergence
we'll come over to our chart here a
bullish Divergence is basically when the
price is making a lower low but the
oscillator is making a higher low
something like this right here okay
price is making a lower low into a key
Zone the oscillator is making a higher
low resembling strangely enough a set of
uneven butt cheeks okay uneven butt
cheeks like this in fact if we take a
look at a picture we can see this is
what Marcus Cipher B should be looking
like when we come down to one of those
levels now the higher the time frame you
see this the juicier the potential trade
setup right if we're only seeing on the
one minute we can expect a nice scalp if
we're seeing it on the 12 minute the 24
minute the one hour the four hour we
could expect more of a swing-ish trade
right which is why you can see the short
trade that I am in right now
I'm treating this more like a swing
trade because we saw the bearish
divergences on the four hour time frame
and down potentially looking to hold
this down to lower targets so basically
we can enter trades as a scalp because
we're identifying those key levels in a
small sideways range but if we
understand the larger context of the
market we could just decide to hold it
for a little bit longer it will
determine where we're going to take
profits but we're going to get into that
in a second but this is what we should
be looking for but going back to the the
Discord Channel today we had a plan we
were looking for potentially coming down
after forming that Rising wedge that we
saw right over here let's take a look
yeah this was the General plan we knew
what confirmations we were looking for
and then of course when we came down to
their look we get the bounce exactly
from that zone and we did see bullish
divergences uh not necessarily on um
Market Cipher but we did see it on EXO
charts and by the way guys if you want
to take advantage of this volatility
scalping these markets with zero percent
limit fees on by bit you can click the
link in the description this will give
you zero percent limit fees also if you
deposit a hundred dollars you will get
one month free of the crypto Fusion
trading bot and uh by the way guys we
have 20 discount on both of our courses
at Jason Casper trading.com the basic
course will actually teach you how to do
this systematically and do it right with
complete swing trade day trade and scout
training tutorials going into much more
depth than I can possibly go in this
video also we have an advanced course
this will basically go over how to read
a chart like this in order flow chart
and stuff like that and if you click the
Jason Casper uh trading bot this will
give you more information about the
crypto Fusion trading bot 14 day free
trial for everybody who signs up one
month free trial if you deposit 100 on
buybid
so that is what that is the promotion
that we have going on right now so the
next thing we need to do after we have
our confirmations to get us into the
trade is we need to have a clearly
defined plan how are we going to get out
of the trade if things go wrong
something that is very very key when it
comes to scalp trading is that we are
risking very very little on the trade
but we're going to have the potential to
earn a lot of reward and the way we're
going to be doing this is with very very
clear entries and exits before we enter
the trade we have to have a clearly
defined stop loss and take profit and
what I like to do is always make sure
that there's more upward potential than
there is downward potential if you're
longing and there's more downward
potential than there is upward potential
if you are shorting now you can see
right here this was my trade setup it
was basically a three to one risk reward
ratio meaning there's three times more
potential reward than risk
and basically the the juicier you can
get your the juicier you can get your
entry the better it is for your trade
let me go into a little bit more detail
here and kind of explain what exactly I
mean by that when we are scalping the
thing that's so powerful about scalp
trays is that we can put a lot of money
on the trade while risking very little
for example I knew that I was longing a
very uh particular level here I knew I
was longing a very very particular level
down here meaning my trade idea would
have been wrong if price came down
0.05 percent lower than my entry right
what does this mean this means I could
put a lot of money on the trade I could
use very high leverage and I could still
be risking very very little in fact if
this trade had gotten stopped out I
would have risked less than a third of a
percent of my entire trading stack on
this scalp trade basically a no loss but
the potential here is so great because
compare to my stop loss my final Target
for the trade is way up here this is
basically giving me 19 times more
potential reward than risk and I've
already taken half the trade out hit a
nice take profit one very early move the
stop loss to the entry and that is
another thing that is very very
necessary
but especially when it comes to scalping
right scalping we need to be quick in
quick out and then if it runs we let it
run right quick in quick out if it runs
we let it run
but risk management is very key
basically what we need to make sure is
that for every trade we take regardless
of our entry that we're only risking the
same amount of our stack per trade for
me that's anywhere between a third to
three percent of my total stack okay so
if my stop loss for example has to be
down here for the Scout trade that means
I need to be putting a much smaller
position on the trade so that I can risk
one percent of my stack if the trade
goes against me but think of it this way
if I only need my stop loss to be right
here I could put much more on the trade
because if I get stopped out I'm losing
much less from that stop loss than I
would be from a stop loss much much
lower than that okay so this is very
important because if we don't have an
exit plan for these scalp trades what's
going to happen is we're going to start
taking very big losses and the key for
scalping is you have to make sure that
your wins are always going to outweigh
your losses which is why we look for
such precise levels on the chart it's
literally when we're scalping if we
don't get that immediate Bounce from the
level you basically need to get out of
the trade if we don't get that immediate
Bounce from a level you basically need
to get out of the trade so you're
looking for an immediate reaction from
the level
understanding that if you get stopped
out in this case it was a very very
small stop loss like a 0.0 0.1 percent
like a tenth percent
stop loss for the trade even less than
that right and so that is what we're
going to be doing understanding that
we're not going to be gambling here we
are basically putting the probabilities
in our favor saying I know what level is
likely to give me a reaction I know what
confirmations I'm looking for on my
oscillator or whatever else you're using
to get into the trade I know where my
stop loss should be I know where my take
profit should be now if you hit a few of
these a day you can rack up small wins
over the day and it can actually add up
pretty dang nicely in fact this is my
fifth trade of the day and on average
I'm making anywhere between 100 to 400
dollars per scalp trade right multiply
that by five and you've got you know
maybe like 700 total just by taking
these small scalp trades and of course
the amount of money you make is going to
vary for depending on your position size
and all that kind of how much Capital
you're trading with but the small gains
do add up over time something else
that's very key guys is moving your stop
loss to the entry after a take profit so
for me what I like to do is I like to
I like to basically take profit the
first place that really does make sense
right so for me the first place that
made sense after this bounce was as soon
as we took out the last High
that we had put in here before putting
that low that's where I'm going to lock
in profit you might say Jason that's
kind of dumb it's not dumb here's why
take a look even if we just take our
profit out at that level right
understanding that we need a very very
small stop loss here we're going to go
ahead and use our long position from our
entry
we know that our stop loss needs to go
under the wick we're bouncing from our
level exactly as a 0.04 stop loss
basically guys that means as soon as we
take out that old high this right here
is even still it's kind of hard to see
um but this is still
if we take a look at this trade setup a
seven to one risk reward just for a
little scalp trade like this that means
even if we're taking this trade even
with a take profit so early there's
still more gain potential here than
there is risk potential so these are
important things and if you want to
learn more about how to do this I do
recommend you check out the course at
Jason Casper trading.com we've got a 20
discount going on right now in the
course guys we do have the swing trading
tutorial The Scouting tutorial the day
trading tutorial this will give you that
system so that you can come to a chart a
blank chart make multiple plans for
multiple assets and then wait for those
setups to come to you so I just wanted
to make this video guys may God bless
everybody in the name of Jesus the
Messiah I know not everybody's religious
here and that's totally okay but I do
pray everybody is very very blessed and
I will see you all in the next video
peace