https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MB-a8xBtEQY
all right y'all
today i want to do more of an
educational video
and i want to show you guys how i trade
i want to show you how i trade
because it's more than just entering a
trade
it's more than just entering one trade
it's a whole system that i have of how
to trade and be consistently profitable
and i want to walk you through that
today
because during this past day
i have made a lot of trades first of all
this morning a lot of you know i entered
this long trade right here this was
something that i did post in my discord
that i was going to go long right here
when we got the bullish divergences
coming down to that 382 level
that trade and my second take profit was
up over 35 percent i'm still in that
long trade
and then as you know well you might not
know but i did take a short trade now
from up here as well
while we were um
while i was already in that long
position that trade right here i was
short
from you know that 46.6k region shout
out to one day closer who already took
that trade with me i know a bunch of
people took that with me
that trade was up uh you know i wanted
to take profit levels as well over 21
and then while i was in this short trade
i entered a long trade
and so i'm still in the short while i
was in the short i entered this long
this long is currently closed out
but you know this long basically i
longed the hidden divergence on the six
minute time frame
took profits out of that trade it was it
was not a bad move you know 18 profits
and then while i was also after that
long i did take another long
right here
and that trade got stopped out that
trade got stopped out and i did take a
loss right here
of two percent so these are the this is
the way i trade guys i'm going to show
you how i do these scalps
you know
it's actually very profitable if you
know how to do it correctly so i'm going
to walk you through that right now but
before i do
uh well yeah let's just walk through it
this is the
comprehensive
strategy
my trading strategy for making
consistent profits okay it
it involves multiple things you have to
have the indicator market cipher
you have to know some basic technical
analysis so
there are five steps to trading and
becoming consistently profitable
the first step is
when you enter a swing trade you need to
hold on to those swing trades
how are we going to find good swing
trades now in the background of all
these scalps that i just took i took
four scalp trays today okay three of
them are very good wins one of them was
a small loss because of good risk
management you guys know how it goes
but
in the background of these scalps
what was going on
i have these swing trades open i have a
swing trade on ethereum from 2586 this
is still currently open the stop loss is
in profit here well it's currently uh
at the entry i should say the stop
losses at the entry i've already taken
profit out it's a guaranteed win for me
i'm long on bitcoin from 34k okay again
this stop loss is in profit and i've
taken profit out of this trade already
i'm long on ethereum again from 28.72
this was an epic trade i remember a lot
of us took this in the discord again
i've taken profit out my stop loss is in
profit
and then i'm i'm along again on bitcoin
from uh
37.6 this stop-loss is also in profit
i've been taking profits out along the
way shout out to carl from the moon
in the background of these scalps i'm
already hedged very nicely in some nice
swing trades
it's very important if you want to be
profitable scalping and you don't want
to get wrecked that you have some good
positions already and you make sure to
hold those positions for a long time
how are you going to do this well
if you want to get into a swing trade
we need to go to a higher term time
frame we need to go to a higher term
time frame we need to find very
important levels of support or
resistance that we can use to enter a
longer term position so for example
okay a recent swing short that i had
was the swing short from let's see here
the swing short from right about here
okay at about 42.6 k
that means while i was scalping okay
this this was a nice short by the way
this short trade
was actually one of the short trades
that i posted in the discord here
under potential trade setups a while ago
let's see where was that one
um
right here okay it was this trade right
here
uh 42.6 short why did we find that short
because we were waiting for us to come
up to that level
with a bearish divergence
and um
[Music]
right here uh where was that
right here okay i was looking to come
into this fib level of resistance come
above these wicks and get a rejection
with the bearish divergence that's what
happened and once that happened then
what i do and what i can do is i can
take profit out of that trade early
right i can take profit out of the trade
early at 41 or even lower move the stop
loss to the entry and then what i have
is i have an open short which ended up
coming much higher than 40 percent but
while i'm scalping now in this area
right
while i'm scalping up and down in this
area
i have an open short trade
that is hedging me
against losses right because at any time
let's say now i'm i'm because i'm i'm
scalp i'm swing short from here
from the 382
you know and i've been in this trade the
whole time
if at any point i lose a scalp i'm
already hedged by unrealized profit in
this short
and there's no reason for me to close
the short
unless we come price comes back up above
you know that that last swing high and
then i'm like okay we're out of the
downward trend now we're moving up it's
time to close the short in profit it
gets stopped out in profit
and a lot of people i feel when they
enter swing trades they stay in them for
too short right you should at least the
way i trade guys
i will enter a position i will take
profit out of that position early i'll
move the stop loss at least to my entry
and then i will leave that position open
and continue to take profit out along
the way maybe 10 out here 10 out there
10 out here and what that does is it
allows me to constantly add realized
profit into my account so you know i
always have more money in my account
after the trade than before the trade
just by taking profit early and moving
the stop loss to the entry and then as
the trade continues i still have a
portion of that position open where i
still can take out
unrealized profit and make that realized
profit okay so having those swing trades
open
is very important
okay this whole time
while short here
right
think about it it's all about layering
your trades i was long from down here
and while i was still holding this
position
right i was still in the lung we come up
here
i enter short i'm still holding the long
it's still open with the portion of the
position open but i'm taking money out
of the short along the way down then we
come back up i've still got my long open
so now that long is accumulating more
and more unrealized profit that i can
take out along the way up
and then we came up to here
and i actually shorted this too
right i shorted this daily candle down
here from about um
right right around 45k that was a level
that that we had been waiting for for a
long time in the discord 45k
let's see where did i
take that trade from right here 45k we
were waiting for us to come up to that
weekly level get a rejection with the
bearish divergence which we absolutely
did
we hit our take profit one
right there
uh and right there we hit take profit
one take
a position 30 percent out of the trade
move that stop loss to the entry and now
you just let it ride then eventually we
come down we hit take profit two
etcetera etcetera
you guys understand you let these
positions ride okay you're still going
to be making money but what it does is
it hedges you because now if you want to
scalp and you want to get a little crazy
where you're taking these small moves
you have something hedging you in order
to prevent you even if you make a loss
to take any kind of loss okay it's
preventing you from taking any kind of
loss
so again the way you're going to find
these swing trades is you're going to
use large time frames like the daily the
four hour okay you're going to draw your
levels of support and resistance on
there and you're going to also use the
large time frames for confirmations
right so for example this short right
here
okay it was a really good short because
we had on the daily time frame right
that we had a fibonacci level from the
all-time high to the all-time low of the
dump a massive level and we had bearish
divergences on the four-hour time frame
with the money flow coming down these
are very clear confirmations on very
high time frames
these are going to be your swing trade
entries okay
so that's step number one to trading the
way i do step number two
is mark out local levels on your chart
okay once you're in your swing trades
and you want to start looking for
smaller trays little scallops here and
there
then you need to mark out local levels
on your chart so what i like to do
is this
let me come back to maybe a 12 minute
time frame here and zoom out
and i will mark local levels on my chart
okay i'll have local fibs
right
i will have local levels of support or
resistance like for example we can even
just see locally
that we have a level of resistance right
here right we can see that
we can see that just by coming back in
time here we had a level it was
respected it was respected again and it
was respected again right mark levels on
the chart pull fibs from different areas
like from this swing low
to the swing high right here
right
and what you're going to do now is on
the on the micro not looking on the
macro but in the most recent price
action if you hear somebody say our
local fib level or our local support
they're talking about on a smaller time
frame right this is technically an
uptrend on a very small time frame right
here this is an uptrend on a very small
time frame
and so we can subdivide this price
action and pull fibs from swingloads to
swing highs within this uptrend to find
good entries along the way to scalp okay
we're going to use fibs we can use
volume if you're going to turn on maybe
a fixed range and just analyze the
volume that we had along this local
uptrend
to see that we have a point of control
right here to see that we have a high
volume node here and a high volume node
right here that gives us confluence with
the 3a2 level you're you're trying to
find confluence on the local small time
frame within the local price action
okay
it's actually kind of a bummer
it's kind of a bummer in hindsight that
i did get stopped out of this last trade
here
because it was actually a pretty good
entry my stop-loss was tight i would
have actually
been in a win right now but that is okay
that is okay it's part of the game guys
losses are part of the game
so
once we mark the local levels on the
chart using fibonacci support and
resistance volume trend lines right
trend lines like this channel here that
i noticed we've been respecting
then what we're going to do
is we are going to
look for divergences and confirmations
on market cipher as we come to these
important levels
so if you're looking at a chart on let's
say the three minute time frame right
and by the way guys if you don't know
this if you don't know how to get these
levels how to use fibonacci and all this
stuff check out
jasoncaspertrading.com because this
course will equip you with the knowledge
and the skills you need to become a
confident profitable trader
you can check out the testimonials here
basically the goal of this course is
assuming you've never even looked at a
chart before
you know basically i'm walking you
through the way i trade walking you
through step by step the way that i
trade
and the way that i use risk management
the way that i have a strategy the way
that i use market cipher showing you how
to do technical analysis
everything you need to know in extreme
detail
risk management very important so you
can lose trades and still be profitable
over time show you strategies that i
already use right out of the box check
it out there's an eighty 80 discount in
the description also guys if you do want
to get into the discord where i post
daily technical analysis updates
important levels of support and
resistance trade setups trade ideas and
even in the chats
will um
post a lot of times in these in these
areas my exact entries not all the time
but a lot of times i do
you can go to patreon.com forward slash
jason casper we have a great trading
community in here i i recommend if
you're interested in being a part of the
group
check it out um it's not a replacement
for taking a course guys it's meant to
supplement your own technical analysis
and to bounce ideas off and stuff
okay so we have our local levels marked
now what we are going to do is we are
going to use market cipher with our
levels to find the good entries
if you don't have a marked chart and
you're just trying to scalp
with market cipher only on these high ti
on these low time frames during such
volatile times guys look if we zoom out
on a higher time frame here
right look at this we've basically been
trading sideways for the past two days
right it will be very difficult for you
to tr to scalp this if you don't have
some kind of frame of reference that's
why it's so important to mark levels on
your chart okay
and so
once you have the levels marked on your
chart now what we're going to do is
we're going to look at market cipher
when we get to one of those levels
so let's take a look at one of the longs
the first long trade that i entered
today
is still in the trade by the way my take
profit 2
was 35
right this is a leveraged trade if
you're wondering how the percentage is
so high
this morning i was doing my ta and i
noticed as i pulled a fib that we were
getting bullish divergences as we're
coming down to a fib level the 382
okay so the first long trade i took
today
let me zoom out now to the 12 minute
and come let's
see here
here we go
this is the first long trade that i took
today
from right here okay why did i enter
this trade well if we come down to a
lower time frame let's say the three
minute
right what was happening
as we were printing lower lows right
here market cipher b was giving us
higher lows actually this was even lower
on the one minute time frame
check it out guys
price is coming down like this we can
see
right here
price is coming down
and momentum is coming up
right
now i missed the initial first pump here
what i did was i caught that second wave
the way you can do that is if marcus
cipher b is printing a bottom and then
it prints another big bottom like that
and it's still diverging in this way
where even still we can connect
this point to this point and it's giving
us a bullish divergence like that that
is where i entered the trade right there
so what did i do i waited for price to
come to a level and when price did come
to the level that's where
i entered the position okay based on
market cipher diverging i'm going to get
into divergences a little bit more in
this video
but that's that's honestly the best way
you're gonna find these scalp trades
okay
now let's take a look at the second
trade that i entered today the short
trade okay the short from up here
okay how did i enter this short trade
well
again we came up to a fib level this is
a 786 fib level right
and what happened as we got to this fib
level let's take a look at a little bit
of a higher time frame here but we were
printing
very
bearish divergences we could see price
coming up making a higher high into the
fib resistance
we could see momentum coming lower as
we're coming into the resistance we
could also see the money flow coming
lower on market cipher b that's very
important
and again this is a trade that you know
i a lot of us took this in the discord
took a short off here
you know we're scalping guys so it's not
like we're betting the farm on these
trades i'm not betting the farm in these
trades but they can still be profitable
and my second take profit that i hit on
here i'm still in the short was up over
21 so it's still a nice move right there
why because i marked out my local levels
first and then when i saw we were
getting a divergence that's where i
entered the trade okay let's take a look
at the third trade that i entered
which was this one right here
this long trade was pretty nice right
this long trade did happen to get us
the wrong chart
this trade happened to get me a pretty
nice move it was a point seven five
percent move uh but with leverage i was
able to
after i longed that hidden bullish
divergence
i was able to get an 18 profit on that
move okay i'm gonna get into how we're
gonna enter the trades limiting in is
very important limiting out okay we're
gonna talk about how to take the profit
and stuff like that it's very important
that you guys know
but uh this is the the general way that
i'm doing it
okay so
now how did i enter this trade for this
trade we had a hidden bullish divergence
where we can see
as we were coming
in making a
higher
um
actually i'm i'm sorry i think i might
have entered the trade right here and
held i'm not really sure i think yes i
entered the trade here and i had my stop
loss below the last swing low
but we can see the hidden bullish
divergence where as we were coming in
here
price was making a higher high
while momentum was making lower highs
okay so we this whole entire time we see
the hidden bullish diversions forming
here
i entered the trade because we came down
to a daily level of
support
as well as a fibonacci 236 level so we
come to the levels
we get our bullish divergence we entered
the trade and again that was a nice move
and i know a bunch of people well a few
people took this with me
it started out kind of bad right it
started out we're in a little draw down
it ended up pretty good wicking all the
way up here
okay now i know a lot of you might be
thinking when do you take profit how do
you know where to take profit we're
going to get into that guys we're going
to get into that but first let's talk
about the last trade i made which was a
loss okay let's talk about the loss not
just going to talk about our wins
going to talk about our losses as well
um
right here boom
now
this trade actually would have been in
profit right now right as we can see but
here's the problem the problem is i got
wicked out down here
right just by a little bit
why did i enter this trade well once
again we came to the daily level
down here we came to
um
hang on guys
hang on
here we go yeah once again
just like that first scalp along i took
we came down to
that same daily level that same
fibonacci level and we were also
printing on the lower time frames on the
three minute right here we as we came to
that level we're printing a bullish
diversion support price is making a
lower low momentum was making a higher
low
again guys
you know i this this trade could have
not been lost for me i could have gotten
out at least at a break even
but that's what happens right you're not
going to win every trade you're not
going to win every trade you're going to
take a loss so this trade was a loss
because it wicks me out right down here
just missed staying in this trade kind
of a bummer guys but it's okay why is it
okay because i'm hedged in my lungs not
only am i hedged in these massive swing
trades that i have open for bitcoin that
are like 500 400 500 in profit
okay
not only am i hedged in those trades
guys but
i am also
hedged in that initial
long that i took this morning right so
the first long i took this morning
from way down here i'm still in so while
i'm taking these other smaller longs i'm
still in this bigger long and while i'm
still in this bigger long i'm still long
from
all
oh
okay
wow i'm still alive from all the way
down
here okay i'm still long from all the
way down here
and at any time if i take a loss i just
come to this trade and it's a very small
loss it's still 25x leverage i'm using
for this here
it's a small loss guys and i can just
take a little profit and realize out of
my current logs and refund that loss
very easily and most of the time it's
not going to be lost because i have a
very good strategy
and
you can even see just based on you know
what i've been showing you here that
even that trade that was lost for me
i still had the right idea
i still the right idea because if this
was 25 x um long right now i could have
had the opportunity to make quite a bit
of profit right here right like 12
10 profit from this uh from this move
right here so i had the right idea i was
just
not it did not enter at the correct time
and then that's something that you are
going to have to
deal with y'all okay so let's get into a
little bit more detail here about how
we're actually going to manage this
okay
lock in profits early this is very
important
your greed guys will make you lose money
you need to be satisfied with making
smaller gains okay smaller gains
because what that will do is it will
allow you to consistently grow your
account and not take big losses here's
what i mean by locking in your profits
for your swings and your scalps okay
let's say that we're long from right
here
and our final take profit is up here
what you need to do
is when price gets to a local area of
support or resistance let's say the way
i do this is i simply just go to the
left on the chart and say where did
price find a sticking point we could say
price did find a sticking point right
here
right
why because we have resistance
resistance support support resistance
and then support and then resistance and
so when i am shooting for my first take
profit i will take profit out at that
first area where i think price is going
to find a sticking point which is 0.35
once i take maybe 30 depending on how
i'm feeling about the scalp 50 out of
the trade right here
then what we do is we move the stop loss
to the entry what this does is if you
get stopped out now you're still going
to be in a small
win
you're still going to be having more
money in your account than when you
started
okay
because you took 30 percent of the
contracts out of the trade here and now
you get stopped out and the only thing
is you have to pay the market fee you
have to pay the market fee for the
remaining contracts that 30 you took out
of your trade will cover the market fee
and leave you with some money in your
account if you don't do this
and you don't take the profit and you
get stopped out
even if you've moved your
stop-loss to the entrance you're still
gonna have to pay that market fee which
means you're going to exit the trade
with less money than when you started
it's all about preservation of capital
guys number one rule to not
number one rule to make money
is to not lose money who said that
pretty sure it was
what's the guy's name
uh what was his name um wonton buffet i
think his name is wonton buffet all
right and guys just a disclaimer here
this is not financial advice i'm not a
financial advisor okay and i want you to
remember if unless
you are tempted within your vain
imagination to think that i am giving
financial advice remember this face
right let it get burned into your mind
guys
if you take this as financial advice
this face will come back to haunt you
because why would you take financial
advice from a guy with a pikachu hat on
top of an other hat with upside down
glasses who lives in his basement gym
right why would you do that you wouldn't
do that because this is not financial
advice this entertainment purpose is
only don't trust a guy
with teeth like this guys
don't do it
not financial advice entertainment
purposes only okay
entertainment purposes only um i'm not a
financial advisor all right if i was a
trader and right now of course this is
all paper trading guys paper
this is how i would do it if i was a
paper trader
it's very important that you limit out
okay limit out meaning as soon as you
open that position hopefully you get a
chance to limit in to your position
right
a lot of times you might not be able to
but always try to limit in and if you
cannot
have a limit order already set there if
you see prices coming down and you see
we're printing a divergence you can get
a chance to limit in
if you cannot limit in and you have to
market in
make sure you immediately set your limit
take profit order up here so that now
you are guaranteed
to have more money in your account than
when you started okay
now
you have to limit orders this will make
or break you guys if you're marketing
out you're going to lose if you're
scalping if you're marketing out you're
gonna lose try to look into the future
if you see a divergence is printing
as we're coming down to a level right
for example we can see right here as we
were coming down
we could see that as price was dropping
as price was dropping we can see the
momentum getting higher it's not
confirmed yet but we can see the
momentum getting higher so you might
want to before it even confirms have a
limit order set at that area of support
where you know it's going to be you can
set the limit order with a stop loss
that fits with your risk management
if you cannot limit in and you have to
market in make sure to limit out all
your take profits is right take profits
is
what a bummer actually guys that this
long got stopped out
but it's part of the game
okay
again let your trades ride and take
profits out right i'm still in a long
and short right now i'm still from just
today from today only i'm in many longs
but from this morning
okay i was in
let me close this stuff out
from this morning i am still in this
long right now so even though i've
stopped out of my long just now and i'm
bummed about it i'm still long
and even though i've taken profit out
when we got to here and i've taken
profit out when we got to up here
i'm still in the trade with a portion of
the position open which means if we keep
pumping i can still take profits out of
this trade and put that into my account
and grow my account
really the way i'm trading guys is like
this you know like
you know those things you go to the
boardwalk i don't know i'm from new
jersey so the jersey shore and all that
right you go to the boardwalk and
there's this this game you play where
they put you in like a room a tiny
little shower stall and they just start
blowing dollar bills around and you
can't get them all you can't get all the
dollar bills but you can get a lot you
take them you stuff them in your pants
right
stuff them in your pockets as many as
you can walk out of there with they will
let you keep okay i'm just trying to put
myself into one of those shower stalls
with dollar bills flowing around and i
can just grab them i'm not going to get
them all i'm not going to make you know
in order to squeeze out as much profit
as possible from this long i would have
to enter right here
not take any profit out along the way i
would have either had to have closed
right here
or i would have to just wait and hope
that we eventually come all the way up
to a higher take profit which honestly
47k is one of my targets
right and that there's a lot of risk
involved with that everything has to go
right for that trade to benefit me
instead of banking on everything going
right why not bank on everything going
wrong and as soon as you're in an
advantageous situation
then you take advantage of that by
taking profits out moving your stop loss
limiting right limited okay
have multiple accounts and keep trades
open right take profits along the way
head yourself in it's very important you
have multiple accounts
okay
personally i have multiple accounts i
just started trading on femex right in
fact my first real trade that i ever
took on femex was that scalp from this
morning right here
by bit guys the regulations are coming
in with buy bet it makes me nervous
so i'm starting to trade on another
account i'm starting to move my funds
over to femax now and i'm going to start
opening multiple accounts and sub
accounts on here as well as i'm still
using vivid for now but if you want to
get on phoenix especially if you're in
the usa that i don't think they require
a vpn they do not from the cell phone
require a vpn
it's the next best thing there is to buy
bit if you're interested and you want to
use my affiliate link you can it would
help me out link is in the description
also pin it in the comment
also guys um
jasoncaspertraining.com if you want to
get the trading course this
comprehensive course if you're new if
you're struggling this will walk you
through if this video was over your head
this will walk you through
everything you need to know to
understand what i'm talking about in
this video
and help you to become confident and
profitable also guys if you want to get
into the discord where i do post daily
technical analysis updates levels
important things trade setups a lot of
those trade setups actually do work and
they're actually quite profitable um you
know for example the one that we took a
few days ago
from the 786 fib level right here
you know i wanted to see us come uh up
to the 46.6 to 47k level with the
bearish divergences that's exactly what
happened
this is my original drawing
this is what happened
my original drawing was pretty close
guys pretty close we we came up not
quite as high as my original drawing but
we did lose that 76 we entered the trade
it was a very profitable trade
if you want to get access to the discord
where we have a good trading community
and hear people posting ta
um it's actually it's actually a really
good discord it's a really good vibes in
here guys we keep it positive we keep it
positive um
it's not a toxic place you can go to
patreon.comcasper all right guys
that's basically it make sure to like
the video make sure to subscribe to the
channel
and um
make sure to share this video guys
because i feel like i'm dropping some
important info in here for people who
might be flopping and groping all right
peace