https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J8lXmBQEvxw
this trading strategy is an absolute
GameChanger I want to share with you the
scalping strategy that I have used to
make about
$225,000 over the course of the past 30
days and I don't even trade every single
day now the reason why I'm sharing my
p&l with you which I usually never do is
because I want you guys to know that
this is a legitimate trading strategy
that I am actually using to make money
over time I'm not just trying to blow
some BS up your patootie if you know
what I'm saying secondly I want to be up
front and say the percentages if I were
just to show you the percentages they
would be skewed because it says I made
32% on my account over the past 30 days
well that's not true because I don't
keep all my actual capital on the
exchange right I keep most of my capital
in cold storage now and so really I've
made about 12% on my total account
during the past 30 days probably trading
between 3 to five days a week and I want
to walk you through exactly how I'm
doing this the strategy that I'm using
very in-depth tutorial so this mini
course is going to be going over step
by- step how I look for these trades how
I am taking profits how I am locking in
these profits over time I really hope
you enjoy this mini course on scalping
primarily the 5c time frame this
strategy really does have a very high
win rate I mean look at the trades I've
taken over the past few days using the
strategy most of them are wins I've only
got three losses here going back now the
past four days this is pretty much the
entire week of trading these all the
trades I've taken on this account I've
only lost three this is another account
that I have been using to trade the
strategy and again the reason I'm
showing you the actual proof right now
is because when I talk about scalping
the 5-second time frame people get
absolutely furious with me and they say
Jason there's no way you can be
profitable doing this there's no way a
strategy like that could work stop
Shilling people stop scamming people
well I'm here to show you the proof guys
I'm here to show you the receipts before
we proceed with this uh strategy here
because really for me this is has been
an absolute Game Changer because for
most of my trading career I have been a
swing Trader and then I transitioned
into more of a day trader where I was
taking maybe one two on a really crazy
day maybe three or four trades per day
right well now this is a game changer I
can come to the charts for maybe two or
three hours it's currently 10:00 in the
morning right now I've been trading
since 7 in the morning that's 3 hours
I've already booked over 2K in profits
taking probably about six or seven
trades today and I could be now done for
the day I could just relax I don't have
to worry about waiting for my levels or
staying at the computer all day or
constantly thinking in my mind oh no am
I going to miss the big trade for the
day because well I've already I've
already made my money for the day I
could already call a day if I want to
and if I don't want to well I could stay
there on the charts for the rest of the
day and look for those swing trades and
look for those day trades so this is
perfect for somebody who has a busy life
and typically they say you know if you
have a busy life well you should be a
swing Trader because then you don't have
to be at the charts 24/7 right well on
the other side of that coin if you're
scalping very low time frames and you
can take two three trades in a 2hour
period then also you don't have to be at
the charge 247 you could be there two
hours a day you could call it a
part-time job you go in you take your
trades you get out on with your life now
this is going to be an introduction to a
mini course and I'm just going to give
you the strategy right now for free
right off the bat basically it's this if
the price is coming to a key level that
you have identified on your chart what
you want to see on Market Cipher B which
is indicator I use for this strategy is
bullish divergences with the momentum
waves getting higher over time for a
long trade and also a bullish Divergence
with the money flow getting higher over
time also for a long trade and you can
see right here this made for a very very
nice move to the upside really that was
the biggest move of the day so far but
really I spent spent the entire morning
scalping this little range right here
simply by looking for trades just like
the one I showed you so again I actually
did take a few trades here let's take a
look at one of them that I took right
over here as well guys right price came
down to a key level of support and when
we take a look at the momentum waves
over time they are absolutely getting
higher giving us the bullish Divergence
the money flow also getting higher
giving us that bullish Divergence here
at Key support and once again look at
this move bam about a
0.2% move now the opposite is true for
short trades all right we can see right
here price came up to what at the time
was a Fibonacci golden pocket retest we
look at our good friend Market ever be
bam a bearish Divergence with the
momentum waves a bearish Divergence with
the money flow and if anybody doesn't
know what a Divergence is it simply just
means the oscillator is doing the
opposite of what the price is doing so
price is making a higher high into a key
level level momentum is making a lower
high into that key level money flow is
making a lower high into a key level
right the oscillator doing the opposite
of what the price is doing so that is
the strategy in a nutshell guys and so
for the rest of this mini course I'm
actually going to be unpacking how to
actually execute this because it's a
little bit more involved than just
taking a trade when you see a Divergence
because you have to think of things such
as risk management such as how much are
you going to put on the trade where is
your stop loss going to go where is your
takeprofit going to go how are you going
to manage these trades that are
happening so quickly on these very low
time frames what other charts are you
going to be using we're going to be
going over that in this mini course and
so guys for the rest of the course check
out Jason Casper trading.com go ahead
and click the courses link right here
you can either sign up for the Scout
trading mini course it's only
$75 or if you sign up for the intro to
trading crypto program there's a 25%
discount on this comprehensive trading
course that goes over everything you
need to know to be profitable over time
plus it also includes the scalp mini
trading series there's a link in the
description and the pin comment if you
are interested now I do not care whether
or not you buy the course I basically
gave you the strategy for free in this
video so whether you want an in-depth
tutorial of me explaining exactly how
I'm doing this or you want to test it
for yourself the one thing I ask guys
leave some comments down below let me
know have you had success scalping on
the very very low time frames do you
have something to add to the strategy
that I am presenting here all right guys
that is it for today's video may God
bless you all in the name of Jesus
Yeshua the Messiah even if you are not
religious I still pray you and your
family are super blessed and I will see
everybody in the next video peace