https://youtu.be/euycMDyPo30?si=jdRTES2yq-QSVNN9&t=613
all right y'all so in today's video i
want to go over
uh this scalp trade that i just took
here it's a little short scalp that i
took about an hour before new york
opened
and the reason why i want to go over
this is because it pretty much had the
perfect confirmations
for a quick scalp
and so
i figured this could help a lot of
people because a lot of times people are
asking me jason like you know
when we have a level or potential scalp
trait how do i know if the confirmations
are there or not to take the trade
okay so let's come over to our um our
chart here
um and basically as you can see it was a
chicken's drinking water trade setup
okay what that means is that we had a
high that we put in right here and then
we simply took out that high
with bearish divergences on market
cipher b so pretty much guys um i'm
going to go ahead and just make a
notepad but if we're looking to scalp
especially if we're looking to um
do a chickens drinking water type trade
the things that we want to look for for
a perfect trade setup would be number
one bearish
divs
right
number two money flow
number three
would be open interest
and i think if we have all three of
these things it can make for pretty much
a
a very good uh trade setup here
and so
i just kind of want to go over this
uh in real time right because it made
for a nice quick little scalp right here
and i am curious now to see you know
what's going to happen
as we come up for our retest
so
um essentially you know this is
something that um happens all the time
right we have a high that we put in or a
low that we put in
and um
you know we take out that higher low and
then get a fake out to the downside okay
a great example of this
is yesterday
right yesterday
we had a level down here
that was a cdwa chickens drink water
this was the exact low
of the move yesterday on yesterday's
dump okay we'll actually go over both of
these you can see that over here on the
28th of august we put in this first low
and then yesterday which was the 30th of
august a few days later we came and we
simply took out that low right and we
did so with
as you could see here
bullish divergences okay now what is a
bullish divergence a bullish divergence
is when you have
the momentum waves
getting higher as the price
is getting lower now these can be
locally or more regionally i want to
point out the fact that we have a
bullish divergence right here locally
but we also have a bullish divergence
right here
over the course of the entire move right
pretty much over the course of the
entire move
from that first low that we put in
to this low right here on august 30th we
have a bullish divergence across the
entire board here and then locally we
even have a bullish divergence right
here okay this is kind of what we want
to look for
if we are looking for a chicken drinking
water trade setup and you can see that
we had the level marked out in advance
because we knew it was an important
level uh to be looking for a potential
bounce from okay and same with this
today now these can be locally these can
be more uh regionally yesterday morning
the high of before we dumped was also a
chicken's drinking water type trade
setup we put in the initial high we put
in a higher high right here with the
momentum waves getting lower
right this is a
bearish divergence okay we want to look
for the momentum waves and the price
doing the opposite thing
again
earlier today but you know before the
trade that i'm currently and while i was
sleeping look at what we had here we had
a high put in we had a higher high
and what did we have on market cipher b
we had a very bearish divergence right
here okay a very very bearish divergence
the momentum waves were getting lower
so when we are looking for a trade setup
a scalp like this okay because a lot of
times what will happen is people will
will you know they'll put in a trade
uh just because we're like breaking out
of resistance still short which is
honestly a horrible idea unless you have
your confirmation the only way we can
know this is a fake out
right is if we actually have
confirmation that this move is
unsustainable right that this move is
unsustainable that this move is
unsustainable we need confirmation of
that because if it is unsustainable
there's a very high chance we're going
to have a a sharp pullback like we're
getting right now and as you can see we
are finding support at this uh little
area of high volume
which is why we have taken profit one on
the trade as you can see here we've
taken profit one on the trade
and um
you know i have my other take profit set
now at the low of this local little
range here and then again at this low
but that's neither here nor there i want
to talk about how we can get into trades
like this
okay so the first thing we're going to
do is we're going to mark out that key
level this high here okay now it helps
if we also know how to mark other key
levels on a chart like these green boxes
that i have on my chart
you can see these are the boxes that i
had on my chart from yesterday
they are very much so
respected right look at this we come
down
uh we didn't find support on this box
but we retest find resistance on this
box we come down bounce perfectly off
this lower box we come up find
resistance on this box come bounce from
this box and now we're back up at the
high of the range now if you want to
learn how to mark levels like this and
do some good technical analysis you can
go to jasongaspertrading.com
this course will give you the knowledge
and the skills you need to become a
confident profitable trader because it
gives you the blueprint to stop chasing
price
and start actually having a plan in
advance which is very very important to
always have a plan
in advance in fact um
you know in the vip discord this is what
we do we we give trade setups in advance
what we're looking for you know for
example yesterday the high of the move
that we put in yesterday boyan who's a
traitor in the discord
he gave the setup in advance and it
played out perfectly according to his
plan right because he was planning
to take out the double top
fill the single prints and basically
take a short from that exact area this
is the setup given in advance
and then you know it happened pretty
much exactly as he was planning for
right and if you do want to join the vip
discord where we have a team of traders
giving levels giving trade setups doing
live streams myself every single day i
upload the important levels you can go
to patreon.com forward slash
jason casper
and back to the bitcoin price action so
the first thing that we want to look for
again is a high that we have this is
great for scalping okay especially when
there's a lot of volume injecting to the
market
now the second thing that we want to
look for
uh so you know we're taking for granted
here
and zero is uh key level right
key level let's make this a little
bigger
actually so that we can see here and um
also let me
push this back on okay so key level
right then we want to look for bearish
diversity we just went over what a
bearish divergence is then we want to
look at money flow money flow is also
key so if we take a look at what was
happening up here okay yesterday
and we go down to these lower time
frames whoops i guess now i have to come
back okay look at what was happening on
these lower time frames guys market
cipher b right does not lie the money
flow does not lie look at what is
happening to the money flow on these
lower time frames
as the price is getting higher we can
see money coming out of the asset right
money is coming out of the asset
this is
a very strong indicator if it's
happening along with
bullet a bit or bullish or bearish
divergence it's a very strong indicator
that the move is unsustainable okay i'm
gonna go ahead
and just show you guys i'm gonna turn
off the everything else here on market
saver so we can just take a look
at these waves here right look at the
waves getting lower this is showing us
money leaving the market now even when
we came back up for another um
another
uh retest this is actually the beginning
of the huge move down when new york
opened right here right
we can see that money flow is still
getting lower
from the initial point that we put in
right over time
and you know i want to show you
something also the the start of the move
to the downside yesterday
was actually another very local chickens
drinking water which did in fact happen
if we put back on our momentum waves
right here boop
right
um
it did also happen with bearish
divergences right this is the one minute
time frame we can see if we take a trend
line from here to here
that this wave to this wave is a bearish
divergence
uh from that high to this high right we
could see the direction coming down as
the price is getting higher right
so we want to look for that money flow
we want to look for those divergences
and then honestly guys a kicker
can also be
looking at open interest now what is
open interest if we go to a website
called coinalize.net
okay this is a free tool that we could
use here we can
look at this thing here called open
interest
okay open interest this is showing us
okay right down here these purple and
blue candles when the candles are
turning blue and getting higher this is
showing us that traders are actively
opening up positions and entering into
the market putting their money at risk
okay it doesn't tell us if they're long
or shorting it just tells us people are
entering into trades when the candles
are turning purple and open interest
coming down and showing us people are
exiting trades this is how we can
identify something like a short squeeze
if people are exiting trades yet the
price is going up this is telling us
this move to the upside is not being
caused
by people longing the market okay the
move to the upside is considered weak if
it's just shorts getting wrecked there's
no new money stepping in to push the
price up in other words right but if
open interest is getting higher this is
telling us that the move is very strong
and it's it can be sustained right
uh let's see if i can find an example of
that so the the shorts from yesterday
when we were coming down yesterday a
very very strong downtrend because open
interest was increasing we saw lots of
new shorts opening up long's being
absorbed it was very very bearish
looking right
now if we put in a high okay and then we
put in a
higher high we want to be taking a look
at the open interest because if the open
interest is coming down
as the price is getting higher
this is telling us that this move is
really not sustainable especially if
it's combined with divergences so up
here look at this when we put in the
high on this five minute candle look at
the open interest massive massive
decrease
in open interest right here is telling
us that there is money leaving the
market there are bearish divergences and
there's no new longs at all coming in
that are going to push this price up
higher this is unsustainable we are
going to get a rejection here right and
these are things that we can look for to
get into high probability trade setups
and the reason why it's a high
probability trade setup
again is because
of the fact that and now we actually
have some bullish divergences down here
if you notice this right and we're
getting a little move to the upside
you know it's it's it's very interesting
to be watching these things at all times
guys we see bullish divergence we see
money flow also starting to get thicker
very locally
but it's a good trade setup because we
know right that as soon as we put in
this high wick right here
that our trade
we enter right here our stop loss goes
above the wick very small risk a point
zero eight percent stop loss okay even
if we take a loss here it's a very very
small loss
our first take profit should be the
first area of support
right so right off the bat if we close
the entire trade this is an eight to one
risk to reward ratio and if we're going
to hold it for longer and take partial
profits right which my next take profits
down here this is a 17 to one risk to
reward trade setup right here okay
very very good setup very very simple
confirmations to get into again we have
our key level we have our bearish divs
or bullish if we're long money flow and
open interest so i just wanted to come
in make this video for you guys and um
you know i do have a um
i have some take profits lower but if we
start to change market structure here
i'll probably close out the entire
position and then
i will look for another entry that's it
for today's video guys god bless
everybody in the name of jesus the
messiah i do hope that you found this
video helpful if you did guys make sure
to like the video make sure to subscribe
to the channel
peace