https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bMJI2v2PnhY
this trading strategy is super easy and
it's the one I use to take the short
trade that you see right here as you can
see I'm about to get stopped out at my
entry after hitting a very juicy
takeprofit one but this is the kind of
trade setup you can look for multiple
times a day it's called a chicken's
drinking water trade setup and there's a
few different ways to trade this we're
going to talk about the way I like to
trade this so what is a chicken's
drinking water a chicken's drinking
water also known as a swing failure
pattern is when the price makes a high
or a low but in this case it's a hide
let's go ahead and turn off our
positions here so we can see the chart
more
clearly price makes a high right
typically when we're trading some kind
of a sideways range and then price goes
for a stop hunt right it basically stops
out everybody who shorted early just to
then reverse the price you're basically
looking to trade a stop hunt and the
reason why it's called a chicken's
drinking water is because if you've ever
seen a chicken drink water which I see
every day because I'm a homestead I grow
my own food I raise my own animals I
love watching chickens drink water they
will take their beak they will stick it
into the water and then real quick they
rip their beak out and they go and they
lap it up in fact one of my favorite
things to do is actually watch chickens
drink water on YouTube so I can go to
chickens drinking
water and I watch this video multiple
multiple times a day all right check out
how the chicken actually drinks water
all right she takes her beak she shoves
it into the water boom right then she
pulls it
out right basically what we're looking
for here is this first high is the water
the priz candles are the chicken's beak
and when we see the chicken stick her
beak in the water and then pull it out
that is when we enter into that position
now we only do this if there are certain
confirmations on the chart that tell us
to get into that trade so what are some
of these confirmations well let's take a
look at the chart and let's take a look
at what happened as we got this chickens
drinking water all right all right so
first of all we need to establish key
areas of support and resistance on the
chart right we don't want to look for
chickens drinking water just anywhere it
helps if we have a key area of support
and resistance and it just so happens
that if we take our Fib from the high to
the low you can see that price came to
the Fibonacci 786 level right here and
we got a rejection from the 786 so a lot
of people shorted that and rightfully so
in fact I also shorted that hit a tp1
and then got stopped out of my entry but
then what happened we got a stop hunt
Okay we came back up above now when you
establish a high or a low right what you
want to do is Mark that level whenever
price makes a new high or a new low you
want to mark that out and tell yourself
this could get stop hunted and then what
you want to do is you want to look at
two indicators as the price comes back
to take that high I like to use Market
Cipher B and what I like to look for is
I like to see the momentum waves and the
money flow getting lower as the price
actually takes that high all right now
if you don't use Market cyer because it
is a premium indicator you can use
something called the awesome oscillator
all right and basically with the awesome
oscillator you want to see a bearish
Divergence what's a bearish Divergence
it's where the oscillator is making a
lower high as the price is making a
higher high now that is what you want to
look for you want to see that it depends
on what time frame you're trading if
you're using a bigger time frame to to
put in this high like let's say this is
a high that is made on a daily candle
you would want to see this on the daily
chart right if the high is made on a
lower time frame candle you use lower
time frames what you want to do is you
want to make sure that you're seeing
this across multiple time frames the 6
Minute money flow momentum getting lower
the three minute what do we see as we
make that high money flow and momentum
getting lower the one minute what do we
see as we make that high the momentum
waves and the money flow getting lower
as we make that high if you see this at
a key level this is a valid chickens
drinking water trade setup you are going
to enter the trade once you see a candle
close below that previous High okay so
basically what we have here is a soon as
we close a one minute candle below that
green line This is Where I would enter
the trade and what you do is you put
your stop loss above that Wick this is
your stop- loss very lowrisk trade right
and then your first takeprofit is going
to be the low the first low that price
made before it made that higher high all
right that would be a tp1 to lock in the
trade and then move the stop loss to
your entry all right once you I I
usually take out half the trade all
right once you move the stop loss to
your entry you can either close the
whole trade whenever you want or you can
let it ride to see what happens because
technically we could come down a bit
lower that's why I've actually kept this
trade open here as you can see and we
are dumping right now and the reason why
is because we came up to once again the
Fibonacci golden pocket right so I like
to keep a portion of the trade open but
this is how you're going to do it now
the other indicator that I use is called
open interest all right open interest is
basically showing our new trades opening
or our trades closing out right
sometimes price is moved by new Traders
actually opening up new positions and
sometimes price is moved by a short
squeeze okay there's a free tool out
there called coinalyze doet coinalyze
Donnet a totally free tool you could
check it
out and what you're going to do is put
on an indicator called open interest all
right open interest this is not trading
view this is coinalyze
doet all right a website and as you are
taking out the high right let's zoom in
on our five minute time frame this was
the high right here okay as you're
taking it out what you also want to see
along with the divergences is you want
to see the open interest getting a
drastic decrease see these purple
candles this is the open interest
getting a big decrease why do we want to
see that well we need to ask ourselves a
question when we're seeing price pumping
like crazy and people getting very
bullish the only way this move can
sustain itself is if there's actually
money coming into the market if there's
actually people willing to buy Bitcoin
at these high prices if you see massive
amounts of Trades closing out here that
means shorts are getting wrecked and
Longs are taking profit and there's no
new money to C continue that move to the
upside and so if you see a big decrease
of open interest as you're also seeing
Market Cipher B Printing lower momentum
and money flow that is a very high
probability that the trade will go in
your favor and as you can see the trade
did go in our favor now what's very
important about this trading strategy
especially if you're using this to scalp
is that you take profits and move your
stop loss to the entry okay I posted
this and we were looking at this for CDW
this morning CDW stands for drinking
drinking water in the Casper crew VIP
Discord New York open live stream where
we give the juicy trade setups like the
long that we gave literally from the
exact bottom we were looking at the CDW
happening and we have to take profit
when price comes down to that first low
all right we made a low right here so we
have to say when price comes down here
we take profit right we made a low right
here so we have to say if price comes
down here we take profit I took four
short trades today
two of them the first two were wins the
second one was a loss because we never
came down to the low obviously the third
one is a win if you don't take profits
and move your stop loss to the entry you
will get wck if you take profit stop
loss to entry even though I took a loss
and even though these are small moves
I'm still up on my whole account 4% on
the day why because you have to stick to
your dang rules of first of all using
the right position size using good risk
management all right that goes beyond
the scope of this video but secondly
stay true to taking profit when you're
in profit moving your stop loss to the
entry understanding that either you're
going to get stopped out making a small
profit or the trade is going to keep
running like the one I'm in right now
and you lock in a profit and then worst
case scenario you make a profit best
case scenario it keeps running with a
smaller position open right you must do
this by the way if you want to join the
Casper cre VIP Discord you go to jasonc
Casper trading.com click the link to
join the Discord guys we have multiple
instructors in here giving their trade
setups giving their levels telling you
their thought process on stocks Forex
crypto a great educational Community if
you want to get educated check out the
courses here white Phoenix one of our
instructors just released literally the
most comprehensive course I've ever seen
on trading it works for all markets if
you want to trade crypto Bitcoin and
altcoins I highly recommend you check
out mexc best deal on fees you could
literally scalp the way I'm showing you
with Market orders only and still be
profitable because the fees are so low
links in the comment pin comment and
description
if you are interested all right guys
that is it for today's video may God
bless you all in the name of Jesus
Yeshua the Messiah even if you are not
religious I still pray you and your
family are super blessed and I'll see
everybody in the next video peace