https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1rjyftr-UMI
All right, y'all. I'm joined today by a
very special guest, Crypto Crank. This
dude is blowing up on the internet, man.
He's trading multi-million dollar
positions. He's showing everything. He's
crushing it right now. So, yo, what's
going on, Crypto Crank? Thanks for
coming on.
>> Hey, what's going on, Casper? Excited,
super excited, man, to uh to be on the
show with you. Uh it's not every day
that you get to join uh your mentor, you
know, your mentor, man. I've been a part
of the Casper crew for for a very long
time and to to finally be live with you,
man, is just uh super super super cool.
Feels like I made it.
>> Yeah, bro. I mean, you're an OG in the
space. You've been here forever. I think
you've been like in this community
longer than I have, but you've been more
of like a mod of every YouTube channel
and in every group, you know. Um,
>> but one thing I've always known about
you is you're a crazy trader, bro.
Yeah, man. Posted the the P&L's been a
mod for a very long time. Um for almost
every crypto channel out there, man. And
uh as I got more involved inside of the
trading communities and the um just the
spaces, man, posting the P&Ls where I
could, learning um but yeah, it's it's
been a crazy ride, man. Since 2017,
2016. Um
just really enjoying the ride, man. It's
been it's been crazy. It's been awesome.
as a matter of fact due to to learn as
much as I can and now eventually start
doing these collabs and building my own
community and super cool man to get the
feedback from from the internet to you
know from all the channels that I have
been on mod for super supportive
>> 100% bro so I was hoping before you tell
us exactly what Bitcoin's about to do um
in the next few weeks just give us a
little bit of your background like how
did you get to where you're at right
So originally I was in the car business.
I was a finance manager um for many
years, dude. And you know, as in the car
business as as a finance manager, you
normally make pretty big money, man. And
I um wanted to learn how to trade. Yeah.
I wanted to get out of the the the 80our
work weeks, man. The 60-hour work weeks
in the in the car business. And um I
started following Bitcoin and and and
the trading communities. And I told
myself, dude, I'm not I don't really
care if Bitcoin's decentralized or what.
I don't think it's a saving grace. I
think it's a cash cow. So, I don't
really to me, man. Um I was watching,
you know, people like you and Cryptoface
originally. You you you were the only
two that I were watching for for a long
time. And I was watching you guys make
money off of this volatility. And I told
myself, you know what, dude? I have I
have pretty good money already. Let's
let's see if I can get started, dude.
So, I put my first 30, 40 grand on the
exchange, dude. And within 90 days, I
lost it. Just got crushed. And I'm like,
golly, man. I need to take this a little
more serious. If these guys could do it,
I could do it. You know, everybody needs
a coach. You guys are going to be my
coaches. I got to go through the sticks,
man, and and grind through this. And so,
I, you know, just took it really slow.
Started reading these uh psychology
books about day trading. And eventually
that's what led to me doing now, man.
Trading with the size that I'm trading
with, watching your your man, you didn't
have the the courses 1 through 18. We
sure needed those back in 2019,
you know what I mean? It would have been
nice, dude, to have all of these courses
that you had. But, um, yeah, man. It was
just walked through it like that. And
now I'm a full-time trader, um,
full-time streamer, full-time doing
everything, dude, with you guys. Just
just like you guys are doing. That's
what's up, bro. Um, yeah. So, you've
been trading with like some massive
positions like um multi-million dollar
positions.
You know, the other day you banked like
200k in one trade, right? Back in
January.
January was my first $150,000 scalp day.
Um, I think my largest swing trade,
dude, was like 60 grand. Uh, the good
old days back in November 5th of 24th
through December. I'm sure you're going
to remember that time, dude. Oh, yeah.
>> The election. We we we had all of that
same levels marked, dude. And it was a
good swing trade, man. And uh made a
couple hundred grand November, December,
but January, February, dude, I gave half
of that back. I'll never forget it,
dude. January 6th through February 20th,
inauguration tariffs, it just started
going downhill from there. And I had to
readjust to the scalping method that I
that I do now. And uh even even though
like a lot of people see the the large
positions and the millions of dollars in
positions, man, um it's all percentages.
It's just the same thing that you teach,
what I teach, um it's all percentages,
man. If I'm making these $30,000 trades,
dude, it's it's 10% on the account. 10x
leverage on on on the account. You know
what I mean?
>> Yeah.
>> But uh but yeah, that was my first first
major major uh trading day. Not my
biggest month, but it was my my biggest
trading single day, dude. It was all
live stream, live execution. Um, I
started off on Discover Crypto. Uh, they
couldn't believe it, man. Drew and and
TJ, all those guys were like, "Dang,
Crank, this is sick, dude." And I just
kept streaming for hours during that
day, man, and just nailing the scalps.
But yeah, it was my very first uh single
150 $160,000 day. It was insane, Jay. It
really was.
>> That is crazy, bro.
>> That is crazy. Um, yeah, man. So, maybe
you could like walk us through your your
strategy, how you're how you're hitting
these scalps like that.
>> Yeah. So, um, I'll go to the chart, man.
And the way I teach it, um, in in the
coliseum is it's really four stages. I
tell actually everybody, dude, to if
you're a beginning trader to to watch
your courses, dude. Dead serious. I I
tell everybody if you you know if you're
going to learn how I do my trading um to
watch your courses 1 through 18 and the
reason being dude is you you there's no
need to reinvent the wheel. I always
tell everybody you don't need to
reinvent the wheel. You just need to do
it better than the next person. Do it
better than me. But you need all the
education so that way you can have the
confidence to to to scalp with the sk
the strategy. So again really it's just
understanding that for one the the
strategy is scalping. All right. two,
the is structure, which is the ranges.
Most people have a hard time finding um
most people have a hard time finding
entries and exits. And if you have a
solid scalping range, multiple touches
in these ranges, whether it's sideways,
you know, um upward channels, downward
channels, these are entries. These these
touches on these support and resistance,
those are your entries. And then the
education, man, more time inside of the
chart to find these ranges. um you're
going to be able to find these entries
and you're going to start getting more
confidence to take these scalps. And so
just to give a a good example of how how
I do this. Um we could actually just go
out to like a like a 4 hour real quick
here. And the best range for me to be
able to talk about this is the good old
range right in here, man. Between 80,000
and 94K.
Uh we we have a clear clear range.
Obviously, we have highs, we have lows.
I draw it right in here. And then we
also have ranges within a range. And so
this is really my bread and butter,
dude. We could see that these ranges
right in here. Um, we have multiple
touch points for one. Again, if we're
going to scalp, we need that range.
Once we have our ranges, we can start
defining tops and bottoms. We have tops
here, multiple touches. We also have uh
the bottoms. We could see here, here,
here, here. And when we have a structure
like this in the coliseum, I explained
guys if it's it's also risk management
is also key. All right, risk management.
And our stop losses in the coliseum are
strictly based off of break of
structure. You long here, break a
structure. You want to get out of these
trades on these scalps. If you
understand the strategy that scalping,
there's a million trades. There's going
to be one thing that that everybody
feels in my community, dude, is that
um there's nothing missed. These big
moves up, these big moves down, those
are not what we're looking for. We want
long, boring ranges. And these boring
ranges, man, are where you can make a
boat ton of money. because again you
have defined bottoms, defined stop-
losses, defined tops, defined stop-
losses, and uh even on the bigger swings
within the range. Again, here, these
tops, these tops, and um yeah, man, this
is really the bread and butter of of of
how I scalp and how I'm doing this. And
then as we find these ranges, it gets a
little bit more tactical, you know, like
um when people were saying like uh this
bottom here, the fact that we didn't
take this out, I knew we were going up,
longed this, shorted this, and then also
on this double bottom here. I have my
fibs identical to yours, Jay. Yeah, you
have back tested I have back tested the
65 and it is gold. I mean here we could
see on the on the structure as well from
this this long accumulation range to the
top of this right in here multiple
golden pockets dude we could see we
absolutely killed and and again guys
this is a range within a range and then
even this range right in here this
parallel I mean we could see just
multiple touches here
bang
um we'll zoom in just a little bit again
you can see multiple touches when this
thing dropped
that magical 65 that we tal about, dude.
Boom. Again. So, all of these scalps
right here, guys, um once we're done
getting our daily bread, we're done for
the day. There is there's no need to the
the longer after a winning day, you're
going to start getting biased. You're
going to start getting overconfident,
overtrading, and this alone is that's a
massive poison in itself. You know,
dude, it's a it's a massive poison in
itself to to do that. But yeah, that's
really the bread and butter of of how I
scalp, what I do, the ranges, how I find
the ranges, multiple touches, highs and
lows, and um and then we just get to
work from there, dude. Find stop- losses
on on the break of structure.
>> Nice, bro. I like your strategy, and uh
I appreciate you um referring people
over to my courses, man. I actually am
posting a new one right now in the
process
of creating a new core series for 2026.
So, but yeah, bro, speak about this,
man. There's no need to to reinvent the
wheel. You've done it for us, dude. And
the fact that it's free, I get to use
it, so I get to I get to promote it. I
And I already am part of the Casper
crew, dude. So, I you know, I I tell
everybody,
>> learn it, dude. You walk through
everything that I I couldn't have done
it better. And and it really helps be
they, you know, they get in all these
channels. Everybody's part of
everybody's channel until they they find
out that it's just the same thing and
they're just adding to their arsenal of
trading tools. It's the same thing, but
it's just different styles.
>> Yeah, that's one thing I've noticed
about every trader, even if they have a
different strategy. Like I even know
traders that strictly use like Ichimoku,
but at the end of the day, we're looking
at the same levels, you know, the same
targets, you know, it's just support and
resistance. It's so crazy like when
you're first learning how to trade, you
learn support and resistance and then
you go through this phase where you're
like trying to learn Elliot waves and
like order flow and TPO and all this
crazy stuff
because you think that's the secret,
>> the sauce, man. And it's not. Simple
trading is the best trading. I say this
every stream. You don't need to
overthink it, dude. Just support
resistances, fib levels, and volume.
>> Yeah. And I promise you, simple trading
in a market like this with such chop
that we have and of course Bitcoin's
volatility,
you don't need to overthink the markets,
man. Watch the courses and and again,
everything that I'm going over, dude,
I've learned from from your community.
Um I I just started trading with large
size because I always wanted to I always
told myself, dude,
everybody needs a coach. You know, if
you want to be a football player, dude,
and you want to be the the Drew Brees or
the the Payton Mannings or whoever,
dude, or if you want to be the Everybody
needs a coach, dude. But you know what?
I told myself, I don't want to be a
cryptof face. I want to be a crypto
crank. I want to learn how to do this,
and I want to do it good, and I want to
be and it takes a lot, guys. Trading is
just not all roses, man. You're going to
go through moments, you I've I'll be the
first to admit, dude, when you're losing
money and you're broken and you're sad
and you're crying about it, dude, and
you got a wife and she Thank God I have
a wonderful support at my house, dude.
Because my wife's like, "You can do
this. You you're you can do this."
>> And now it's it's robotic, you know?
It's just like you, dude. You're it's
robotic. None of these things shake you
out anymore. The uncertainty because
you're now educated, so you have the
confidence to stick to your levels. But
that takes a lot of time, man, to get
the psychology in your mind that winning
in in crypto is not natural. Losing in
crypto is natural. And so when you start
understanding that the odds are just
straight up against you for one in
crypto, second,
I think only 1 to 3% of traders make it,
dude, it's it's hard as it is. You know
what I mean? And so yeah, man, it you
you got to stick to the rules. You got
to get the right education from the
right people. and and you cannot deviate
from the rules or interfere with the
process.
>> 100%, bro. And make sure everybody to go
subscribe to CryptoCrank on YouTube.
Link in the description, link in the pin
comment. Um because seriously, he's
putting out some awesome content. He's
live streaming. He's scalping these
markets. Absolutely crushing it right
now. And again, he's an OG in this
space. You know, he just got into
YouTube recently, but he's been doing
this for years.
So, one thing I really appreciate about
you is you uh are a man of faith as
well, right? You're a Christian.
>> I am a Christian. Yeah, man. I've been
um you know, my dad's a pastor and um
Yeah, man. I've uh I've been a believer.
I had a I had to have a come to uh
meeting Jesus uh come to Jesus meeting
uh a few years back, man. you know, when
you're kind of indoctrinated into into
the faith, you know, I was born to a to
a family that's a pastor, and then at
some point as a man, you really got to
ask yourself, um, am I a Christian? Am I
a believer? Do I do I actually read my
word?
And, you know, it it just sucks, uh,
Jay, and I don't know if you've had
moments like this in your life, man,
where it seems like you always come to
the Lord at your lows. And one thing I
noticed, man, is that God kept telling
me, Crank, I'm going to give it to you,
but it's going to be on my terms. You
keep putting all of these things before
um you keep putting all of these things
before me, and you need to put
everything first me and then your wife
and then everything else. And so, yeah,
man. Uh once I, you know, it was God
reaching out. When I say I had to come
to Jesus meeting a few years back, God
was reaching out. I was at a low. And
one thing that God God wants, dude. He
doesn't want our He doesn't want our I'm
sorry. He wants our obedience. And so,
yeah, man. Uh he reached out and I
reached back for the first time as a
man. Um I'm 35, so first time as an act
as a man saying, "Hey, yeah, I'm a
believer. I do believe in God. I put I
do everything for him first." And I
didn't really start growing until I did
that. I was fighting the system, dude.
And it's and it's for eternity. So now I
do everything. Yeah. Absolutely, man.
And you are as well, man. When I'd like
to ask you that same question, dude. How
long have you did how long have you been
a believer, man? When did you you know,
and I know once you made this decision,
did your life change?
>> Yeah. So, I've been a believer since I
was 22
in 2012.
And the funny thing is, honestly, it
happened to me at like the highest of
highs in life. So my whole high school
career, I just wanted to be a musician.
I wanted to be in a band. I wanted a
record deal. I wanted to tour. And I had
I got all that stuff. Um my band got
signed out of high school. I started
touring nine months out of the year
internationally. I remember this one
point in my life. I was doing a sound
check at a soldout venue. I think it was
like House of Blues in like Anaheim,
California or something. And um I
thought to myself, you know, this is
exactly what I hope my life would be
like.
And somehow in that time,
I just started to be super convicted
about my lifestyle.
And long story short, simply or similar
to what happened to you, like the Lord
told me like, "Look, Jay, this band is
your God. Music is your God."
and that's not right.
>> And so I ended up uh quitting the band,
selling all my musical stuff.
And yeah, from that point on, my life
completely changed. Like I had such
peace about the decision. I never looked
back. Didn't know what I was going to
do. Had no education, had no friends cuz
you know, you're in a band, you can't
have relationships. I was living in my
parents' garage.
And um like you said, the Lord said,
"Put me first.
and you won't ever have to worry about
anything." He said that very clearly to
me one night.
>> And I I can't say I've done that
perfectly, but I can't say I haven't had
to worry about anything.
And I can also say this, like, and I
don't really talk about this too much,
but
but I'm going to talk about it now. What
the heck?
Ever since I sold all my stuff for the
music, I gave all that money away. I
gave it all away. And when I did that, I
had such like a joy about giving away
this money. Right.
>> And you're talking about like tithing
ti. You gave it to the Lord or did you
just you?
>> Yeah.
>> You gave it to the Lord. You tithed.
Yeah. Great. Super cool.
>> I gave it all away.
And I got such joy from that. And then I
ended up
where the Lord would give me goals for
giving away money. And I would save up
money. It would take me time to save it
so I could give it away.
>> And and the more I did this, the more
the Lord gave me money. And the more I
gave, the more he would give. And I
would pray, Lord, I I pray that you put
people in my life where I could give to
specifically. It was it was orphanages
and churches.
>> And I had this prayer.
I said, 'Lord, I pray that I'd be able
to give away $200,000 a year to churches
and orphanages. The time seems
impossible, but he put that on my heart.
I pray this prayer every day.
And
>> wow,
>> you know, eventually
that became a reality. That became a
reality. And then I was even able to
surpass that goal. And the more I gave,
the more the Lord just opened up
blessing financially. it for me in that
way.
And you know, this is a short version of
the story, but all that is to say, I
know people are going to judge me for
saying this, this, and that, whatever.
It doesn't matter. I don't care.
You know, it's so true. The Lord says in
Malachi to test me in giving, if you
bring your full tithe into the
storehouses, the Lord's going to open up
heaven and rain down blessing on you.
And in my life, that's been 100% a
reality. And people talk about
manifesting and all this stuff, this
like new age pagan witchcraft basically.
And there is some truth to that. There
is. But if you leave God out of the
equation, man, it's going to lead to a
bad place.
>> And you're talking about turning
churches into businesses and just do
like you're saying like that that pagan
where they're demanding that you tithe
instead of just really coming from
yourself. And that's I had a problem
with that as well, man, with with
tithing because I thought, man, I'm
watching these churches just just dude.
They're they're just demanding from
people to tithe. Weren't really talking
about it from the Bible. Um, and then I
started watching some of these big
churches, dude, just do some radical
stuff. And I'm and I started praying and
then I, you know, I'm talking to my mom
and I'm like, she goes, Crank, you need
to you just need to pray. You need to
pray because God's going to tell you
where to tithe. He's and and and if
something's going on shady where you're
tithing, he's also going to let you
know. You need to trust him, but you
need to you need to tithe and you need
to you need to give your percentage to
the Lord and you need to do this. So,
and you're right, man. Ever since then,
it just don't worry about I mean, that's
that's a rowdy goal, man. If God's
putting it on your heart to to give
$200,000 a year and you're and you're
doing this like clockwork now and you're
that's amazing, dude. I mean, you're
super super super blessed, man. That's
>> allow
>> That's awesome, dude.
>> Like, yeah. I I don't take any credit
for this at all, you know. Um cuz I know
the Lord gave me that vision and he he
brought it to fruition. It's for his
glory,
>> not mine.
>> Mhm.
>> Um
>> that's why I rarely talk about this
stuff. But yeah, the Lord has done
amazing things
through my obedience in that way where
literally we've been able to build
schools for for orphans and church
buildings and dig wells and build houses
for people that live in nothing um all
over the world. It's it's been
absolutely amazing.
So, you know, for me, my faith is a huge
part of what I do and it seems like it's
that way for you, too.
It is. You got to walk. You got to
listen, man. Like you said, he doesn't
want I'm I'm I'm sorry. He wants our
obedience. But you know what, man? It's
weird how God comes to us um at the
beginning in the in the moment of
humility. You know, it's anytime you try
something new, you got to go through
humility stages, man. And just
understand that, you know, you got to
trust. You got to trust. And so, yeah,
man. When when when God reached out to
me, I lost a boat ton of money, dude.
And I this was my third time doing it.
My third time losing a just a ton of
money, dude. And um I started praying
and I said, "Oh man, do I just give this
up, man?" I got too cocky. I got I just
do I give this up and my wife was just
telling me, "You need to pray. You need
to you need to pray, Crank." And so it
was weird, man. God told me to uh go
>> Yeah. Yeah. My mom calls me crank. Yeah.
And uh so
it was weird, man. I was praying and I
and uh long story short, man, he just
said, "Go and talk to this dude named
Greg." And I said, "Okay, why do you
want me to talk to Greg?" Well, I go and
I talked to this dude, Greg. And I said,
"Hey, God told me I need to come talk to
you." He goes, "God told me you were
going to come and talk to me this week."
And he's one of the most blessed men
I've ever met in my life. I mean, Jay,
he is dude, this dude's rolling hard.
gives all the glory to God twice a week.
Make sure that he goes to the church and
cleans the bathrooms for free. Just just
deep into the church. He's a marriage
counselor. This dude is just blessed.
And you know, he he told me, God told me
you're going to come and talk to me. He
goes, "It's time. You've been raised
into the word, boy. You've been raised
in the word, and now it's time you start
being obedient. God's going to give you
what you want, but it's going to be on
his time, but you are not going to be
putting these things first in front of
him. you're you're going to do it again
and you're going to fail and you're
going to fail and you're failing. And
then he asked me, did at any point
throughout all the previous success did
you ever thank God during those moments.
And I thought to myself, not once, not
once did I ever say, "Glory to God, man.
This is all just made buu money." Nope.
I only prayed to him, dude, when I lost
buu money and I'm ready to give up. And
so this next time around, dude, like you
said, I don't do it for I don't do it
for me, dude. I do it for the Lord
first. I'm trying to be a a man of God
with my wife to be a leader, that's a
whole another conversation right there,
dude. To be able to lead your family um
and lead your wife and and your and your
your kids, that's a whole another plate
to fill, dude. And but God works on
those things, too. He does work on those
things, too. So, that's the part that
I'm on right now where I'm, you know,
putting the Lord first. My trading's
doing extraordinary, but now I'm trying
to be also a leader in my house. And
that's, you know, I've been married 15
years, dude. Uh 13 years, but I'm, you
know, I've been with my wife, dude,
since I was 18 years old. I'm 35. We've
lived together since we were 18. And
I've been married, you know, have my my
my children, but yeah, man, that's my
next step in my life. You know, I'm
putting him first every day the best
that I can. You know, we're all we're
all,
>> you know, fall short of the glory of
God, dude. But
>> yeah,
>> I do want to be a man and a leader now,
like the like the way I'm I'm trying to
do with my streams. And well, I don't
even compare those two things actually,
my streams. That's just working. But you
know what I'm saying, man? Be be a
leader of the of a household like like
you said, you do crazy things, dude,
with my with my family. That's crazy,
man. Because maybe, you know, we I got
on this stream to hear that. I can't
believe you were giving building
orphanages and wealth for people that
have nothing. I mean, this is huge,
dude. That's a big heart. I mean, that's
a big heart, Jada.
>> Super super cool to hear that, man. I'm
just
>> I'd like to ask you a Go ahead.
>> Yeah. I'm, you know, I look at it as
like we're we're just vessels. Like the
for some reason the Lord gave me that
that vision and
>> Mhm. Mhm.
>> You know, it's not like anything that I
did, but he gave that to me. And then
because I listened, God was able to do
those things. So for me that's
encouraging because no matter what
vision the Lord gives you if you listen
he God's going to do that thing through
you
>> you know and like you said and what
about being like a pastor man being a uh
do they call him a pastors or um what is
it I know you have your other channel
and you're working on that as well. Oh
yeah
>> I've watched some of it when you're
inside of the church man and and is that
another calling for you dude other than
day trading? I don't know. I'm very
passionate about studying scripture.
>> I I actually teach biblical
>> Pretty well versed, brother, in both
languages. That's sick.
>> If you ever want to learn biblical
Hebrew, I've got a course on free course
on that, too.
I'm not even kidding.
>> That's awesome. And you know, you know
full-blown Hebrew, dude. You know how to
speak full-blown Hebrew?
>> Uh, can I mean, low I I I can't really
speak modern conversational Hebrew. I
could get by. I could ask where the
bathroom is and order some food, but um
I'm mostly biblical Hebrew.
>> Okay. Okay. Cool. Cool. Amazing, dude.
That's it's hard to learn. That's
awesome. I guess not the Bible, but but
to, you know, understand it in its uh
most natural form, I would say. Right.
>> Yeah. I highly encourage if anyone's
into that, pursue learning the original
languages cuz
it'll help you grow in your love and
knowledge of the Lord.
Did you notice any differences, dude,
between I don't know what kind of Bible
you read. Like I'm a New King James
version, you know what I mean?
>> Yeah.
>> And uh does did you notice the
differences between two when you started
understanding?
Uh, well, I mean, you
>> I'd like to know because
>> you understand why they translate things
different ways. Whenever you're going
from one language into another, there's
going to come a time where you have to
make a decision because the word could
be translated maybe like four or five
ways. So, you have to make a decision.
So, it doesn't necessarily change the
meaning,
but it might take away some of the depth
or depending on which word you choose,
it might add depth or something like
that. Uh there's a lot of word play that
happens in the Hebrew that you totally
miss in the English. Um
and even in the Greek there there are
certain things that grammatically the
Greek is implying certain things and you
can't really translate that into the
English unless you add a whole bunch of
other words. So
>> I hope that makes sense. But in general
English Bibles are very good
>> you know.
>> Okay.
>> If you know
>> they're not doing us wrong. They're not
doing us wrong, man, and falling us
short. They're they're pretty spot on,
>> I think. So, I mean, you know, if you
get into like textual criticism and like
different manuscript traditions and
stuff, you can go down that road and
you'll see why some people say like
newer translations remove verses or
whatever. And there's reasons for all
that stuff. No one's trying to do you
dirty.
>> Cool.
>> Bottom line.
>> It's good to know, man. I mean, I like
hearing it because you're way more
versed than me, dude. Like I said, I'm,
you know, I'm just getting started all
over again like a like a newborn, man.
You know, I've been Yeah. Super cool.
>> Do you want to uh You want to go over
some charts, dude? I I loved hearing all
this, dude, because again, it's on my
heart. I can't believe that you're you
know, I love the story, dude. I love um
>> like I said, dude, he comes to us in
humility. I had to just say, "Man, okay,
now it's time. I've known better. Now I
got to and it's going to start being
weird taking that step every every day.
But now, dude, now it's just like you
said, all glory to God. The more you the
more you give to him, the more confident
you're going to be to do it over and
over and over again. And even if you
know things go wrong, dude, even while
you're believing, he he still has the
ultimate plan, dude. He's got the
ultimate plan on how this is uh is going
to go down, you know.
>> Hey, man, bro. You know, seek him first.
Everything else will just fall into
place.
>> Love it. Super love it.
>> So, yeah, man. if you could give us a
secret. What's Bitcoin going to do? Is
the low end? What do you see for the
rest of 2026? I know you're a scalper,
but I want you to give us some higher
time frame analysis here so that this
video has some time to be relevant.
So, one thing I I like saying guys about
macro time frame is eventually it's
going to come to you.
There's a million different ways to
trade within all of these ranges. Um,
I'll trade the macro time frames, dude,
when that price action comes to me. But
other than showing these things, I mean,
man, let's go, let's just start off with
with BTCUSD, let's go to a long-term
Coinbase chart. And, you know, when we
pull these fibs, dude, from the bare
market lows of of 153 up to all-time
highs, I really do believe the fact that
we front ran this, dude, um, to 57
$54,000, I don't think that the bottom's
in. I don't, just me personally, I don't
think that the bottom's in. I know we've
seen a lot of people also show the trend
line of 35k you know when we when we
look at it from here to here to here
you know these macro targets uh you know
30 35k somewhere in here
I would say dude
um I don't like I don't like on the
3-week dude momentum is just completely
coming down RSIs are coming down this
this momentum wave is get just getting
started on a weekly
Same thing. We're just getting started.
Do I think that that a a short squeeze
is imminent? Absolutely. 72 to 84 grand
somewhere in there, you know what I
mean? Would be a super super strong
um short squeeze. But on the on the
macro, dude, I mean, these momentum,
this is this thing is
I mean, I do like that this is a a lower
high on on the weekly right in here. You
know, this this
>> Yeah, I see it right there.
>> Bullish divergence. this bullish
divergence. I do like this. I do like
this, dude. So, do I think that a bounce
is imminent on the daily? I'm saying it
absolutely looks like we're getting a a
pump here shortly, sometime within the
next week. I think this thing's going to
rip. This is very very similar to this
price action right in here. We could
see, you know, this this momentum wave
here. And then we also had,
you know, these smaller momentum waves
right in here. Money flow was fat. Tight
RSIs. Really, really tight RSIs. Money
flow just getting flat. We had one more
dip. This momentum wave was created. I
This one's going to do the same thing, I
think. Dude, money flow just kind of
gets flat like this. And then bang, we
got ourselves this uh this bare market
pump. And this looks very very
identical. I mean, look, we just came
came up just like that. I think that
this is going to be, you know, very
similar. or this thing is going to end
up coming up to I'd say I mean this move
right here dude was 15% on this money
flow and um I think it's 15% right now I
mean from this bottom dude is is right
around $72,000
74 grand dude I think is going to be our
first big hurdle
>> but I do think I don't think our our our
Bitcoin bottom is in dude I don't think
60 60k was it man even though that's
down 50%
What do you think? What do you I mean, I
think on the daily, we're definitely
getting this pump. This looks identical.
This
money uh money flow is getting flat. I'd
like to see this right in here, you
know? I'd like to see this momentum wave
kind of curve do the exact same thing
here and here. And we get this pop get
this pop right up into here.
>> I'm looking for the same as you, bro.
Um,
the higher low so far looks pretty nice
from the 60K low. I'm looking for a bull
trap and then
I'm looking for one or two more big
dumps.
You know, I've bought my first bot
Bitcoin
>> here uh for the bare market.
>> It's 60K. Yeah. Yeah. I know you had a
post, dude, from a couple months ago.
You said, "Hey, I will start buying
Bitcoin under 70K."
>> Yeah.
>> You know, we got this double bottom
here. I know you like this confirmation
as well, dude. Um, I know you like this
confirmation on the on the weekly here.
This was pretty nice, dude. I like this
on the weekly, but I just don't I just
don't know, man, if this is really the
bottom. And I'm sure you've seen this as
well. What do you think about the time
frame on the weekly, dude?
>> Yeah. I mean, did you see floppingers
video recently?
>> I he he was in my stream last night and
he specifically told me, "Watch the
video." He goes, "Crank, I just went
over all of this stuff." He goes, "Dude,
it's a good I need to watch it because
you're the second. I need to watch it
today because I'm sure Is this what he's
breaking down that it's like
>> he's showing?" Yeah. Like we're at some
pretty critical support with a double
bottom on the weekly. He's saying maybe
the low's not as low as people are
thinking. He's not calling for a
V-shaped recovery, but he's saying maybe
we consolidate in this area and don't
come as low as people think. uh which is
an interesting possibility, but I just
go back historically and look at the red
money flow on the weekly. And basically,
if you start buying when money flow
curves into the red on the weekly and we
break structure on the monthly, you
start dcaing or buying on every dip,
you're like in the sweet spot, man.
So,
>> so you're thinking I mean, so you're
you're starting to DCA in. I was, man, I
was going to take some of these profits
from the last two months, man. And I was
going to buy a couple Bitcoin, but I
just I'm like, do I trade with it and
just continue to do these ranges or do I
I guess that's the difference, man,
between trading and investing. You know
what I mean? If I bought Bitcoin, I'm
putting it away and I'm storing it and
I'm not touching it for till we get way
past I, you know, I know for certain I
know for certain for Bitcoin 126 is not
the high.
>> Oh, for sure. I I know for certain, but
I do not believe for certain that the
bottom is in.
>> Yeah.
>> For Bitcoin. So, but it's like you said
on your last video, uh last couple
videos, you said
>> for certain though, you're not buying a
top.
>> Yeah.
>> Which you're buying at a 50% discount
plus. So, for certain you're not buying
a top. So, yeah. I you know, I would
tell all the communities for sure. I'd
start DCAing in.
>> Yeah.
>> I know for f And do you agree Bitcoin's
top is not it's not 126, dude? No. No
way. Bitcoin's going to a million
dollars. I think Bitcoin's for I think
for certain is going to a million
dollars.
>> Yeah. I mean, that wouldn't surprise me.
I'm shooting for like 180 to 200 first
and then Yeah. 500
>> before your next sell. Is that what
you're thinking? You buy here and you're
going to take that that 150% off of the
table and and just keep readjusting.
Maybe turn that 126 or true 100K into
support as we
>> go into 2028, 2032, somewhere in there.
>> Yeah, man. I mean, I've made so much
money just with the four-year cycles
since 2016. Um, just buying dumps and
then setting sell targets on the way up.
And so, I'm hoping to do the same thing
this time. So, pretty much my strategy
right now, and I have three
compartments. Like, I'm a forever huddle
guy. Like, I've got my forever Bitcoin
huddle. I'm not going to touch it
forever. Then I have my long-term swing
trading spot where I trade the four-year
cycles. Money flows red, I'm buying
every big dump. And then on the way up,
as we approach all-time highs, I start
selling.
>> Um,
>> okay.
>> All that is separate from my trading.
So, I don't I don't even mix those at
all. Like my leverage trading is not
mixed at all with my Bitcoin buying,
>> you know. But I would prefer a move down
between 30 and 40K. Like that's where
historically we bottom out at that 786
fib.
You've got it on your chart.
You like you like this right in here at
the 54. Yeah, I would I would really
like it, man. I mean, dude, this is
huge. I mean, multiple bounce zones. I
know that me and you have gone over the
same chart right here with the same fib
that we front ran this one. Remember how
we front ran this one and we were
waiting for it? Yeah,
>> we totally front round this one. And I'm
like, shoot, man. I can't believe that
this thing. And then I stick to the same
rule that you taught us, dude, that if
we typically front run these golden
pockets, we normally melt right through
them.
>> Just completely melt right through them.
And so, but that did not happen until a
year later, you know what I mean? Where
we did melt right through it.
>> It took some time.
>> So, it did and it actually bottom and
and like you say, it normally comes
right down to the 786 if it melts right
through it. And look, dude. I mean, this
is still even if we pull the fib, dude.
And um
but see, I don't like I don't what I
don't do now is when structure is
broken, dude. I pull the fibs way
farther out. You know what I mean?
That's I can't stick to that structure
anymore. Now I have to pull it from
literally the whole market structure.
And yeah, that we are front running this
again. And so maybe this is the bottom,
dude. Who knows? Yeah,
>> I just with with the confidence that I'm
building right now in my scalps,
I'm going to make a lot of money
>> from 65 to 72. From 72 to 78, from 78 to
82s was a huge level as well. 80 84s to
89s. Um
>> 89 back to 82. I mean 94s to 97s.
There's so much to be made and so but
yeah, I now what do you also think man
about altcoins? Um, I've been I've been
preaching guys that
the money did everyone's talking this is
probably going to be a much larger bull
run and I'm like guys the if the money
didn't rotate at 120,000 $126,000
Bitcoin, why in the world would you
think it's going to happen now? And me
personally, I think if it was an
institutional bull run, I do think that
you need to stick to the institutional
assets. So, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Salana,
XRP.
Um, and that's that's and then the only
two that I think that were really strong
during this cycle was B&B and Tron. If
we look at Tron, dude,
>> Tron hasn't been in a bare cycle for
years. It's just been cooking, dude.
>> Everyone uses
>> BNB,
>> the network at least.
>> Say it again.
>> Everyone uses the Tron.
>> Everyone uses Tron. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yep. And I mean,
>> Binance,
>> everyone uses Binance. I mean, dude,
even Tron is just a bulletproof asset
right now, dude. BNB, BNB looks
absolutely amazing, man. And so, you
know, when I'm telling these guys about,
you know, we're back into this heavy
accumulation area again from here to
here. I mean, this thing is this is buy
zone for me, dude, for for BNB. But
again, if it's a if it's an
institutional asset, the money didn't
rotate from Bitcoin into altcoins. This
is our first uh you know fouryear cycle
is still intact but there's only two
things that happened. One bitcoin put in
an all-time high a year before the h
havinging and two we didn't have an alt
season. I mean other than that the
four-year cycle is intact. Bitcoin is
right where it should be. We should
probably bottom somewhere between
September through November. Start our
accumulation. And most people need to
understand that that tops are made in a
day. Bottoms are created over weeks and
months. And so just be very careful
investing into altcoins is what I I
would say, dude, because the money
didn't rotate the first time. I don't
think it's going to happen the second
time. And third, we had some assets that
nobody even knew about, dude, that had
massive partnerships. Like Canton
Network came up out of nowhere. Do you
see what I'm saying? like we don't even
know the real blockchain that's going to
be used um for RWAs and governments and
>> right
>> so I just be very careful you know how
do you feel about that?
>> Well I mean my expectations were not met
this cycle with the altcoins and
thankfully I've always been very Bitcoin
heavy
but I am not buying any altcoins right
now uh as I'm buying Bitcoin. I'm not
buying altcoins. I'm not buying anything
unless they dip below their 2022 lows.
And I'm only going to be buying coins
that I know
are sticking around. Ethereum, Solana,
you know, that kind of stuff. Chain link
for sure.
>> I Yeah, I I want and that's one asset
that I do want a lot. And that's what I
was thinking too. Dude, if I bought a
few Bitcoin, I really would love Salon
at like 2030 bucks. Dude, we got so
close.
>> I would buy like a boat ton of Salana,
dude. Like a boat ton of Salana because
I do think that that's an easy play just
to get back to 170s.
>> Yeah,
>> two 209 easy play, dude.
>> Even if we never like
>> go catab parabolic,
>> you know, it's just it's a it's a nice
play like you said.
>> And I feel like an idiot.
>> It's not selling, you know. I watched my
altcoin portfolio
go up and I was not I didn't sell
anything because I didn't hit any of my
sell targets.
So now I just have to hodddle it back
down and if I can get in lower than my
original entry then I will and then I
will take the profit when we come back
up.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Now, normally what I'll do
too, man, was when momentum's on our
side um to the upside, then I'll start
doing coin margin as well. Like I did a
challenge, dude, where I turned 100
chain link into 2,000 chain link um 10
Salana into 300 Salana. I did it all
live stream, but I was teaching people
how to coin margin trade. And the reason
being I don't, you know, if I'm going to
buy these bags and I'm going to hold
them, sometimes I'll do that too, man.
Like I'll buy a quarter piece of Bitcoin
when it was at 80K, dude. And then the
moment we went up to uh we popped back
up to 100, you know what I mean? I I
sold that. Or when we dropped all the
way down to 90 and we we went right back
to to 116. I I'll take trading profits.
I'll buy Bitcoin specifically to trade,
but I'll hold it because it's just
growing my trading account, dude,
massively. You know what I mean? while
we're in this momentum phase. But
there's a huge difference between
touching 80, 90, 100K for the first
time, even a second time for a bounce,
and then hitting it multiple times to
the upside and getting rejected. So then
momentum is not on our side anymore. I
don't want to sit inside of those those
assets. That's a cut off point for me
where I'm like, "Okay, it's time to just
to stack tether and trade."
>> But
>> 100%.
>> Yeah, bro. So, why don't you tell
everybody where they can find you online
and all that stuff? Discord, YouTube,
socials, all that.
>> Yeah, if you guys want to follow me on
X, it's real CryptoCrank. Just go right
on to X. Um, I'm going to be there. I
post um all of my trades. I'm posting
the setups, the P&Ls, and then on my
YouTube, it's just cryptocrank. And I go
live um almost every day. I do market
analysis. I'm really known for just
doing the live executional trading. I
don't One thing that I I really pride
myself on is getting into a stream, a
one-hour stream. I'm in no trades and
over the hour, two hours, we execute
live trading, live executional trading,
live scalps, and uh but yeah, follow me
on YouTube, follow me on um on X, guys.
Those are my two uh those are my two
socials.
>> Awesome, bro.
Um I appreciate you coming on, man. God
bless you and we'll have to do it again.
Let's do it again, man. Let's do it
again. And we'll uh we'll go live and um
and we'll we'll break it all down, baby.
I really appreciate it, guys. Um
everybody in the coliseum, make sure to
follow Casper,
you guys. He's he's he's a real one,
man. There's not a lot of of of real
traders out there that are that are
breaking down true alpha, showing
positions, P&Ls, being transparent.
Guys, follow Jason Casper. I I man can't
plead it hard enough. So, thank you
again, Casper. I really appreciate it,
dude.
>> Thank you, bro. God bless. Peace and