https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wQ56uvPE7_s
all right y'all so today we're going to
be going over a very juicy market cipher
scalping strategy
and this strategy is one that i use
often but this is more of a stripped
down simplified version of it and this
is the strategy that i did use to get to
scalps like this one that i did post in
my discord 800 profits guys we gave this
setup
in advance in the discord as you can see
right here get the setup in advance
looking for this strategy to play out
again we did take another scalp right
here just recently last friday
from that level trade setup given in
advance in the discord juicy profits
took that trade actually from two
different accounts you can see we give
the setups in advance and the reason why
we're able to do that in advance is
because there's a very specific strategy
that i'm looking for and so today i kind
of want to walk you through that but
this is more of a simplified version for
somebody who's maybe newer to trading
and here is the general outline actually
this is a video i'm currently editing
this is the general outline for the
market cipher scalping strategy okay now
there's three aspects to this
number one is to mark levels on your
chart number two is we're going to be
looking for divergences
and number three is even if we don't see
divergences we can look at the rsis on
market cipher b the momentum and the
money flow to determine if it is a good
enter a good entry for a trade
now when i say we're going to mark
levels on our chart what i mean is this
now most of the time
and if you follow my channel by the way
make sure to like the video make sure to
subscribe to the channel guys
really helps build the channel get this
info out to more people also if you do
want to get into the vip discord where
we post the trade setups in advance and
all that good stuff daily technical
analysis updates you can go to
patreon.com forward slash jason casper
so when i say mark levels on the chart
if you follow this channel for any
amount of time you know that i like to
trade sideways markets meaning a lot of
people are always waiting for the next
big move right they're looking to catch
this or they're looking to catch this
but my philosophy is a little bit
different my philosophy is if i identify
a sideways market
something like this right here where we
have a very clear low and a very clear
high
and i'm simply looking to scalp long
when we come to the low short when we
come to the high long when we come to
the low short when we come to the high
eventually one of these times when i
short the high it's going to be that
massive move or on the contrary if we're
trading this bull flag type thing here
okay we have a very clear low a very
clear high and again when we come down
back to the low and you're getting along
here well we've taken three successful
trades and that third one is the
juiciest okay and so that's the way i
like to trade in and that usually
involves scalping and day trading based
on sideways ranges so when we were
talking about marking levels on a chart
what i would recommend for people who
are newer who might not be as in
good at doing technical analysis to mark
out the juiciest levels in the world to
like catch ninja injuries what we can do
is we can generalize and say when we
come down to the general low of a
sideways area then i can be looking for
a long position and when we come to the
general high of the sideways area then i
can be looking for
a short position
and one of the ways i like to do that is
to simply just go back in time and look
to see where did bitcoin generally or
any asset you're trading form a high and
you can just draw lines on the chart
these are called areas of support and
resistance and the way i like to do it
is you're going to find the first
significant high and the first
significant low in a general area so we
had a massive move to the downside and
we can see that we put in our first
significant low right here then we put
in our first significant high right here
and so that has kind of outlined for me
the general high and low areas okay
now again this does not have to be
perfect this is generalizing what we're
going to do is we're going to use our
indicators to determine
when we're looking to enter either long
or short based on these various things
now the first thing we're going to look
to do
is look for divergences now what is a
divergence this is something that a lot
of people get confused with a divergence
is where price and momentum are doing
the opposite thing so let me show you an
example quickly of a bullish divergence
a bullish divergence is where price is
making a lower low
yet momentum on market safer b is making
a higher low now this is a little bit
difficult to see here
and i'm butchering right now this trend
line because i was using the brush tool
by accident but we can see momentum
is getting higher from point a
to point b
price is getting lower and from those
same points point a to point b momentum
is getting
higher okay this is called a bullish
divergence showing us that there's an
imbalance bitcoin is oversold there's
too many people selling it because
market ciphers telling us momentum is
coming up yet price is coming down so
when we come down to a level of support
like that i would generally be looking
to take a long scout position there
again another instance of that would be
right here where we see bitcoin making a
massively lower low
while momentum here is making a higher
low again as we come down to the low of
the sideways range boom we can take a
scalp right from there now
what about shorts
you can do the same exact thing for
shorts let's see if i can find one
quickly i can right here we can see
bitcoin getting higher momentum right
here uh is getting lower right ever so
slight right here and we can take the
scalp short because we're coming up
toward the high of the range and we can
take the scalp short now of course we
can do this on multiple time frames my
favorite time frame to do this on guys
is actually the six minute time frame
okay the six minute time frame i i find
it to be very
um good for scalping
if you're i looking at a sideways area
like this okay so let's go down to that
six minute time frame here
because right now i'm on the 12 which is
good too but you're not gonna get as
many signals
so here we are on our six minute time
frame and let's just quickly see and i
look at this on the six minute time
frame this right here um
uh now actually we didn't get a
divergence right there
but we did get one right here
right to the exact
high and then we can see
right here coming down okay so the first
thing you're going to look for to enter
these trades is divergences because
divergences are going to be a very
powerful signal to either enter long or
short
now let's say we don't see a divergence
but we're still coming up to our general
high or our general low of the range
then what we're going to do
is we're going to look for these three
things right here we're going to look at
our rsis we're going to look at our
momentum and we're going to look at our
money flow on market cipher b
so if anybody is unfamiliar with what
these aspects of market cipher b are the
rsis are these two lines right here so
i'm going to go ahead
and
just turn everything off except for the
rsi so turn off our waves turn off our
v-wap turn off our money flow turn off
our big green dots sorry bit boy turn
off these and all we have here
are our rsis
okay
now what i like to look for
if we are going to come up to
and what happened here here we are
if we are going to come up to a high
what i'd like to see
even if we don't get our divergences on
our money on our momentum waves
is still potentially a really good trade
the first thing we want to look for on
rsis is we want to see are the rsis
completely touching each other
does it look like there's only one rsi
if it looks like there's only one rsi
even though there's two because they're
completely overlapped this is a sign
that we are going to get a move from
that high all right look at this
second time it happens rsi is completely
touching
we come down okay let's see if it
happens again
right here
rsi is completely touching looks like
one rsi
we come down okay from the general high
of this
little area now again we're going to be
looking for this to happen after a
significant pump in the sideways market
okay and this works for longs as well we
can see when we come down here to the
support
rsi's touching together boom we get to
move to the upside again right down here
rsi's touching completely together and
boom move to the upside now keep in mind
this one this specific instance also did
have a bullish divergence here so when
you see the bullish divergence
in addition to the rsi is touching that
is like a 100 point i should i could
never say 100 okay but that is going to
be a very good opportunity to
potentially get into a trade now here's
another good thing about trading this
way guys you have a very very good risk
to reward ratio and here's why
if we are identifying sideways areas we
have very very clear areas of support
very very clear areas of resistance the
support is obviously the bottom line the
resistance is obviously the top line if
we're entering trades at the low to long
and entering shorts at the height then
the risk to reward ratio of the trade is
going to be very good if we're shorting
here
we can put our stop-loss above that last
high when we got our entry signals
knowing that okay we're only going to
risk half a percent to potentially gain
four percent or when we come down to the
low of the range we can also say okay
i'm going to enter here because the rsis
were touching and i only have to risk
put the stop loss under the swing low
maybe risk point eight percent to
potentially gain here at four percent
and of course we're not going to always
hit our final target that's why we take
profit out along the way and by the way
if you want to learn a comprehensive
systematized way of how i trade
okay
to systematize your trading this is
meant for traders who are struggling who
to be profitable and they're looking for
a way to systematize their trading so
that they don't blow their account and
they can actually start being profitable
you have some people who have taken this
course right here who have quit their
job to trade full-time after learning
these things because it does give you
the step-by-step pieces to the puzzle to
stop getting wrecked and start at least
breaking even and if you apply these
principles to a t it's mathematically
impossible that you will blow your
account because we're just using high
probability setups and good risk
management
right you can check out the testimonials
here but even if you've never looked at
a chart before we teach you very good
technical analysis to mark out the
levels to look for so you can catch
those really good entries how i use
market cipher five very profitable
strategies that i use as well as mindset
and risk management so that you know how
to enter into this and treat it like a
business there's currently a 20 percent
discount in is the description of the
video
okay
so if there's no divergence guys
remember what we're gonna do
is we are going to look at the rsi's
momentum and money flow so the first
thing i like to do is look at the rsis
let's say there's no divergence but
we're coming up to a high and we're like
is this a good place to enter a scalp if
the rsis are touching each other and
they look like one rsi even though we
know there's two then you could say yes
this is a potentially good place to
enter a scalp trade the second thing
we're going to look for are the momentum
waste now i'm going to turn on the
momentum waves here okay
come over here to the gear turn on our
light blue and our dark blue waves here
and now what we can do is we can ask
ourselves this question we have to go
back to our
lines of support and resistance here
zoom out a little bit
but the question we're going to be
asking ourselves is do we see an anchor
and a trigger wave do we see an anchor
and a trigger wave now notice this right
here um well right here this this was a
diversion so this is really a perfect
setup right here
perfect setup would be the divergence
coming in the rsi is looking like one
with the divergence where we see the
anchor wave and the trigger wave as the
price is getting higher sometimes you're
not going to see
the um
the divergence so in that case we're
going to use multiple things in order to
enter our trade we want to see that
market cipher b is topping out as the
rsis are looking as one rsi and then the
third thing we want to look for is we
want to see that money flow on market
cipher b if we take a look over here
at the money flow on market cipher b we
want to ask ourselves is money flow
curving up or is it curving down now if
we see that market cipher b is coming to
a top and we see that the rsis are one
and we give it a little bit of time here
to see that the money flow is indeed
coming down fast as we are getting our
um candles printing then you can say
okay we come to the high we've come to a
resistance market cipher is printing
atop the rsis are together and i see
money flow coming down all right another
uh let's look for another place where we
would have caught a short trade this one
right here guys this one right here
this is actually the trade that i
entered over here
this crazy bitcoin short trade
800 high leverage trade shorted it right
from here guys right from here okay at
47 200
that was right here
um
was that it
dang maybe that's not it guys
no this was it right here
um
where did i short it from
let me see i have my exact entry right
here i shorted it from 47 400 so that
was it guys we took a short right from
here why
because we use this strategy we came up
to the area of the resistance okay
around that area we looked for
divergence we didn't see divergences
here okay did not see a divergence here
right price is coming up so is momentum
but then what did we do we looked at the
rsis we looked at the momentum waves and
the money flow and the rsis were one
right here we can see they were together
also market cipher b was printing a top
as we came there and the clincher guys
look at the money flow look at the money
flow this is something that a lot of
people do not pay much attention to on
market cipher b but you really need to
because here's why
the money flow is one of the most
powerful indicators if we turn off again
our waves
and we turn off even the rsi we'll keep
the our size on for now
look at this guys just look
money flow
starts to come up we get to move to the
upside money flow starts to come down we
get to move to the downside
if you see
price coming near your high
the rsis together and if you see the
money flow getting lower
as that happens
those are the three things you want to
look for so
just to recap guys because i know this
might be a little bit complex
but this is a very powerful way to trade
because it gives you a very good risk to
reward ratio it gives you very very
clearly defined highs and lows to look
for trades and we're really just looking
for three indicators on market cipher b
first we're going to mark our
levels second we're going to look for
divergences
okay if we see no divergences
then we go to plan b which is 98 000
bitcoin by november 2021 just kidding
then we go to plan b which is rsi's
momentum and money flow
and the three things that we're going to
be looking for on the rsi's momentum and
money flow are going to be
let me go ahead turn on our waves
turn on our rsis
they're already on
we want to see these three things number
one
the rsis are
together
okay number two
market cipher b is printing a red dot
we're about to print a red dot number
three
money flow clearly coming down
okay
so
this is a very successful profitable
market cipher trading strategy again
this is a general strategy
you might not always catch the exact top
or the exact bottom with this strategy
the way i was able to catch the exact
top on this trade
i mean
we we really did catch the top here
because the top was
what was the exact top the exact top of
the move was
and my entry was
47 416 right so very very good entry the
way we were able to do that is we had
some other technical analysis that we
were looking at and again if you want to
learn that you can check out the course
at
jasoncaspertrading.com 20 discount in
the description also if you do want to
get into the vip discord where we post
this technical analysis to help you if
you're learning you can go to
patreon.com for slash jason castro all
right
that's it for today's video god bless
everybody in the name of jesus the
messiah i pray everyone is super blessed
make sure to like the video and
subscribe to the channel and i'll see
y'all in the next one peace