https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=10Synp-joH8
all right y'all so today we're going to
be talking about the bitcoin technical
analysis and i'm currently on the road
y'all i've been on the road for the past
few days and i want to talk about what
has been going on with bitcoin because
we're coming to some very very important
levels now i am currently in a short
position right now as you can see
currently up about a little bit over two
thousand dollars in profit
right here now this is a trade setup
that we did give this morning
in the vip discord where we wanted to
see the price come up to this very
important zone between thirty thousand
one hundred and thirty thousand five
hundred with bearish divergences on the
twelve minute time frame and as we can
see if we come to market cipher b on the
12 minute time frame as we came up to
that exact level
we were indeed getting bearish
divergences on the 12 minute time frame
we also wanted to see money flow getting
lower
on the six minute time frame
on the three minute time frame so we got
our confirmations and now we're getting
a move to the downside and this is one
of the best ways that you can actually
be successful trading is have a plan in
advance and then when
the price action does what you're
planning for you can execute on the
trade now i have hit a take profit one
here i have my stop-loss at my entry i'm
going to see how much i can milk out of
the trade but now that i've secured a
profit i can just relax and not worry
about it so
let's talk about why bitcoin did get a
slight move to the downside here
and let me talk about my overall
sentiment on the market because it's no
joke that we are
at very crucial levels of support and
resistance by the way if you do want to
join the vip discord where we post the
exact levels that we're looking to trade
every single day
as well as the trade setups i'm looking
to take as well as a thriving community
of traders you can go to
jasoncaspertrading.com and uh the next
area of support actually is literally
right here uh literally right here
because we want to see a potential
retest of this support resistance flip
right there in fact i should while i'm
making this video limit out a little bit
more of this position right here
let's just limit out a little bit more
right here see if we can get that
but that is actually the next level of
support the retest of that resistance
right here
and um
[Music]
actually to be honest with you guys it
does look like we're getting some
bullish divergences right here but that
goes beyond the scope of the video that
i want to make right now first of all
why are we finding resistance at this
area what we have to do is we have to
look at what bitcoin has been doing
uh for the past few days okay so we had
a very intense move to the downside
where we broke down from the very
important support level of about 37 500
the reason why this was such an
important support level
is because it was the
diagonal support from the low that we
put in january 24th then again we put
the low in february 24th and then we
bounced twice from this trend line and
now we've lost the trend line
then what we did was we came down and we
put a bottom down here right around the
golden pocket
but the first major area of resistance
that we had along the way up was going
to be
in this area where we had consolidation
right here we can see two things that
are very important the first thing that
we can see is that we had a very high
volume node right here at about 31
the second thing that's very important
is if we go to the daily time frame we
can see that we actually did have
two daily candles closed right about
here at about thirty thousand one
hundred dollars giving us this very
important resistance zone
where the reason why this is so
important guys if we zoom in here
is if we want to see a real reversal
okay if we want to see a real recovery
right here
what we need to do
is we need to now start forming
bullish market structure which means we
need to start putting in higher highs
and higher lows now we've put in our low
okay right down here and in order for us
to start now switching into bullish
market structure we need to come above
the previous highs which is about 32.6
and so this is the doorway right here
into
a higher high this has been major
resistance the last video i made on
friday i was saying this is major
resistance right here this juicy level
we have rejected it basically
not to the dollar but very very close so
what am i looking at now
we can see the short trade is still
going we had a fast move up we're
getting a fast move down let's take a
look just objectively at what we're
seeing here on the charts
okay on the charts on the daily time
frame we are bottoming out on the four
hour time frame we also are getting
bullish divergences we're getting money
flow crossing to the upside
but we're coming up to resistance so
what that tells me is this
if this is going to be a real bottom
okay
what i would like to see is i would like
to see a retest coming back to a major
area where we can expect
bitcoin to find support and put in a
higher low potentially we have now a
high a higher low a higher high maybe we
can put in a higher low so we need to
think to ourselves
if we are going to see a reversal what
place should we look for bitcoin to find
support to get into a long trade what i
like to do is i'd like to pull out my
fib right so what i would do is i'd take
the fib from the swing low to the most
recent swing high that we put in and we
can see right here that
27.5 ish
is going to be a nice area of support
down here we're definitely if we get a
move to the downside i would be looking
for support there
something else take from the most recent
swing low to the most recent swing high
and we can see that around 29.5
we also do have another fibonacci golden
pocket retracement right there and so
these would be two areas that i would be
looking for bitcoin to come down to
potentially
get a bounce
to put in a higher height understanding
the fact that this right here
is going to be major major resistance
what we have to do here is we have to be
thinking one step ahead of the market
instead of following into a trade long
or short we need to sit down at the
drawing board and say okay
what are the possibilities
and if a happens then my plan is this if
b happens then my plan is this and i'm
kind of guys on the road as i said i'm
literally in the trunk of my car making
this video for you guys
so make sure to like make sure to
subscribe to the channel because you're
not going to get this juicy information
anywhere besides the jason casper
youtube channel guys pikachu hat and all
definitely not financial advice not even
real trading just paper trading
but
a few things guys these would be areas i
would look for retests we can also see
that the highest volume node from the
entire move to the upside is also that
29.5 thousand dollar area
so i am actually potentially looking at
something like this because of the four
hour time frame right
if we get another trigger wave here that
prints really tight close to the zero
line that could be actually a pretty
nice
uh bounce okay now keep in mind on a
smaller term timeframe we are absolutely
at support right now because we have
these previous highs right here
and you know just very very clear
support resistance flip this could be
you know a um
a higher low but personally for me i
would be looking for lower
so that's kind of where i'm at right now
i do think that what we put in down here
could potentially be a bottom but i also
wouldn't be surprised if we start to
like just simply trade sideways here for
a while so this trade i'm in now
i actually would even hold it back down
all the way to the low
and then expect maybe when we come back
to this low gonna move back up to this
high i think a lot of times people are
too impatient in these markets and
they're expecting huge moves all the
time
when in reality most of the time we
don't get huge moves and we just have to
take what the market can give to us now
if you want to learn how to trade this
way you can check out the course at
jasoncaspertrading.com
this course will give you the knowledge
and the skills you need to wear pikachu
i'm sorry this course will give you the
knowledge and the skills you need to
become a confident profitable trader
because we give you
the blueprint to having a plan in
advance that you can come in
in the morning and say you know what
if bitcoin does this and market cipher
does this then i will take a trade and
then you can take a trade and you can
take a profit and you can lock in that
profit guys
and
move your stop loss to your entry so
that you can
you know be profitable paper trading
this way all right
that's kind of where i'm at with bitcoin
right now guys um
25 discount on the course in the
description of the video
patreon.com jason casper to join the
community tomorrow we do have a vip live
stream at 8 30 in the morning where we
will be going over our plan for the
entire week potentially finding a trade
during new york open looking for a scalp
guys look forward to seeing you guys
there god bless everybody in the name of
jesus the messiah yeshua the messiah i
will see everybody in the next video
peace