https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=twiHuDh_NEM
about to walk you through a very simple
yet powerful scalping strategy that is
meant to be used on the lower time
frames the 5 minute time frame and even
lower this is the strategy that I use to
get into the scalp trade you see right
here on your screen and I use this
strategy all the time to get into some
Ninja scalps that has a very good risk
reward ratio so make sure to like the
video subscribe to the channel and click
that Bell for notifications because we
are bringing you the juiciest trading
strategy videos here on YouTube going to
go over the basics of this strategy
starting with the long trade that I'm in
right now and then I'm going to show you
how to fine-tune this strategy to get
those ninja amazing risk to reward
ratios now for this strategy I use an
indicator called Market Cipher it is a
premium indicator there are many other
indicators out there that function very
similarly but for this strategy I have
not found anything that gives as
accurate a signal as Market Cipher and
basically what we are going to be doing
is we are going to be looking at three
aspects of the market Cipher indicator
now when you load Market Cipher it looks
crazy this is Market Cipher B by the way
there's a whole bunch of stuff here I've
basically chopped mine up into two so
that we can more easily see what am I
looking for at a key area where I'm
looking for a trade and there's three
things I'm looking for I am looking for
the price to be making a lower low for a
long trade and then I am looking for the
money flow to be getting higher as the
price comes up to that lower low and I'm
also looking for the momentum waves over
time to be getting higher as the price
comes into that lower low and I am also
looking at this yellow line This is
called the vwob line I'm looking for
this to get higher as the price comes
into that lower low if I see all three
of these things then I can go ahead and
take the trade so basically I'm looking
at the money flow on Market Cipher is
that purple stuff that curves into blue
I'm looking at the momentum waves on
Market Cipher these are these blue bumpy
humpies right here I'm looking at these
and then thirdly I am looking at this
yellow line right here on some when you
load up Market Cipher it's not actually
a line it's an area it looks like this
right here right but nonetheless we're
looking for it to get higher over time
if we see those three things it is a
trade entry so let's go back and look at
a few major pivots in price where we
could have taken some nice scalps some
of those scalps actually would have
turned out to be much more than a scalp
now one of the best things about trading
this way is it basically gives you a
very clear-cut criteria that you need to
see before entering a trade this will
keep you from chasing price and trading
with emotion and this will also keep you
out of bad trades and only get you into
trades that have a high probability of
going in your favor so I want to start
with the top of this move that Bitcoin
got Tuesday August 29th
2023 if we go ahead and turn on our
Market safer indicator we can see that
we actually don't get any kind of a
signal to take a short according to this
strategy until we actually come up to
this exact high right this is very key
you might be tempted to short all this
stuff if you were watching my live
stream when I was live streaming the
long trade that I was in from lower I
was not shorting any of this stuff and
the reason is because I wasn't seeing my
confirmations on the oscillator but once
we get up to this exact High notice what
we see right here right we are seeing
number one the money flow getting lower
over time we are seeing number two the
momentum waves getting lower over time
and you have to zoom in to see this but
you would have seen it in the moment as
we are literally making this last High
the vwap on Market me this yellow area
is getting lower as the price is making
that high we have all three of our
confirmations right here to take a short
trade and as you can see this specific
trade would have resulted in much more
than a scalp if you had actually taken
that trade now that brings us to this
little rangy area right here and let's
take a look and see are there any other
trades that we would have taken here
would we have taken a scalp long trade
right here no we would not have why
because the money flow was getting lower
would we have taken a scalp long trade
right here yes we would because if we
take a look at this low that we made
right here we can see that over time the
money flow is getting slightly higher we
can see that the momentum waves over
time also are getting slightly higher
it's very slight and we can also see
that as we come to make that low this
yellow vwap is getting higher over time
and if we take a look we can see that
this would have actually given us a
pretty nice
.5% move give or take a little bit more
than that now when we're talking about
scalping a0 5% move on bitcoin is
actually a pretty dang good trade in
fact it's my typical tp1 around
05% in a scalp trade now let's take a
look at some of these other lows that
you know we could have been trading
let's be looking out no trade no trade
no trade no trade okay how about
this guy right here this low Wick right
here would this have given us a scalp
trade entry according to the strategy
well price makes a lower low we see that
the momentum I'm sorry the money flow
over time is getting higher we can also
see that the vwap over time is also
making a higher low right here and we
can also see that the momentum waves are
getting higher as the price is making
that lower low so the answer is yes we
would have gotten into to a trade right
here and as you can see boom this would
have been a very nice move of almost 2%
1.7% all right so we would actually have
not taken this trade here according to
the strategy and let's see the next
entry that we would have gotten right
here at this low for about a 6% move why
because the money flow is getting higher
over time as we put in that low the vwap
is also getting higher over time as we
put in that low and then of course
course the momentum waves also getting
higher over time as we put in this low
now you can go and back test this
yourself but I do just want to point out
the fact that this strategy will keep
you out of a lot of potential trades
right we didn't get an entry here we did
not get an entry here we did not get an
entry until we come all the way down to
this low that we put in right here it's
pretty crazy none of these gave us a
long entry not until we hit this low so
this strategy does require a little bit
of patience because you have to wait for
it to actually give you all three
confirmations now I highly recommend
when you were using this strategy that
you implement some kind of other
technical analysis what do I mean by
that you need to have some kind of key
level on the chart of support or
resistance that's going to also tell you
this is a key place to look for a trade
now I want to take a look at two of the
biggest moves that we actually got
during this entire chunk of price action
remember according to this strategy we
would have shorted this exact top and
longed this exact low that's the long
trade that I am actually currently in
right now we actually gave this setup in
advance in the Casper crew VIP Discord
from
25339 shout out to everybody in the
Casper crew who took this long by the
way if you want to join the Casper crew
you can go to Jason Casper trading.com
click the link to join the VIP Discord
we do multiple live streams every single
day going through the live Market open
sessions looking for trades given our
levels and our setups also if you want
to learn how to trade this way we
currently have a 25% discount on these
trading courses and if you want a long
and short Bitcoin and altcoins with a
great deal on fees check out mexe Link
in the pin comment in description 0%
limit order fees 0 1% Market order fees
an amazing deal especially if you're
scalping on low time frames people are
like Jason what about the fees well if
you're on mexe you really don't have to
worry about those fees even scalping A5
% move can be very profitable now the
biggest and the best moves are going to
happen when you use this strategy at a
very key level now the two biggest moves
we could have gotten in the past few
days using this strategy is the short
from right here and the long from right
here notice something the short was
coming up to the high volume node of all
the price action that we've traded all
the way from March 20 20123 to August
30th
2023 and then when we came down for the
long we were coming down to the
Fibonacci golden pocket retracement from
the most recent low to the most recent
High what you can do for this strategy
is if you find confluences technically
on the chart that tell you this is a
very important area to look when you go
ahead and take that trade you can take
it and hold a portion of it for a much
bigger move if you're not at a key level
maybe you'd want to close that entire
trade after a point 5% move or something
like that when you have a key level on
the chart this also allows you to get
very good risk reward ratios why because
if you know for example that you are
looking to Long the golden pocket and
you see your confirmations at that
golden pocket this basically allows you
to get into a trade and you know that
your stop loss needs to be below the
golden pocket it's giving you less than
a 1% stop loss and even if we're just
shooting up back to Value area low this
is still a 4:1 risk reward ratio now
this is the 4-Hour time frame when I
actually took this trade guys I was
using a much
juicier uh risk to reward ratio I was
looking at it like this I got my
confirmations right here basically so I
got to enter my trade right here I put
my stop loss below that Wick and my
takeprofit one was literally just a
retest of this previous low now you
might say Jason this is such a tiny
little move well if you take a look at
it it's almost a 1% move and it's a 6:1
risk reward absolutely amazing that was
my takeprofit one on this trade setup
because I was looking to Long the 618
Fibonacci level and basically six times
more potential reward than risk on a
takeprofit one I took out half the trade
and now I'm letting the rest ride you
can see us right now out basically a 20
to1 risk reward absolutely amazing so if
you have a little bit of technical
analysis that you apply to this strategy
it can give you very precise ninja
entries for much larger moves and if you
don't have a level there and you're just
trading basically this choppy price
action you can still take the trades but
you need to understand that you have to
be quick with your ins and your outs all
right y'all that is it for today's
trading strategy video go and back test
this on your own it works for Bitcoin
altcoins other assets as well forward
test it of course on your demo account
let me know what you think about this
strategy in the comment section Down
Below have you had success trading this
way let me know also may God bless
everybody in the name of Jesus Yeshua
the Messiah even if you are not
religious I pray you and your family are
super blessed and I will see everybody
in the next video peace