https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YuCJPWYd-0E
all right y'all
blessings to everybody in the name of
yeshua the messiah jesus the messiah i
do
pray that each and every one of you is
blessed
in many ways it is a beautiful sunny day
today
a monday morning i am quite tired due to
the fact that the past two nights i've
gotten
about four hours of sleep but that's
okay
that's okay that is a-okay y'all
in the stream today i want to talk about
finding good trade entries in an
uptrend because we are currently
in an uptrend and a lot of people are
finding themselves
in this cycle where bitcoin
ethereum starts at pumping and they
missed the move and then by the time
they long we get a little retracement
and they lose money so i want to talk
about how to avoid that y'all
shout out to memory man shout out to
enoch fpv
shout out to sandra smith
shout out to j-boy bullish all right
we will be live in about two minutes or
so
and as usual guys if we can get this
stream
up to 750 likes during the stream
i will be giving away 0.025 bitcoin
during the stream and so um
yeah share the video call your mom tell
her to come on in
give the video a like also guys we do
have we do have um
yeah let me let me let me talk about
this real quick all right y'all
we do have believe it or not in honor
i don't know if you all knew this but
yesterday
it was my 31th birthday
and in honor of my first day of being an
old
man we are having a 31 percent discount
on the course and you can do it you can
get that by using this code i'm going to
type in the chat right now
casper is ols
okay casper is ols i
was trying to say casper is old
okay but but
i made a typo and i decided you know
what
i'm just going to go ahead and keep that
typo so
casper is ols um
shout out to leon thank you thank you
brother
yeah i know i know i'm so old 31 i ca i
can't believe it okay guys
what i want to talk about in today's
stream
is the following
let me just pull up some chisnarts here
we're going to pull up some chisenarts
here we go so we're at the chisnarts
guys
the charts okay and you know
we just had in the past four hours or so
a massive move with the bitcoin where
with this one four hour candle
we came up about you know five percent
right five percent and now we're
starting to get a little
retracement and so i know a lot of
people were
you know watching these charts watching
things come down
feeling hesitant to get into a long
trade
and then all of a sudden the next time
they look at the charge man we're
pumping what is going on and then
people long up here and then now we're
starting to get retracement
what i want to talk about is if we're in
a bullish environment such as we are
right now
because there ain't no denying the fact
right if we go to the
the good old daily time frame there
ain't no denying the fact that we are in
a strong
bullish uptrend in fact if we take a
look at market cipher b here we were
talking previously
the fact that we could potentially print
a bearish divergence on the daily
we can see now that is simply not the
case we are not going to print a
bearish divergence on the daily time
frame
right we are absolutely not uh the
momentum wave is higher than the
previous the money flow has crossed
from the purple into the blue
and things are looking pretty dang
bullish guys are they not looking pretty
dang bullish
and so times like this is where the
trend is your friend
the trend is your friend until the end
of the trend
meaning this if if we're in an uptrend
you can
really bank on getting those long trades
in and because we're in an uptrend you
can expect
that we are going to continue in the
uptrend until all of a sudden we don't
continue in the uptrend but
you know there's a likely probability
that the trend will continue if we are
in a trend
and personally all i think we can come
up more here i absolutely do think we
can come up
to at least 48k 51k potentially even 60k
okay so the trend shall be
your friend um
look at this trend here right and
personally for me guys
i was in a short trade uh since friday i
was in a short trade since friday
uh you know over in the discord on
august 7th which was two days ago so
wait what was that friday
or was that saturday night
i am not sure anymore guys but august
7th right
i am i posted this trade setup right if
we come
to 45 000 the weekly level and the
bearish divergences are still there in
the two hour and the four hour
we can enter this scalp what i was
looking for was i was looking for price
to come
above this weekly level of forty five
thousand two hundred forty eight dollars
and then i wanted price to come above
the level and then lose the level
and we were going to enter the short and
these were my four
take profits now that is what happened
we came up to that level with the
bearish divergences we hit take profit
one
boom right here on that first candle
and you know long story short guys we
ended up hitting we ended up hitting
multiple take profits
we hit take profit three which was
actually the last take profit that we
hit
and um we didn't come down to take
profit four but i did close out this
trade
with a a good amount of profit um you
know
about 104 percent
was the last time i took a little profit
out of this trade
um so it was nice it's about a two
thousand dollar move
and then what happened was we started to
consolidate
on some support and
that turned into a move to the upside so
i want to talk about finding those moves
to the upside it really goes back to
this
if you all have been following this
channel for a long time you know that i
like to use market cipher
and i'm a big fan of different
strategies specifically
the four hour 24 minute strategy is a
great way
to find entries if we are in a strong
trend so when we were in a downtrend we
could use the strategy in order to
find shorts if we're in an uptrend we
can use that strategy in order to find
long so
how does that work basically the
four-hour 24-minute strategy
works like this where you're going to
split your screen
into two and on the one side over here
you're going to have what what in the
world is going on on this chart yo i
don't even know
i don't even know what's going on
what's going on in this chart i know
i have weird things on the chart let me
uh let me remove these things here
all right so for the four-hour minute
strategy you are going to have two
charts you're gonna have a
four hour chart and then you're going to
split the screen and you're going to put
on the 24 minute chart
and what we're basically going to do if
we're in a strong trend
is in order to catch these pumps
before they happen and this is great for
newer traders and it works even better
if you can combine this with some
important levels of support and
resistance
okay if we have a
trigger wave on the four hour time frame
okay
what a trigger wave is guys is basically
it's not an anchor wave
if you're unfamiliar with market cipher
the way that it kind of works is
you will have what's called a trigger
wave and an anchor wave an anchor wave
gives you the reference point showing
you that we have reached a bottom or a
top but in the case of an uptrend
an anchor wave is something like this a
big old big old dot
on the bottom of market cipher b
on the four hour the lower the better if
this thing can be on the 60
or or lower it's even more powerful as
an anchor wave and then a trigger wave
is any wave
consecutively higher than that first
wave so right here
we can see if we just draw a line
through here that momentum
started low at this anchor wave and then
we printed a trigger wave right here and
then we printed another trigger wave
right here okay so
this would be our anchor this is our
reference point showing us we've reached
a bottom and momentum is now revving up
and as momentum gets higher
it's showing us that we're going to get
another push
to the upside now guys keep in mind this
is one specific strategy that i use
that works very well in trending markets
okay
trending markets and it's great for
newer traders because it doesn't take
too much technical analysis in order to
find good trade entries
but what we're going to do is we're
going to wait for first of all that low
wave to print
and then if we get a higher wave on the
market cipher b
that is going to be our signal that we
should start looking for an entry so
once this green dot on market cipher b
starts to print
on the four hour time frame this is
telling us
it's time to start looking for a long
position
for a long position for a long
position now i'm frozen here on the
screen
so i have to redo my my thing for a long
position all right y'all that is the
first sign and you can set an alert for
this simply by right clicking on it
right right clicking on market cipher
bizl
click add an alert to market cipher bizl
you're going to click
market cipher bizl is blue wave crossing
up
giving you a small green dot okay and
you are going to do this
once per bar and you're going to give it
a fancy name like this
market cipher bizzle
uh trigger wave right
trigger wave and honestly guys i usually
do
trigger wave all right
and you're gonna set this alert and when
you get this alert on your phone
that's where you're going to start
looking for along and once once you see
this dot starts to print
that's where you're going to come over
to the 24 minute time frame
and what we're going to be looking for
on the 24 minute time frame is either
we are either going to be looking for a
green trigger wave
on the 24 minute time frame or
a money flow crossover on the 24 minute
time frame
okay either or now again
this strategy can be refined and
perfected
so that you can actually get even better
entries
and i'm going to show you how to do that
as well but really
um well first of all
i should just say this personally for me
guys
if you're if you're in my discord right
you know my potential trade setups my
my technical analysis i am indeed
posting
you know i'm posting charts i'm showing
supports i'm showing resistances
but um you know last night we really did
we we found some good support
um
we did find some good support right on
this well there was a 382 right here
that
that ended up giving us our massive
bounce but you guys know i'm
primarily looking only for short trades
right i'm primarily only looking for
short trades like this
the reason for that guys is because i'm
already i've got my long pants on
okay i'm on two bitcoin longs one of
them is from
37 630. this was a
setup that i um
i i'm pretty sure i entered it i posted
it in the discord but in the regular
chat channel
this right here is another bitcoin long
that i'm in
uh from 34k okay so this one is from 34
000 and then i'm in an ethereum long
trade from 2586
up 400 percent this ethereum trade this
was one that i did post in the discord
here
um basically where i said i just longed
the reason i just longed was because we
came down to a daily level of support
we had a bullish divergence on market
cipher b i know a lot of people
a few people shout out to the toast
father and a few other people who took
this trade with me in there
i'm already long guys so i'm i'm mostly
looking for
schwartz okay but i will still add to my
long positions
if we get a good setup like this
you know but pretty much in the
potential trade setups i've been po
i've been i've been you know posting
about
um shores but at the same time guys
if i start posting technical analysis in
the discord
where i'm giving a level uh you know
you can i alright let me say a few
things about the discord real quick
first of all guys it's not necessarily
it is not a signals
group yes i do give signals in there um
uh here's how it works when i post a
trade setup in the potential
trade channel right where we're pretend
where i'm i'm saying look
i'm expecting this to happen and if it
happens this is the trade i'm going to
enter for example
this trade right here i've said i'm if
this happens
this is the trade i will enter if i get
the market cypher confirmations while we
get this price action i will short this
these are trades i can plan in advance
and post
entries and take profit levels like i
did here if i'm just looking at a chart
and i see a good entry
i don't have time to go and make a post
and say this is the entry these are the
take profits this is the stop loss i
don't have time for that because
by the time i do that the move could
already be missed
so i will usually just post my entries
in the regular old
vip chat rooms like vip
bitcoin right here vip ethereum um
that i might be making a scalp channel
where i post scout moves but you guys
have to understand that
if i'm if i'm just saying hey i'm long
here it means
you know i got you got to learn it now
otherwise you're gonna miss the move
okay so i should just say that because i
know a lot of people are like
you don't post your trade entries in the
potential trade setups you just post
them in the regular chat
reason is guys because i don't i don't
want people to take a trade late and get
wrecked right because if i'm taking a
little scalp i don't know
you know how how big that move is gonna
be how small that move is gonna be
um but anyway my point here is you guys
know i'm primarily looking for shorts
and um but i will be adding to my
position if we get a good
uh a good setup and by the way guys you
can that discord
you can join it by going to patreon.com
for slash jason casper
also guys if you want to learn technical
analysis if you want to learn how to
catch those trades how to catch the
bounces how to scalp and all this
check out jasoncaspertrading.com this
course will give you the knowledge and
the skills you need to become a
confident
trader and improve if you're struggling
this will help you improve we go through
all the technical analysis you need to
know
this is changing the way people approach
the markets it's really you can check
out the testimonials
we go through all the ta we go through
extreme
market cipher sessions how to create a
strategy how to back test how to have
risk management so that even if you're
not the most profitable trader you can
still
i'm sorry even if you lose the majority
of your trades you can still be
profitable if you have good risk
management
and today we do have a 31 percent
discount
in honor of my 31st birthday it's only
good for today guys
it's casper is ols basically
um you know jason casper is old but i
had the typo there
you can go to jasoncasper.com
jasoncaspertrain.com and use that code
boom and um yeah so uh yeah also guys if
we can get the stream up to 750 likes i
will be doing the bitcoin giveaway
so yes the entering in and up trend what
we want to do is as soon as we see that
we are getting
this uh this green dot here on the four
hour time frame
we want to enter a trade when we either
get a green dot on the 24 minute or a
money flow crossover
on the 24 minute okay if we just look at
this
last set up here we had a green dot
printing on market cipher b on the four
hour
and that dot started printing right here
at about
four o'clock a.m and at about uh
4 48 5 a.m we get a money flow crossover
on the 24 minute
that would have been our signal to enter
we would have entered on this candle
right here
just before the very significant pump
that could have given us a nice move of
about
you know 4.5 percent and
this is a great way to catch those those
moves
in an uptrend because the green dot on
the market cipher b4 hour is telling you
that we've come to
a bottom right it's telling you that the
retracement is over and now it's time
to get another move to the upside and
you know i got stopped out of my short
in my sleep but if i had been awake
that would have been a signal to me to
exit this short completely of course
i got stopped out in profit i had my
stop loss in profit
but that you know would have been a
signal to me to
get the heck out now here's the thing
here's the thing
you can refine this strategy and make it
a little bit more effective
if you have some basic levels of support
and resistance marked out on your chart
already now let's take a look at what i
mean by that
first of all you know if we look
right here this is a 24-minute timeframe
let's take a look at the four-hour time
frame
right the four-hour time frame
i shorted right here right from this
weekly level
and i'm going to basically do the 4 hour
24 minute strategy in reverse right
because basically the reason i entered
this short is because we came up to a
very significant level which was 45.2 k
give or take
i'll put a line right here boom 45.2 k
we were printing a bearish divergence on
market cipher b
where as the price was coming up
momentum was coming down
right momentum wasn't coming down and
the if we do the four hour 24 minute
strategy we can see that
we would not actually have entered this
trade until
right here on this candle right here
which still would have given us a nice
move it still had given us a four
percent move
right but i was able to enter the trade
from a little bit higher
from basically the top from basically
the top
and so this is how you're going to
combine the four-hour 24-minute strategy
with some basic technical analysis
in order to really find those good trade
entries
and in order to do this it's a little
bit less
you know you're not just going to look
for a dot okay you have to look at
market cipher
and kind of front run it a little bit
and understand your environment a little
bit more
use in conjunction with support and
resistance levels
in order to find those really good trade
setups now
in order to explain this uh more clearly
i have to actually um do a few
things here hang on guys shout out to
super googly thank you brother
for the super chat all right okay
remember guys this is not financial
advice and lest anybody think
this is financial advice remember who
you're listening to guys
you're listening to a guy in the
basement gym
upside down glasses pikachu hat not only
a pikachu
hat but another hat on top of the
pikachu hat you would never want to take
financial advice from somebody like this
okay
you would never want to okay this is so
just remember this is
entertainment only and i'm not a trader
and you're not a trader you shouldn't
trade
i recommend nobody trade don't trade
okay this is just we're all the purpose
of this is just to analyze a chart
and say if i was a trader what would i
do right
that's how you should be taking this so
we can see that you know if we had taken
the 4-hour 24-minute strategy and of
course guys
in an uptrend in an uptrend you never
want to short based only on the 4 hour
24 minute strategy
you only want to take longs based on the
4 hour 24 minute strategy unless you're
a little bit more advanced
and you can see things like divergences
and you have good levels of support and
resistance mark
but my purpose here is to show you that
although i did use
you know in hindsight i could have used
the four hour 24 minute strategy because
you could say we had a bearish
divergence the the four hours printing a
red dot the next time we got a red dot
in the 24 minute
was right here we could have taken the
short instead
what i did was i waited for price to
come to a level of resistance that
i already had marked on the chart which
was forty five thousand two hundred
forty eight dollars
give or take and then i was waiting for
price
to come to that level and lose that
level and
what i was doing is i was combining
market cipher with
the level of support and resistance by
seeing that
as we're printing the bullish divergence
which was not confirmed
right it was not confirmed as we were
coming up to our resistance but we could
see it forming
and even if we go down to a lower time
frame like the two hour then it becomes
extremely clear
that yes we are printing a bearish
divergence as we are coming
to our level of resistance right
and now what i can do is i can see okay
we're printing the bearish divergence as
we're coming to our level of resistance
and then i'm going to come over to the
24 minute time frame and on the 24
minute time frame i can see the same
thing we're getting the divergence
as we're coming to our exact level of
resistance okay and remember i
entered the trade before the red dot
printed on
the um market cipher b for hour and i
entered the trade before the red dot
printed on the 24
minute what i was doing was i was
looking at marcus cipher
looking at it as an entire structure
okay
saying what is what is the general
structure of market cipher because
we don't want to just look for dots guys
you never just want to look for a dot
instead we want to look for you know
the overall structure of this thing
because this is this is telling us
this is basically interpreting the price
action for us
and putting it into you know a
visual language right you guys know you
guys remember
during the peak of the health crisis
that we had in this country
in 2020 i don't know if anybody
remembers that but you would have these
governors come on tv and they'd be like
yup the hospitals are uh they're at full
capacity i don't think
anybody's going to survive and then in
the little box next to them you got this
guy going like
right the sign language guy okay marcus
cipher is the sign language guy
sorry about that marcus cipher is the
sign language guy
uh for the governor of the state which
which is the price action okay
and so we we can we we don't just look
for dots right we
look for overall structure
if we see that price is coming up and
momentum is coming
down like this this is telling us that
there's an imbalance and there needs to
be a correction
same on the two hour and the four hour
time frame if we see momentum coming
down like this
and price is going up that means there
needs to be a correction
let's take a look at this here guys on
the two hour right now we can see
that price is coming down i'm sorry
momentum potentially is coming down
potentially we're going to print
a bearish divergence right here yet
price is pumping up this is telling us
you know it's not confirmed yet right we
need to use multiple time frames but
this is telling us there could be an
imbalance
and we could need to see a correction
here uh you know 46k
actually is an interesting level of
resistance
but um you know we are we are looking
for
not just a dot but at the general
structure
of market cipher and so
if you combine these two things you're
going to be able to find those good
entries now let's take a look at the
long entry here
right let's take a look at the long
entry as we're coming
down printing this bottom on the
four-hour time frame right here
i'm sorry this is a two-hour time frame
but even we can we can see it starting
to form on the four-hour time frame
we can see the v-wap starting to cross
up
on the four hour time frame if we go
down to the one hour time frame we can
actually see
that we are really starting to print a
bottom
right here okay before the green dot
prints it becomes abundantly clear
that the wave is crossing over and we're
about to print a big old green dot on
the bottom
right here okay it becomes abundantly
clear
and um you know if we if we take a look
on the 24 minute what do we see
we see a bullish divergence where
momentum is coming up
while price action is coming down
momentum is printing a higher low while
price is printing a lower low
and we see that we're about to print the
bottom on the higher time frames here
and not only that guys but we're coming
to an important level
of support okay again we're combining
the market cipher with the support and
resistance
and if i just pull out my good friend
you guys know
good old fib fib fib fibonacci
right you guys know fibonacci my good
old italian friend
mathematician super smart guy right
look at these bearish divergences
forming on the four hour guys look at
these bearish divs forming on the four
hour
this is intense but if we had just
pulled out good old fibonacci from the
swing low
to the swing high at the time
actually i think i i pulled it from this
swing low
yeah from this swing low here is where i
was looking
and i noticed this but i still thought
we could come down lower guys
i still thought we could come down lower
and actually you know what maybe we
didn't hit a fib
support no we did we did we hit this 382
right here
we hit this 382 support we which threw
it we came back up
if we had pulled our fib out and we
noticed that we were coming to
a golden pocket right believe it or not
this line right here was a golden pocket
fibonacci level
it was the high of the range guys this
is basically a re-test
of the high of the range and we had a
wick here
from back in back in early
may we can see we're coming to a level
of support
while we are getting our confirmations
on marcus cipher
and you know really because we're
hitting the support and let's say that
you're new and and you don't have enough
confidence to look at across multiple
time frames and say i can
see what market cipher is about to do
even still you could wait for this
four hour dot to start printing and then
catch along on the 24 minute
and have more confidence that the trade
is going to go well because of the fact
that we found support here
you know we did find support here back
here but look at what color the dot was
when we're finding support here we're
printing the red dot on market cipher b
on the four hour which means we do need
to consolidate or come down
that's exactly what happened but now
that we're starting to print the bottom
on the four hour on the support time to
come up
and again you can although i like the
four hour time frame you can
see what the four hour time frame is
about to do by looking at the two
hour if you come to the two hour and if
you come to the one hour
and you see on the one hour a green dot
printing you know
that pretty soon the four hour is going
to start printing a green dot as well
so if we're coming to a support and the
four hours been cooling off for quite
some time right
the wave is coming down for quite some
time we printed the wave august 8th at 4
am
we start to come down until august 9th
at 0 o'clock
am and then you go to the one hour and
you see all right it's uh
it's 23 o'clock p.m on august 8th
we're printing the green dot probably
means we're going to come up from here
we're finding support
then you can start to really look for
those long entries and that's how you're
going to do it in the middle of an
uptrend what you don't want to do guys
this is important is you don't want to
fomo into a trade
you do not want to fomo into a long
after a pump
if you miss the move then you miss the
move and you gotta you gotta wait for
another trade
if you miss the move you miss the move
and you gotta just you gotta just deal
with that right
you cannot trade the past you cannot say
we're pumping let me long right right
now
would i long right here i would not
people might say
we're printing a bowl flag we're gonna
break out of the bowl flag any time
guys personally i would not long here i
would not we're about to print a red dot
on one hour
okay we are cooling down on the higher
time frames
the 45 minutes printing a red dot
potential even
bearish divergences you know
we could pump from here guys we
absolutely could pump from here
i'm telling you i would not take it long
from here
because i would want to wait for a good
entry why would you want to take a trade
if things are if the probabilities are
not stacked in your favor
trading is all about probabilities so if
we can
stack the probabilities in our favor
then we can find a good entry and keep
in mind
even in the strong uptrend we are going
to have the retracements
right we are going to have the
retracements you know we had the short
from the weekly level we had the short
it was a good short guys
it was a good short you know a five
percent move with a little leverage
a little leverage you know i squeeze out
from this move right
it was a good trade and you know
i unfortunately did miss an opportunity
to add to my lung
while i was asleep i thought we would
come down a little bit more
but uh yeah so i personally you know i
don't like to take the longs unless i
see
we're coming to a support market cypher
is printing a local bottom right it
could even be
if you're looking to get into a long uh
that you you know we wait for
a re-test of the weekly a retest of the
weekly
and you know market cipher prints the
red dot we come down we print the green
dot
you know and you see that we're getting
bullish divergences on the lower time
frames
you know but don't just enter into a
trade guys
out of fomo don't do it don't do it
i'm telling y'all guys listen old jason
casper alright i've done that a million
times
i followed into a long trade and i got
myself wrecked all right just like my
old
southern grandpa i'm trying to get him
into bitcoin for so long
right my grandpa my southern grandpa my
colloquial
southern grandpa the dude you know i've
been telling him when bitcoin was 600
i'm like
grandpa you got to get into bitcoin man
i'm telling you this thing's going to a
thousand it's going to 2 000
it's going to 3 000. he's like nah son i
ain't getting under that
bitcoin stuff you know i'm uh i only
trust in the integrity of the united
states dollar son you know the greatest
country on earth you know we so grade up
all over in america
and i'm like grandpa you know you got to
do it then bitcoins are 3 000 bitcoin is
it
10 000. come on grandpa you got you got
to get into this bitcoin you know
yeah son out trust that thing's a ponzi
scheme right you overhear the pyramid
scheme well
you know finally finally my my
colloquial
southern grandfather he did get into
bitcoin
i'll tell you where tell you where he
got it
tell you where i'll show you
right here right here this is where he
got in
all right and any time
all right anytime you guys enter a trade
because we're pumping
you could be that southern grandpa you
could be that southern grandpa
okay you don't want to be the southern
grandpa all right
this is serious stuff guys do i look
like i'm joking around
all right do i look like it this is
serious
okay
what i don't i don't want to answer this
call get the heck out of here
um shout out to memory man who uh who
wanted to go long last night but it
pumped
and now he's short yep cool memory man
because uh
what the heck cool you know
because we're getting a little we're
getting a little we got a little
retracement here you probably could have
squeezed out some good profit here and
honestly
you know scalp shorts you can take them
scalp shorts easy guys you can take them
scalp shorts easy
if you have a level of elise and you
know how can we find levels of
resistance guys we could pull out our
fibs right pull out the fib
from here to here right and we could do
some fib extensions
right some fib extensions what happens
you know i don't i don't know i've never
done this but
turn on the 1.618 well what do you know
guys well what do you know
what do you know you know if you don't
know
now you know
my good friend is how i sing that song
uh so
yeah let's see here okay so we're
pulling out our fib
pulling out the old fibonacci and what
do you know guys what do you know
would you know it would you know it we
come right smack into
a fib extension level and you know
what a great short honestly guys
this is kind of a good short in fact you
could make a case here
that we come up to the 1.618 fib level
bearish divergence on the uh
on the uno hour
and as long as we don't put in a higher
eye you know maybe we'll maybe we'll
come down and consolidate a little more
after a pump like this
you know so yeah don't ever fomo in guys
just um
yeah don't ever fomo in just uh just
wait it out wait it out
let me tell you right now okay if i was
in no trade
and i am in a trade what would i really
be looking for well
you know i'd be looking obviously to
hopping along here
but if i was looking for a short what i
would want to do right now
is i would want price to come up above
this 1.618 level
print a higher high while the market
cipher bizzle
comes up and prints a lower high on the
12 minute
that would be a opportunity for me to
enter a short trade right if we got the
bearish divergence
on 12 minute like that let's let's go
down to the sixth minute and see what we
have what happened here
i mean look at this guys yeah we come up
to the 1.618
and we got the the the bearish
divergences these is how you could enter
little little scalp trades keep in mind
the money flow is getting thick so you
got to be careful you got to take profit
soon
right but if i was looking for a long
right here
and again you got to be patient
sometimes guys sometimes
you're you're not going to get an
opportunity you're not always going to
get an opportunity
and that's something that you have to be
okay with because if you're trying to
force trades
you're going to get wrecked 100 you've
got to wait for those setups to come to
you
do not try and force a trade but um
you know another thing we could do is
you know if we're finding good
resistance at the 1.618
uh we can clearly see that uh you know
momentum is coming down here
but um yeah if we're unable to put in
the higher high
then you could also take a short because
you see the bearish divergences forming
on the higher time frames
and again guys if none of this stuff
makes sense check out
jasoncaspertrading.com
because we go through everything here
how to do the levels how to get the fibs
how to use the volume how to use the
moving averages had to use the market
cipher how to find the divergences how
to have a strategy how to use risk
management today
we do have oh 666 viewers
i don't like that you know you all know
good old jason casper is a bible thumper
so
um what's up louis rivera
i have no idea how to spell colloquial i
don't even know how to say
colloquial colloquial is it colloquial
i don't know
so um yeah so so so yeah 31
discount on the course today y'all be
because of the fact
that we are indeed uh it is my 31st
birthday
um super googly you do not get the
patreon if you enroll to the course guys
so the the discord and the course are
separate
because i want to keep the i want to
keep the discord
um organized i want to keep it a
community of people who are invested
and we do have a really great community
in there the course used to have a
discord while the course was being live
streamed it no longer is
uh the course is all pre-recorded okay
guys if we can get this stream up to 750
likes i'm a giveaway
do you know how much 0.02 bitcoin is
worth right now
what check this out check this out btc
btc
usdizzle and let's do a good old
0.025 bow
gonna give away 1145.92
if we can get this up to 750 likes
you know so you know call your mom y'all
call your mom tell her hey come like the
stream you know
share the stream on your on your uh on
your book faces
and all the other social media tic tac
and
what's the other one elon musk one and
all that guys you know
yeah yeah i'm the only youtuber i'm the
only youtuber out here
trying to give away eleven hundred
dollars of bitcoin man that could
honestly
if you had eleven hundred dollars you
start trading with that responsibly you
could grow that
to 10k 100k 200k you could grow that man
that's that's a lot of money you know um
thanks david um
shout out to julius who's here in the
live recording days
uh adam uh shout out to you adam amir
thank you tommy strand for the birthday
wishes guys yesterday was my birthday
i'm officially old
um you know i woke up yesterday morning
my back
catherine wants to know how do you add
to a long trade
so basically the way you add to a long
trade is you simply just
wait for a what would be a good long
entry
and then you just uh you know what would
be a good long entry
and then you just add more contracts to
your position
right you just add more contracts to
that's how you do it
that's honestly how you do it let's come
to the one hour here let's come to the
one hour i mean honestly guys you can
you can make a good case so you could
get a nice short scalp in here
and memory man's already done it shout
out to memory man for the short scalp
and that's the thing guys you know
trading there's always opportunity out
there
and if if you are a little bit more
refined
and you know more how to use the charts
you could absolutely take a short scalp
i mean even even in these bullish
scenarios
right if you have your levels marked out
properly
um if you got them levels marked out
properly i know you know when i entered
the short right here people were like
man that's a dumb move
that was a stupid move of you jason
casper that was so dumb
how could you be so stupid well i'll
tell you why i'll tell you how i could
be so stupid guys
well first of all the lord does have
favor upon me
okay i cannot ignore the fact that the
lord is merciful
and gracious and long-suffering slow to
anger
and if we uh if we surrender everything
we have to him
then he will bless us abundantly that is
the truth but also market cipher and
support and resistance guys we were
coming to a level of resistance and
we're getting a bearish divergence
on the four-hour time frame i mean you
know
that uh that ain't no joke guys that
ain't no joke
it really ain't no joke um
that really ain't no joke
well y'all i'm actually i'm gonna have
to uh let's see here do we have do we
have any uh
shout out to michael who says i'm the
real 100 x hidden gem in crypto
i've learned so much here just watching
these streams thanks man
the mods too shout out to the mods
yeah ethereum
um ethereum
is uh yeah i've got some targets for
ethereum
africa wants to know how do you
surrender everything to jesus
in my understanding you basically it is
it's a heart thing
you basically need to come to the point
where
the only thing in your life that
actually matters is your relationship
with the lord and you are willing to lay
everything down for it everything that
you think you want
everything even though you think you
need remember
you know when the israelites came out of
the land of egypt
it was pretty nice in egypt even though
they were slaves right
and there's their spiritual symbology
there they were slaves
in egypt it's just how like we are
slaves to our sin right
and um when they left egypt they had to
surrender
everything they had to to the lord in
order for their survival they were in
the desert
for 40 years they didn't know how they
were going to get food they didn't know
how they were going to get water
and the lord provided for them and
that's that is the the attitude that you
need to have
jesus says you know those who seek to
save their life will lose it but those
who lose their life for my sake and for
the sake of the good news will find it
it's a paradox
but everything that we have in this life
we need to hold it with an open hand and
say lord
everything i have is yours and you
do with it what you will i am simply
just an instrument simply just a tool
and hopefully you know our our desire
should be to live our lives in a way
that reflects who our creator is right
people say yeah you know um
i don't i don't i don't believe in god
you know all these uh
all these rules and stuff in the bible
well those rules reflect who god is
and um for example why does god say
why does god say um
shall not bear false witness because god
himself is truth
right so if we do not bear false witness
we are reflecting who he is
right he says do not murder because god
is life
if we do not murder we are reflecting
the fact that he is the one who creates
and sustains life
if we why does god say do not commit
adultery
is because he is a faithful covenant
keeping god
and if we are to reflect him we also
need to be faithful in the covenants
that we make
and you know that's that's really what
it's about guys
um
i don't know what happened with crypto
face guys i do not know
yes i do eat chicken i do eat chicken
uh yep yeah scoob's 25 you missed the
analysis but you're here for the sermon
so yeah i'm actually going to have to
cut the stream guys because i am going
to i'm going to go into a vip stream
at 10 and 15 minutes there's going to be
a 15 a.m
yup hashem ricky yeah
we are going to do a vip stream where i
go into extreme detail talk about my um
talk about all my trading levels my
plans and everything's um
why do i murder chicken well i think
that there's
there's a difference between um taking
an animal's life for the sake of
sustenance and survival and the sake of
murdering a person and you know
there is a biblical precedent for doing
that in the proper way
in the proper way i would say that
modern
big agra the way that meat is handled
and produced is evil i would say that is
evil
you know when god said um you know when
he created man
and he said um you know be fruitful and
multiply and fill the earth
and and subdue it and rule over it
you know he he charged us to guard and
protect
and work the earth and obviously in our
in the
now that death has entered the creation
you know things have changed until the
renewed heavens and earth so
you know eating meat god has made an
allowance for that for now
so i don't think there is anything
morally wrong with that as well when
jesus was here
when yeshua was on the earth he himself
he ate fish he ate lamb uh
yeah anyway guys i'm gonna have to cut
the stream lest we wax too biblical
and uh yes i will see everybody who's in
the discord
um in the vip stream in about 15 minutes
all right y'all
blessings and peace peace