https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E-N_Yf-4qy0
all right y'all so i wanted to come in
and make a quick video about finding
good scalp setups because right now i
took this little bitcoin scalp here and
you can see i locked in a quick 300
profit i still have about 300 unrealized
profit
stop loss is also in profit so worst
case scenario i'll close a trade with
about 350 profit
so how did i find this trade setup
because a lot of people are asking me
how to scalp on low time frames
and the truth is when it comes to
stopping on low time frames i don't just
look at low time frames i take a more
comprehensive approach
so this specific scalp trade right here
began this morning in the vip discord
when i was looking at the local levels
to take trades from
and you can see right here that we have
this
previous high and we have a golden
pocket right above
that high right here okay
and so i'm specifically looking for
an area to take a trade from all right
a high with a golden pocket just above
that high
okay now i execute the trade on a very
low time frame and that's what makes it
a scalp
but let's kind of reverse engineer the
trade because this is something that if
you if you get into the habit of doing
this every day
you can find those really good trade
setups so it all begins on a higher term
time frame right
we're looking at the sideways range that
bitcoin is trading in and usually any
asset when it's going to be
ranging in a sideways market you'll
notice that it will usually have very
clearly defined highs and very clearly
defined lows and a center point and what
we want to do
is we want to find confluence
so that we can say okay
look
um if there is a specific level of
confluence i will be looking for a trade
there doesn't mean i'm going to take a
trade there but it simply means i'm
going to be looking for a trade right
there okay so we can see that we have
this very high volume node in the middle
of the range
and then as the price action was playing
out today
we can see that if we pull a fibonacci
retracement from the high to the low
that we have the golden pocket lining up
perfectly
with
that
high volume node okay now this gives us
a level a very
intraday scalp trade level to look for a
trade at okay even if things look
bullish on a higher term time frame like
the one hour looks pretty bullish right
but we know this level is here and what
this does is it peaks our interests and
now we can say okay if i'm coming in for
a scalp trade where would a good
opportunity be
now when we zoom into a lower time frame
like the 12 minute we get a lot more
interesting information
okay first of all
this golden pocket right here
okay is
is giving us a few
uh
other interesting areas of confluence
all right number one
we can see that we have this little area
of consolidation right here okay some
people might call this an order block if
we look at a higher term time frame
right maybe like the 24 minute time
frame or the 20 minute time frame we
have like an order block right here
and also we have this this previous high
right here where we know that there's
liquidity in the market
so what this does is this is identifying
for us multiple air multiple
points of confluence
that we can look at to say
i think there's a good chance that
bitcoin is going to get some kind of
reaction here even in an uptrend which
we're in locally right low high high or
low higher high higher low higher high
high or low higher high
our job if we're scalping is where is
that higher high going to be so that we
can scalp it down to the higher low
if you see things like this and actually
right now we're coming down to the v wap
which means that um
there's a good chance that we might
actually bounce from here
so um
we might come down a little bit lower
but
if we are in fact going to
uh
look for scalps we need to identify
those key levels otherwise if we're
scalping we're going to end up chasing
price which always always always is the
worst thing you can do chasing price
is always the worst thing that you can
do
because what chasing price does
is that will cause you to flop and grope
right if you know that we're dumping you
trying short you're probably already
going to be
too late right by the time you get into
that short trade
and on the contrary if you're trying to
long and you see we're pumping you're
probably going to be too late by the
time you get into that long trade you
need to know in advance where that's
going to be and so we're going to find
these areas of confluence now if this is
something you don't know how to do you
can check out the course at
jasoncaspertrading.com
this course will give you the knowledge
and skills you need to become a
confident profitable trader by having a
plan in advance knowing where to look
for
these types of levels right because i
had the plan in advance i would have
never been able to get in right on this
wick
if i had not had this plan in advance
right
and so
it's actually an important skill to have
you can't be scalping if you don't have
a plan in advance in my experience you
cannot be scalping if you don't have a
plan in advance
so once we know where we're looking for
a scalp then we need to look at our
confirmations now for me that's going to
be market cipher b
very clearly when i see that we are
coming up to an area of resistance
right i am then looking at these lower
term time frames to see do we have
bearish divergences as we come to that
level and the answer is yes
we have bearish divergences we see
momentum getting lower over time
we can even on the one minute time frame
see that the money flow if we draw a
line from the hump to the hump is
getting lower over time
when you have these confluences and then
you see these bearish divergences even
on low time frames there is a high
chance that you're going to get some
kind of a move down from there you don't
just want to take scalps from anywhere
you have to have lots of confluence and
then you have to look at your indicators
so the three things i want to see on
market cipher are number one bearish
divergence with the momentum waves
number two bearish diversions with the
money flow number three i want to see
that rsi looking nice and tight okay i
want it to be purple
and i want it to look like there's only
one rsi instead of two i want the
stochastic rsi and the regular rsi to
come together
uh to form one and those are gonna be
the three things that i look for then
also on the three minute time frame
right i see the same thing i see the
bearish divergence ever so slight here
but nonetheless still bearish divergence
right there
and then when i come to the 12 minute
time from the higher time frames what do
i see i see a bearish trigger wave
forming with the money flow coming down
all those things together are telling me
that this is a good trade to enter into
and we can see now the trade is up now
another
uh juicy amount of profits in fact uh
3199 let's take a little more profit out
at uh
3199 let's see if we can take a little
more profit out
can we do it
can we do it i don't know
i don't know
and then once you're in the trade guys
here's the thing my stop-loss is right
here my stop-loss is at 33.50 right here
cool
so once you're in the trade
once you lock in that profit take
partial profits out and then move that
stop loss into profit that way worst
case scenario right now when i get
stopped out i'm actually going to get
stopped out with a profit
right you can't go wrong being stopped
out on a profit
and best case scenario this thing is
going to keep riding
and perhaps when um
you know if this if this uh 12-minute
trigger wave can take us down a little
bit more maybe to re-test daily open or
something
then i can get even more money so it's
it's about identifying levels
with lots of confluence knowing what
confirmations you're looking for
locking in profit and that is how
i scout lower time frames and it's a
little bit more complex
than day trades because with scallops
you really have to be on point but i
just want to come in and make that video
i hope you guys found it useful
and if you did make sure to like the
video make sure to subscribe to the
channel
god bless everybody in the name of jesus
the messiah i pray everybody watching
this video
is super blessed
and with that being said guys this video
has been sponsored by
carl from the moon and jason casper
going to mcdonald's
hello um i would like to get a big mac
meal
coming to a theater near you guys
god bless and peace