https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GCGONeV-gNo&t=15s
all right yo so i want to talk about a
trading strategy that you can use to
take short trades
like this okay i'm currently in a short
from about 21 515
uh up about 38
i have had to take profit one
and i want to talk about how i was able
to get into
this trade right here because i think
that this could help a lot of people
identify
good times to take a short now first of
all i'm gonna take a little bit of
profit here
there we go
first of all we need to
always have a plan okay shout out to uh
shady butt fresh by the way we need to
always have a plan
the plan begins in the vip discord this
morning when i was looking to take a
short from
daily open around 21 500 where we also
had a golden pocket of point of control
a value area high of the range this was
the beginning of why i was even looking
for a short trade from that area in the
first place okay so this is not an
arbitrary area where i took the short
front this is a predetermined area
that i
was looking for the setup in advance
okay this is actually the second trade
that i've taken today the first trade
was this chicken's drinking water that i
gave the setup during the vip live
stream this morning that we do every
monday
where we took out these highs
with bearish divergences and we got a
move to the downside from there i
actually just live streamed that trade
in my previous live stream
but
now we've got this second trade right up
here
and so the first short trade that we
took was this one right here
shorting this area and now the second
one is here again it's because we have
the level in advance so step number one
to trading this way is
have that level in advance have that set
up in advance now this was a chicken's
drinking water trade but i did not get
the confirmations that i usually look
for usually when i'm trading chickens
drinking water i'm looking for bearish
divergence on market cypher b now if we
go to the setup i gave here you can see
that i was i was wanting to see bearish
divergence on the 12-minute time frame
okay but when we come and we look at our
chart we did not see bearish divergence
on the 12-minute timeframe in fact if
anything you could say that this looks
very bullish on the 12-minute timeframe
so why did i take this trade
there's a free tool out there called
coinalize.net
and what coinalize.net can show you is
it can show you the active participants
in the market
now
if you ever see something like this
where we have a key level now keep in
mind this was a fibonacci gold and
pocket retracement this was a value area
high of a range we had a lot of
confluences here and i'm just going to
go ahead and draw it on the chart here
so that we can see more clearly
where was that fib
pulled from
oh it was this one right here okay cool
yeah
so now i have to go and adjust the fib
so that we can see more clearly
but again remember step number one is
identifying
key levels on a chart okay so we knew
that this was an area of confluence
we're not going to use this trading
strategy just willy-nilly no we need to
have a clear area of resistance and
right now we can see that we had a clear
area of resistance at this fibonacci
golden pocket retracement we're going to
go back to our one minute time frame so
we can really watch what happened in
real time here
now
you're going to go to coinalize.net and
you're going to put on two indicators
okay two indicators indicator number one
is going to be open interest and number
indicator number two is going to be cvd
okay you're going to come over here to
indicators type in open interest put
that on come over to indicator type in
cvd go ahead and put that on
and
when you see that price is pumping up to
a key level and you notice that the open
interest is going down like crazy this
is telling us first of all let's define
what open interest is
open interest is telling us are there
active participants in the market
opening trades or not if we get a move
to the upside
and open interest is coming down that is
telling us that this move to the upside
is not fueled
by new market participants stepping in
and opening up long trades but instead
it's being fueled by shorts getting
closed okay this move to the upside was
a short squeeze okay shorts were getting
close
and what this is telling us is that
there's no new volume coming into the
market to sustain that move to the
upside
which means it's very very probable that
if we do come to a key area of
resistance and we see that the open
interest is coming down like crazy as we
pump up to there which it absolutely was
we got that pump open interest is coming
down the entire time
it's very very likely that we're going
to reject from there okay
and this is something you can use to
kind of enter into scalp trades even if
you don't have uh market cyber
confirmations which i typically like to
look for because this is telling me
right here
that this move to the upside isn't a
whole bunch of people stepping into the
market longing bitcoin no this is
actually a whole bunch of shorts getting
wrecked getting stopped out of their
positions and there's simply not enough
new traders coming in to sustain that
move to the upside okay if we come over
to
our order flow chart and exocharts by
the way if you do want to learn order
flow and stuff like that you can check
out the course
learn.jasoncaspertrading.com there's a
15 discount in the description this is a
course that me and boyan put together
boyne is a one of the traders in the vip
discord and if you do want to get into
the vip discord where we post the levels
and the setups every day
uh you can go to patreon.com jason
casper
but if we come over to our exo chart
template right here we can also see that
there's two things happening here number
one
we can see that traders are closing out
right here this is showing us shorts if
the candles are turning purple that
means shorts are opening if the candles
are turning gray that means shorts are
closing we can see as this move to the
upside is happening shorts are closing
big time right
and we can also see that we do have some
longs opening
and then look at this as soon as we hit
that into our level our daily open level
right that's the level again that we
were waiting for right the daily open
golden pocket value high confluence
right we're not just doing this
arbitrarily but we know there's a key
level here
as we come to there we can see some
longs are opening up okay
massive amounts of shorts are closing
and then immediately we see a big move
to the downside
all the longs that were opening up here
immediately are
under the water have to be forced to
close their position and so that can
give us confirmation to enter into
the trade and so this is a scalping
strategy that i use from time to time
and i figured it would be helpful for
other people to see how this looks so
that if you see something like this you
can also take advantage of the
volatility in the market so again guys
um
the the the what we are going to be
looking for step number one have a plan
have a level that you're looking for
and then step number two as price comes
to that level i would always be looking
for divergences if we don't see
divergences there
you know then be looking at
coinalize.net be looking at exocharge
see what's happening or a whole bunch of
trades closing out is just a big short
squeeze that immediately uh results in
longs being stuck up here and a whole
bunch of shorts closing out uh if so it
could make for a good scalp trade so
guys make sure to like the video make
sure to subscribe to the channel god
bless everybody in the name of jesus the
messiah and i will see everybody in the
next
video
peace
you