https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OKdHY8rTg_s
all right y'all so i'm currently
scalping the new york open session right
here i just took a little short scalp on
bitcoin i've taken profits stop-loss to
my entry
for a nice little profit for a scallop
trade right here
and this is going to be a one-minute
scalping strategy tutorial video and i
want to walk you through how you can
find these really really high
probability scalp setups
on these lower time frames guys because
it can be done but the thing is people
get
too excited oftentimes and they try and
take too many trades
so what i want to do today is i want to
walk you through things you can look for
every single day
so that you can enter scalps on very low
time frames
now again when we're scalping we're not
going for those big moves we want to
take profits very early right that way
we can lock it in
to guarantee that we're going to have
more money in our account after the
trade than before right take profit
early move that stop loss to the entry
and then if it runs hey you can get more
money if it gets stopped out of your
entry you know you made a small gain get
a few of these a day
two or three of these a day that's not a
bad profit for the day
cool just did another tv all right so
let's let's get into this guys let's
let's get into what we're going to do
the trade setup i took today was a short
from the daily open okay short from the
daily open now i actually took two
trades today from the daily open
and both of them use the same strategy
okay so here's what we're going to do
every single day when we come to the
charts
we are going to be marking out key areas
of support and resistance
where we are going to be looking for
trades
so one of the first things that i like
to do when i come to the chart in the
morning
and let me just quickly turn off all my
ta for the day is i like to look and see
if we have any areas of key support or
resistance
where i can be looking for a trade now
one of those areas that we should always
be aware of
is the daily open what is the daily open
the daily open if you go on a daily
chart okay just
it's very very simple it's simply the
price where that daily candle opened and
so all we have to do to get that level
is come over here
to horizontal ray click the magnet tool
come over to the candle and click it
and that will give us our daily open
now levels i like to look for for these
types of scalps are daily opens golden
pockets
other areas uh such as points of control
volume levels and stuff like that now if
you don't know how to obtain these
levels
you can check out the comprehensive
trading course at
jasoncaspertrading.com there's a 25
discount in the description of the video
guys this will give you that point a to
point b system so that you can always
have a plan knowing where you're looking
for trades where you should take profit
where your stop-loss should be etcetera
25 discount in the description check out
the testimonials this is changing the
way thousands of people approach the
markets here
but back to the strategy so once we have
a level established we're going to
simply just set an alert at that level
okay so for example
i had an alert go off when we hit daily
open now what we are going to do and
this is very very simple
we cannot fool ourselves here but we
have to be looking at market cipher b on
the one minute time frame now some
people use other indicators for me i use
market cipher b okay
we can probably do this strategy also
with the rsi let's check out if we can
um right here
in this case yeah we could have done it
also with the rsi
i'm gonna have both here so that even if
you don't have marcus cipher you can
still use this strategy but the market
cipher money flow is really really key
for this so basically what we're going
to do
is we're going to be looking for a
divergence on the one minute time frame
with money flow and momentum what that
means is
i want to see even on the one minute
time frame right i want to see this
money flow getting lower i want to see
this money flow getting lower
and i also want to see these momentum
waves getting lower
and i also want to see this rsi
being together let me explain what i
mean by that
on market cipher b i want to see as
price is coming to our level i want to
see price making a higher high
looking like a breakout or if we were
taking along looking like a breakdown
and then what i want to see on market
cipher b is i want to see the momentum
waves getting lower
okay as the price is getting higher i
want to see this money flow clearly
getting lower because the money flow on
market cipher b guys is a very very
powerful indication by the way
if you want to get market cipher i do
have an affiliate link in the
description if you're interested
if you're not interested in my affiliate
link i'm pretty sure bit boy has a
discount code i don't care if you use my
link or not i really do not care at all
so let's quickly just take a look at how
powerful this money flow is here
okay i'm pretty much going to turn off
everything
except the money flow right let's turn
off everything except the money flow
and let's just notice something right
look at the money flow guys and look at
how price reacts well i shouldn't say
how price reacts right because market
cipher is basically interpreting what's
happening in the market into a visual
for us
when money flow crosses to the upside
we get a move to the upside when money
flow crosses to the downside we get to
move to the downside when money flow
crosses to the upside you get to move to
the upside when money flow crosses to
the downside we get to move to the
downside now obviously we can't just
long and short money flow on one minute
that's why we're using all of these
things together
now when we see a divergence on the
money flow that is going to be very very
key for this one minute strategy a
divergence on the money flow is really
where the price is making a higher high
right but the money flow is getting
lower
this is telling us that this move to the
upside cannot be sustainable all right
so the first thing i'm looking at on the
one minute time frame is going to be the
money flow the second thing i'm going to
be looking at are these momentum waves
right here
okay these momentum waves right here
if we see that the momentum waves are
also getting lower along with the money
flow this is a very clear confirmation
at least in my mind
that we are going to get a rejection
from that level enough to take a scalp
trade guys
okay enough to take a scalp trade
now
the last piece of the puzzle is going to
be these r size now there's two rsis
here
my marquee cipher is purple and blue for
the sake of this video guys i'm going to
go ahead and
i'm sorry it's so disgusting to look at
this
red and green color here
but
notice these two rsis here all right
what i want to see there's a purple one
and then there's one that changes from
red to green i want to see the one that
changes from
red to green if i'm shorting be red
and if i'm longing i prefer to see it
green
and i want to see more importantly than
the color of the rsi is i want to see
them very tight together like there's
only one rsi it looks like there's only
one rsi right here right the stochastic
and the regular rsi come together as one
and that is
the
signal all three of these things the rsi
as one
preferably diverging as well rsi is
diverging
together as one rsi momentum waves are
money flow is coming down
at a key level
these are the things we're going to look
at to get into a scalp
on the one minute time frame and this is
a very very very high win right now once
we get into that trade guys
we're going to take profits early and
move that stop loss to the entry to
guarantee
that we are going to have a winning
trade okay
once we enter the trade
when we get that first move down because
it's very probable we're going to come
down
in pretty big chunk right here after we
get those confirmations you are going to
take out 50 percent of the trade at
least move that stop loss to your entry
to guarantee a win and then let the rest
ride because a lot of times when you
have all these confirmations to scalp
like that it can turn into a larger move
right
and then we set take profits along the
way down like as you guys can see right
here i've got another take profit down
here okay
and so that will guarantee that you are
not going to close the trade a loser you
are going to close the trade a winner
people ask what is your initial stop
loss
if i use a stop loss i put it above the
last high
and then put it to my entry at tp1 now
notice something here we had two of
these entries today we had one from
right here
and i did take that and then we had one
from right here and i did take that too
right
because we had that thing happen twice
right we had the divergences momentum
money flow rsi key level we had to
happen twice
so just be aware that if you have that
key level because we're using such a low
time frame
you might be able to take the same short
multiple times and rack up multiple wins
in a row
one more tip for this strategy guys is
that on this six minute time frame we
want to see
these divergences happening on as many
time frames as possible although the one
minute is my trigger time frame
because i saw divergence on the six
minute because i saw it divergence on
the three minute
and got my entry on the one minute this
gave me high confidence to enter the
scalp
now let's say you don't have market
cipher we're just using typical rsi
indicator
you know what then do we look for well
unfortunately we don't have the money
flow on the rsi but we can still look
for these divergences okay these are not
going to give us as high when rate
signals
but if you see it on the six minute if
you see it on the three minute and you
see it on the one minute as we're coming
to a key level
it's also a very high probability setup
the only downside to this is
because we don't have the money flow it
might not be enough of a move to make
money the money flow for me is really
key but if you're more experienced using
other indicators by all means go for i'm
just telling you what i personally do
all right
now
um that's kind of it for this strategy
guys if you do want the course there's a
25 discount also the vip discord guys
showing my private messages on the vip
discord shout out to uh joe
who makes these awesome pictures for me
he's really cool
if you are interested in the vip discord
where we post trade setups in advance
our plans for the day multiple live
streams a week
in here the levels we're looking at as
well as the thriving community of
traders posting the juiciest technical
analysis and potential trade setups you
can go to
patreon.comforcelife.json casper
this is not a signals group this is an
educational group we are traders we're
here to help each other out we're here
to teach each other and find confidence
with each other's technical analysis as
we can see now looks like we just hit
into the v wap
wow we just lost v wap
let's take a look here what is happening
as we lose view op
now i'm just rambling here on this video
this is for another video we'll be
talking about open interest and all that
stuff anyway god bless you all in the
name of jesus the messiah i pray you are
all super blessed
this scallop is turning out kind of good
here guys
as you can see
and uh yeah make sure to like the video
make sure to subscribe to the channel
i'll see everybody in the next video
peace
you