https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RKbZ0NKL2_U
all right y'all this is going to be a
trading strategy video and i want to
talk about finding good scalp trade
setups when bitcoin or any asset really
is trading sideways now for the past two
days bitcoin specifically has been
trading sideways in this little range
what looks to be
somewhat of a bull flag right we had a
very big move to the upside
and now we're consolidating trading
sideways this is an area where a lot of
people would stay out of the markets
they would say
you'll get sliced up trying to trade
in this little area of consolidation but
if we zoom in maybe down to the six
minute time frame
and we just kind of look at this on a
more zoomed out look on the six minute
time frame we can see that we actually
do have quite a lot of opportunity here
to make trades
and i want to talk about the strategy i
used to short up here and i shorted that
down
to this low right here of about two
point
almost two point five percent which for
a scalp trade is very good
and then i was able to grab a long from
right down here
and i'm currently still in the long
this short got stopped out in profit but
i'm still in this long from here
and that long was you know up about
almost four percent and now currently
again i took a short from up here
now what i want to walk through in
today's video is how we're going to find
these trade setups because in hindsight
it seems pretty obvious oh yeah just
long the lowest point but
how do we know that's the lowest point
how do we know where to look for a trade
and it basically comes down to three
things now just so you guys know i'm not
messing around
uh these are the trade setups so this is
the first short that i took my entry was
48 361.
we can see 48
361 was right about here
and i shorted that down to right about
here where i um
took profits on my short and entered a
long trade that long trade you can see
my entry was 47 400.
400 was right about here
okay
so i got into a long position right here
and then my current short from up here
my entry is
49085 so 49085
is right about
here
and you can see i'm short from there and
the short is currently more
right now more than 58 in profit yes i'm
using leverage in case somebody's
wondering how i'm able to get such a big
um
profit and loss from
these small moves okay
so how was i able to find these trade
setups
the first thing that you need to do
when you are scalping in sideways action
like this
is you need to know technical analysis
you need to be able to do your technical
analysis now the first short
that i took
we can see here in my vip discord the
last thing i posted on friday
was that i was in a scalp short but i
was looking to take another scalp short
if we get a bearish divergence
as we come into the 0.65 fib level slash
daily level okay and i draw a circle on
the chart
right where i wanted to short from
now this was not a random level on a
chart we can see that this was a
fibonacci golden pocket 0.65 level
and it was a daily level right here at
340.
and i wanted to see bearish divergences
on the chart so step number one is you
need to do
your technical analysis i apologize guys
you need to do your technical analysis
that is step number one step number two
is after you've done your analysis and
you find areas of interest
then you need to be able to look at
market cipher
and see if you have confirmations now if
we're trading in sideways markets
what are the confirmations going to be
they are always going to be for me
okay this is not financial advice by the
way
this is always going to be for me what
is called a divergence
okay so this was the daily level this
white level right here
was
the daily level okay
and as we came up to the daily level we
did print a bearish divergence on market
site for b we can see we put in a higher
high
as momentum put in a lower high
this is called a bearish divergence and
not only that but if we go farther back
in time we can see that the bearish
divergences
are actually forming the entire way up
right
from this point all the way to here we
can see that not only is
momentum coming down
from way back here
but also money flows coming down we can
put a trend line here and see money flow
coming down
as the price is coming up
so step number one is finding your level
and step number two is looking at market
cipher and we're not just looking at
market cipher in the immediate short
term like yes we see a bearish
divergence right in this area here
but we're looking across a longer term
as well to see okay i can see the
bearish divergences building coming all
the way back to
all the way back to here in fact the
bearish divergences really are forming
from this high that we put in here
and we can see that from this point all
the way to the the short right
we were putting in the bearish
divergence from that entire time all the
way to here
okay so we're looking for the
divergences forming we're looking for
divergences within divergences now
people are going to ask jay how do you
know which divergences to take seriously
well
you can take them all seriously it
depends on how long you expect to be in
a trade and it also depends on how key
of a level you have on your chart
so
for example right here this was actually
the 618 level
and we can see that the 618 level did
give us a bearish divergence as well
right
and we did get a rejection from that
level so i would take that seriously but
then if we get a divergence on a not
level
for example right here
this is a not level
there's no level here on the chart and
so even though we got the bearish
divergence to that point
i would not have taken that short i
would not have taken this short i've not
taken that short this short or that
short because there's not a level on the
chart so we have to make sure that we're
doing our levels first and then we're
only taking shorts when we get to our
level now this was a 618
right
this was the daily level and look at how
well the level was respected right i
posted this a few hours later boom
whoops
getting trade alerts up the wazoo right
now
um
the very next thing we see is us
rejecting off of that daily level okay
so the next day i come to the charts
and now
i am zoomed in on this little range okay
and how did i enter the long trade that
i took this long trade right here
from
this low that we put in
right about here
how did i get into this law
well we can see that i sliced up the
price action in as many ways as i
possibly could looking for areas where i
would potentially look to enter a long
trade and these were the two long trade
setups that i gave in the vip discord
now by the way guys
if you want to get into the vip discord
you can do that by going to patreon.com
forward slash jason casper
also guys if
you do not know technical analysis
and you want to learn how to find these
levels how to find daily levels how to
find value area lows with golden pocket
confluence how to find point of controls
how to identify patterns and stuff like
that how to mark these levels on a chart
check out jsoncaspertrading.com
this course will give you the knowledge
and the skills you need to become a more
confident more profitable trader
and this course actually you can check
out the testimonials here
but really what we do is we walk you
through step by step a systematic
methodical approach to trading that
shows you how to find the best trade
setups how to have a strategy that works
how to use risk management so that
you're locking in your profits making
sure winning trades don't turn into
losing trades making sure that even if
you do take losing trades you're not
going to blow your account because
you're risking the appropriate amount of
money how to use leverage how to use
stop losses all that stuff
check it out there's currently a 30
discount for a very limited time
in the description of this video i
mentioned it in last night's live stream
but we're going to be revamping the
course we're going to be doing the
course live once again live streaming it
three times a week with live questions
and answers with access to a whole bunch
of cool resources
so um
for right now the discount is going on
and then we're gonna do that away and
kind of revamp this whole thing so check
out the discount in the description if
you're interested
but we can see here
that um
we in fact
do
see
on this chart that i marked out in the
vip discord
that right here we had confluence we had
the fibonacci 618 level coming in very
nicely with the value area low
now i was looking at this area for a
potential chickens drinking water setup
where we would come down and come below
this previous wick
drop down to the golden pocket and then
get a move to the upside right that's
what i was looking for
and so i was looking for that to happen
with bullish divergences right
we have an untapped golden pocket with
confluence with the value area low
if we happen to make our way down there
i'll be looking for bullish divergences
for a juicy scalp long that could
potentially turn into a swing long
okay now i'm currently still in that
long it started as a scalp and it's a
very nice long trade right now i've
taken profits out already still have a
portion of the position open
but if we come to the chart here we can
see
that as we came down to that fibonacci
golden pocket area we'll just redraw it
again here
we also had the value area low right
here
if we come down to a very low time frame
like the three minute
we can see that we in fact did have a
slight bullish divergence as we lost
that level right here slight bullish
divergence right there
also on the one minute time frame
we did have some very slight divergences
coming in as we were coming down to this
level okay now this was a little bit
unclear to see i have to be honest with
you guys it was a little bit unclear my
confirmations weren't clear in fact i
was live when i entered the short and if
you were there on the live stream you
know i was like
i don't know about this one guys
i don't know about this one but
i still got the confirmations we still
came down to the level i had my plan
and because i'm using good risk
management only risking one percent of
my trading account i decided hey i'm
gonna go ahead and take the
i'm gonna go ahead and take the loan and
hold it so that's how i got into the
loan
and
let me see here
just
checking on my trades here because i did
just hit
um actually i just missed hitting a take
profit on the short
so i have to see what happens now the
short this is actually very interesting
guys
this is good that this is happening
right now look what happened we got a
bullish divergence on the three minute
time frame right now
literally as i'm doing this video we got
a bullish divergence on the three minute
time frame where price is coming lower
momentum is coming higher and now we're
getting like a little pump from here and
this could very well be
this very very well could be something
that's going to give us a pump
up and give us a higher high right now
especially once this three minute thing
starts to confirm
so let's quickly talk about how i got
into this short scalp right up here
which
you know i did take profits out of it's
a very nice short scalp even though
we're dealing with small price movements
you can still make a lot of money
especially if you lock in profits
especially if you limit into the trade
limit order out of the trade move the
stop loss just above or below your entry
so that even that market order isn't
going to set you back you can make money
doing this
if you're taking you know fifty percent
of the position out of the trade okay so
how did we find this last trade well
earlier this morning
again we were looking at potential
levels and one of the levels i was
looking at
were the wicks around 48
800 where we could get a really nice
fake out and then get a swing failure
pattern if we saw bearish divergences on
the four hour time frame and down
these were the wicks i was looking at
right here
and so what happened was we did in fact
if we go to a higher time frame like the
four hour we came above these wicks
right here
and as we came above the wicks look at
what we're getting on the four hour time
frame bearish divergence
bearish divergence where the price is
coming up massive high
lower momentum wave and we can see those
divergences forming on the two hour we
can even see them forming on the one
hour we can even see them forming on the
24 minute over time we can see these
bearish divergences forming as we're
coming up to that level and it's not a
random level
it is a very important level on the
chart um
well it's multiple levels
it was a uh well first of all we're
looking to take out these wicks
and second of all
this exact level up here is if we turn
on our technical analysis
um let me see here
i don't know if i have the folder
on my chart right now um
well i do on this local term right we
see this is a chicken's drinking water
wick potential right there
and also if we turn on here we go
nope that's not it either
well never mind guys it's also the val
it's also a value area high a value area
high
um of this range that we've been trading
in this general area from this dump okay
and so there was multiple confluence
there and as we came up to that area
as we came up to that area we were
getting the bearish divergences just
like we wanted to see and that's how i
was able to enter the scalp
so to sum up everything y'all the way
we're going to trade these sideways
markets
is number one
we need to have our levels marked out
that's the first thing we need to do
and then number two we need to have a
plan and we need to tell ourselves if
we get to a certain level
right for example this
if we get to this level and i see my
confirmations i will enter the trade
otherwise how are you going to know when
to look to enter a trade right these are
sideways markets you can get chopped up
right you can get chopped up very easily
unless you have a very good entry with
very clear confirmations
so step one do your ta step two have a
plan step three execute the plan step
four would be honestly make sure you're
using good risk management so that if
you take a loss it's not going to set
you back and then step five would be
make sure that you take profit when
you're in profit right if you are in a
trade if you were in a short
scalp like this thing right look at this
short scalp i'm in right that this might
be the pump that takes us up to 100k i
don't know
but i already took profit out of the
trade 50 of the position is out of the
trade already my stop loss is
just below my entry so that if i get
stopped out i will still end the trade
with more money in my account than i
started so all in all i had these three
scalp trades that i took in the past few
days that are all adding up to get me a
pretty nice profit and of course in the
meantime guys i still have my massive
swing long trades open that are just in
massive massive profits
so
that's it for this video if you liked
the video make sure to like the video
make sure to subscribe to the channel
y'all
and um
yeah
i don't even know what to say you know i
don't know how to end i don't know how
to end i don't know how to leave you
guys i just love juicy price action and
i love all of you
peace oh
and may god bless all of you peace