https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1Y5OKeEDMmc&t=31s
All right, we're going to get into
finding more juicy key levels, guys. But
I want to talk about how excited I am
about Antarctic Exchange. This is an
absolute gamecher. It's changing the way
people trade because in the past, you
had to worry about market makers
screwing you over, scamwicks. You never
knew if an exchange was going to freeze
your account, delete your assets, end up
to be a scam. This is the first ever
decentralized exchange where you
completely own all of your own assets,
but it functions as a centralized
exchange. It has all the functionalities
of a centralized exchange. It's just as
clean as a centralized exchange. It has
a mobile app like a centralized
exchange. It has so much flexibility
where you can open multiple trades at
the same time for the same asset. You
could be in four bitcoin longs, four
bitcoin shorts at the same time.
Additionally, you can use your
unrealized profit as margin. And what's
so great about this exchange as well is
the fact that it is
uh every single person who trades on
this exchange is a co-owner of the
exchange. If you trade on the exchange,
you yourself get paid of the trading
fees that the exchange makes. We all own
this exchange together. If you decide to
put capital into the liquidity pool, it
doesn't even have to be a lot. It could
be as very as low as a couple hundred
bucks. You now share in the liquidity
pool profits, which basically comes from
people getting liquidated. This exchange
is made by traders for traders. It
solves all the problems of your typical
centralized exchange. Because everything
is decentralized and 100%
self-custody, you always um know that
your money is secure, everything's
transparent on the blockchain, and the
Casper crew, basically anybody who signs
up under my link, gets the lowest fees
in the game. 0% limit order fees, 01%
market order fees, lower than any other
exchange out there. In fact, this deal
is only possible if you use my link for
Antarctic. We are changing the name of
the game when it comes to derivative
futures trading crypto and a lot more
exciting things to come in the future
for Antarctic. So, make sure to click
the link in the pin comment and
description. They even have demo
trading. So, if you're learning how to
do this, you can demo trade on Antarctic
without risking any of your money. So,
let's get right into the session. All
right, y'all. Welcome to support and
resistance part three where we're going
to be going over volume. What is volume?
Volume is a way to measure how much of
the asset exchanged hands at certain
prices. And we're going to be looking at
a tool called the fixed range volume
profile, the anchored volume profile,
and also the visible range volume
profile. We're going to get into all
three of those. But before I do, I want
to touch real quickly once again on
basic support and resistance. When we're
doing our top down analysis, we start on
the monthly, we go to the weekly, we go
to the daily, we go to the 4 hour. These
are how we get our big levels. But if
you are scalping, you can do this on low
time frames. You can go to the 10-minut
time frame. You can go to the five
minute time frame. And what you can do
is you can trade ranges as small as this
on the five minute time frame. Right?
You can literally do something like this
and say, I'm going to look for shorts at
the top of the range. I'm going to look
for longs at the bottom of the range.
And um I mean, just look at this, right?
You you've established your top and your
bottom here.
And so you literally had a short, a
long, and a short that potentially could
have hit a takerit uh takeprofit. In
fact, I I did take a short from here,
and I did hit a uh take-profit one on
that short trade. All right. So, you can
literally trade the five-minute time
frame doing this exact thing. And if you
happen to have like a weekly or a daily
level in your fiveminut time frame, man,
you know that's a juicy level. Okay? So,
I just want to point out that what works
on a big time frame works on a low time
frame. Trading on the daily and trading
on the 5minute are the same thing. It's
just you have less time to make your
decision. You have less margin for
error. The lower the time frame you
trade on. Okay. So, I want to take a
look at volume here. We're going to
start on the weekly time frame. And I
want to take a look at an indicator
called the visible range volume profile.
All right. So, you're going to go to
indicators up here. Type in VRVP. The
visible range volume profile. Make sure
to star it. Click that on. And what this
is going to do is this is going to show
you where the majority of the volume is.
Okay. So, let me show you exactly what
we have here. This is showing you the
volume of pretty much everything that's
visible on the screen. So, we can go all
the way back in time. And this volume
profile, I'll get into exactly what it
means in a second, is showing you all
the volume that's visible on your
screen. So, as you zoom in, this volume
profile is going to
change
because hang on, it's not
changing. There's something wrong. Hang
on, let's refresh the
screen. There you go. As you zoom in,
it's going to change because it's only
dealing with the volume that you have
here on the screen. So, I don't have
indicator on anymore. I'm going to have
to put the indicator on. And you can use
this on any time frame. the visible
range volume profile. The reason why
it's called visible range is because
whatever is visible on your screen is
what it is showing you. Now, what we
have here, and first of all, you're
going to double click it. And I like to
set up my volume profiles as such. Row
size 200, value area 70. I go to style.
I click my PC. That's called your point
of control. And I also like to make mine
blue and purple. All right? I recommend
you do that, too. Now what are we
looking at here? There are three things
that we need to be very much aware of.
First of all, we have this white line.
This is the P. What does the PC mean?
The P is the point of control. And this
means at this exact price, most bit
Bitcoin exchange hands most at this
exact price. Most people bought and sold
at the exact price of
96,831. It's the highest volume node of
all the price action you see on your
screen. Okay. more people bought and
sold Bitcoin at this exact price than
any other price that you see on your
screen. All right, so this is called the
point of control. Then you can see these
uh bars here are shaded, right? They're
shaded uh blue and purple and then all
of a sudden they turn gray. The top of
purple area is called the value area
high and the bottom of the blue and
low. What does this do? This is giving
us the fair value zone for the asset.
The point of control is most fair value.
All right? If you want to buy something
on sale, the point of control is not the
place to do it. You want to sell
something at a premium, the point of
control is not something is not the
place to do it. This shaded area is
telling you anything above this area is
considered
overbought. In other words, anything
above this area, the asset is overvalued
from what it should be and there needs
to be a correction to the downside.
Anything below this area is telling you
the asset is oversold. It's undervalued.
it's actually costing less than it
should. And so when we come below this
area, we expect to move back into the
fair value zone. And you can look and
see here that just based on what we have
on the screen, based on the fair value
zone, it's been very accurate. Whenever
price comes to an area where it's
considered undervalued, we have a
correction to the upside. It comes back
into the fair value zone. Whenever it
comes up to above that fair value zone,
above the value area high, well, it's
overvalued and we have a correction back
down to the fair value zone. So, just to
reiterate, the bottom is called the
value area low because it's the lowest
point of the fair value zone. The top is
called the value area high because it's
the highest point of the fair value
zone. And the point of control where
most people were willing to buy and sell
is called the point of control. Now,
just think about this in general. These
levels are determined by the market
participants. The market itself, the
participators in the market are
determining these levels. All right?
Because the only reason the point of
control is the point of control is
because most people decided this was a
good price to buy and sell Bitcoin,
right? The only reason this is the value
area high is because most people in the
market decided they were going to sell
up here because the market determined,
yeah, you know what? This is overvalued.
Let's short this. Let's sell this. The
only reason this is considered the
undervalued is because the market
determined, yeah, undervalued. Let's buy
here. Right?
And so these three levels, the value
area high, the value area low, and the
point of control are always going to be
key levels on your chart in confluence
in conjunction with your high volume,
I'm sorry, with your high time frame
levels. So you can see here we have a
monthly level right at the value area
low. That's called confluence. Two
things in the same spot,
right? This uh visible range volume
profile is going to change depending on
how you zoom in and zoom out. And I
typically don't use this uh indicator. I
typically like to use something a little
bit more precise and I'm going to get
into that now because you can see this
changes a lot right but it is good if
you want to say okay like what's the
highest volume node in like the entire
uptrend or whatever right you could take
a look at with the visible range volume
profile the two main volume indicators I
like to use are the fixed range volume
profile and then also right here it's
under projection I like to use the fixed
range volume profile and the anchored
volume
profile. Here's the way you're going to
use these. Remember how in the beginning
of the course when we were looking at
the fact that 90% of the time price
trades sideways and then 10% of the time
it gets a big move. You're going to
identify those sideways ranges, right?
Every time you identify a sideways range
because you can identify it as a
sideways range without
volume. Like you don't need volume to
see that the market determined that this
was resistance and this was support. You
don't need any fancy tools to tell you
that. But now imagine if you do have a
fancy tool to tell you the exact price
that the market has considered it to be
high and low, right? Because trading is
all about buying low and selling high.
So now what we can do is we can take the
volume the fixed range volume profile
and drag it through each one of these
ranges. And now what we can do is we can
see the volume profile
uh within the sideways range itself.
Okay. So, it's not going to change when
we zoom in and zoom out. It's going to
be fixed. That's why it's called the
fixed range volume profile. And what you
want to do every time you come to a
chart, as you're looking for your daily,
your weekly, and your monthly levels,
you're going to be pulling these fixed
range volume profiles. Now, look at
this. When we came down to our daily
level, the one that we launched in the
Casper Crew VIP Discord at
jasonaspertrading.com. If you are
looking for a thriving trading community
with pro traders to help you along on
your trading journey, check out
jasoncastrading.com to join the VIP
Discord, the best trading community in
the world, where myself and other
instructors, although we do not give
signals, we do walk you through our live
trading every single day, multiple live
streams a day, three or four live
trading streams a day where we're
telling you exactly what we are looking
for. And if we see a trade, we don't
give signals, but we let you know what
we are doing according to our analysis,
so you can find confluence with your own
trading analysis. Of course, inside you
will find myself and other instructors
such as Thor, one of our great
instructors, live streaming every day.
Boy, man, in one live stream, D took
four scalp trades. Absolutely crushed
it. Of course, White Phoenix is in here
as well, crushing it with his charts and
his daily live streams. Of course, I'm
in here, too. We're trading Bitcoin,
altcoins, stocks, forex, commodities.
You'll find it all in here. Plus, every
single month, we do games where we give
away thousands of dollars in cash
prizes. And no matter what time of day
it is, you will find conversations going
on, people to help you, and our advanced
TA channels where seasoned traders who
have been vetted by the team are posting
their analysis, their levels, and their
ideas to help you on your trading
journey.
Jason.com to join the community. Links
to this are in the pinned comment and
description. Go ahead and click the link
to join the best trading community in
the world. What happened, right? Well,
we came down to this level. It was a
daily level. And we already went over
why we had liquidity here. So, not only
do we have liquidity and a daily level
at just visible support with our green
box, we also now have the value area
low. We know that the market has
considered anything below this blue line
to be undervalued looking for a
correction to the upside. And so now
what we have here is confluence. We have
our daily level. We have our value area
low. We have our box just our visible
support where price came down here
multiple times. And we have that
liquidity. Now look at this. We have our
weekly level at
98345 right on the point of control.
Pretty crazy. Also, if we take a fib,
and I know we didn't get here yet, we
also have the golden pocket right there.
So, what you want to do with this volume
is you want to look for where are those
key levels on the volume profile and
then see if you can find other levels
that you've done through other analysis
that line up perfectly. That's where you
want to be looking for your trades. And
here's how volume theory really works.
We can assume that if we come to the
value area low, if we lose it and then
reclaim it, the probabilities are more
so than not that we will make our way up
to at least the point of control and
then probably fill the entirety of the
value area. On the contrary, if we come
above the value area high and then we
come back in, probabilities are most
that we will come down to the PC and
then eventually all the way down to the
value area low. And so one of the ways
you want to set up your trades now is
yeah, you're going to look at your
levels, but as we look at this, we can
say to ourselves, okay, the best trades
I can take are going to be from the
value area low and the value area high
of the range. The best
trades are going to be where we have the
price objectively oversold or
objectively overbought. And so you're
going to put your support and resistance
levels here at the highs and the lows of
your range that you've determined just
by looking with your eyes. Now we're
adding the volume. And then you're going
to be looking for your high time frame
levels. All right? And so this is how
you're going to do your analysis to
determine where you're looking for a
trade. And this is how you can start to
plan out your trades. Because if you
know, for example, you know, I'm
expecting a rejection from this box of
resistance where I have four levels. I
have the value area high, the daily, the
weekly, and another daily. You can tell
yourself, okay, my idea will become
wrong if we just keep pumping up past
this daily. And you know what? I'm going
to look for a short here, and I'm going
to shoot for back to the bottom of the
range, giving me, let's say, a 3:1
risk-reward ratio. This is how now
you're planning out your trade, right?
The price action hasn't even got here
yet, but you already kind of have a plan
in the back of your mind saying, "This
is where I'm going to look for a short
trade." Now, of course, we haven't
gotten to what we look for to actually
pull the trigger and take the trade, but
it doesn't matter for now because for
right now, we're coming to a chart.
We're doing an analysis, and we're
making a plan, and our plan involves key
levels on a chart and risk management.
We're already setting ourselves up for
success because we know this is
resistance. We have four things here
telling us this is a key resistance
where price is likely to get a
rejection. and we can kind of have a
rough idea and say, you know what, if I
wake up tomorrow and price is in this
area, I'm going to be looking at
different indicators and tools to
determine, should I take a trade here?
And I'm already telling myself, you
know, this is a sideways range, which
means if I'm shorting resistance, my
final target should be support. This is
going to give me about a 3:1 riskreward
ratio. I'm risking one to make three.
And then you ask yourself, is this trade
even worth it for me to take? Do I want
to risk one to make three, or do I want
to wait for a better trade setup? Maybe
you say to yourself, you know, I'd
rather take a higher riskreward trade
setup. So, I'm going to shoot for the
weekly level. I'm going to shoot for the
weekly level. If we come to the daily, I
decide not to take a trade from here
because it's just not good enough
riskreward for me. I'll wait to see if
we reject from the weekly because now
I'm risking one to make seven. Right?
And so, this is how we're going to start
to think over and plan our next trade.
Looking at the volume. Now another thing
very important about these indicate uh
the volume profile is
this there's the checkbox that says
extend
right as the price action develops this
these levels are going to change because
as the price continues to let's say do
this the value areas are going to change
because people are going to be buying
and selling at different prices right so
there's two options here option number
one you don't extend right and you are
simply looking at the volume as it
stands
Let's say oh hang on uh as it stands
like in a little range here right where
it's not giving you the whole picture or
if you click extend right it's going to
now shoot to where price action
currently is now both have their
advantages both have their advantages.
Let me tell you why both have their
advantages. you would want to not click
extend, right? Because when like we
said, support lost equals resistance,
right? Which means this sideways range
that we've already broken out of the
place where it used to be considered
overvalued is now going to be massive
support. And so for this range, you
would not click extend, right? Because
you want to know what was the fair value
zone of this range. Because if we start
to come back down here, right, let's say
we do come back down here, we are going
to respect these levels again, right?
When you break out of a sideways range,
just like how support lost equals
resistance, resistance claimed equals
support. It's the same with these volume
levels. In fact, you will often times
find price come back into an old range
and then start to respect the same range
again. Right? So, you want to keep track
of these previous range high volume
node, low volume nodes. All right, I
forgot to tell you value area low, value
area high. These are also called low
volume nodes. And one thing also I
should point out is the PC is most
important. But also you look at these
spikes here in the volume profile. This
is showing you like the volume profile.
The the mountain tops are where the most
asset bought was bought and sold and the
valleys are where the least was. Right?
So you could mark this out right here
and say this is a high volume node. not
as high as the point of control, but
it's still a pretty important level. And
you can see this little spike in volume
down here, too, and say, you know, this
is a pretty important level right here
because um you know, we have a lot of
volume coming in in this little
consolidation here. So, maybe I should
keep that on my chart, right? But in
general, you do want to not click
extend, right, for these previous ranges
because now you can see like if we do
get a breakdown, look at this. We have
the point of control and right on the
point of control we have ourselves two
daily levels where we put on our
monthlies. You can see right at the
value area low now we have a daily, a
monthly and a daily, right? So you want
to kind of keep those old ranges on your
chart in the event of a breakdown. This
is how you're going to obtain your key
levels on the way down. Now if you're
trading the range as it stands, then you
want to click extend, right? And that
leads us to our next volume indicator,
anchored volume profile. This basically
means you pick a spot to start it and as
the price action develops, it will just
always show you the volume from the
point where you clicked it to the
current candle. Okay? So, this is always
going to show you the value area high,
the value area low, and the PC. It's
kind of like clicking extend right on
your fixed range volume profile, but it
gives it to you as if it's a visible
range volume profile. So, it looks a
little bit some people think it looks
cleaner. I typically don't use this one.
I typically use extend right on the
fixed range but it is a good indicator
if you want to just like look at the
range real quick and just click once and
then you don't have to worry about
extend right you can just keep it here
and it will automatically change as the
price action develops. All right so now
we know about basic support and
resistance trend lines channels top down
analysis monthly daily weekly 4hour
levels and now we know about volume
levels and you're starting to see how
we're building confluence. Confluence is
where there are multiple things pointing
to one level that tells you this is the
level that you want to look at. All
right guys, that is it for this session.
God bless everyone and I'll see you in
the next.