https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LP43gxIhgD0
y'all myself and many others are
currently in this epic bitcoin scalp
right from this level trade is currently
up over 64 in profit so how do we find
this trade setup this was a level we
were looking at earlier today right here
in this white box we could see in the
vip discord we were looking to bounce
from around forty thousand seven hundred
dollars that's pretty much exactly what
happened guys you can see we were
getting bullish divergences on the 12
minute time frame money flow and
momentum was coming up as price was
making the lower low we also caught this
epic ethereum scalp which we are also in
again we are looking at this trade setup
in advance in the vip discord massive
level of confluence we come down to it
with bullish divergences on market
cipher b boom we get the scalp guys
that's how you got to do it if you do
want to join this discord where we post
these types of things in advance you can
go to patreon.com
jason casper if you have some nice
levels and divergences on marcus cipher
you can catch these small moves and make
massive profits on them