https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WljZ754O2zw
all right y'all today we have had some
pretty nice price action and i want to
talk about how i was able to take the
short from up here and take it along
from down here i think this can help a
lot of people who are looking to
day trade or take scalp trades because
these are the types of things we want to
look for
when we are looking to take high
probability trade setups so make sure to
like the video make sure to subscribe to
the channel because we're going to be
going over some juicy stuff
now it all begins with having key areas
of support and resistance marked out on
the chart this morning i made a video
about how i was able to grab a short
trade from right here long story short
we had a high volume node pretty much
coming in
right here okay and so not only did we
have the high volume node there but we
also had the fibonacci golden pocket
retracement right there as you can see
and you know it all starts with having
key levels marked out on the chart when
we came up to here we saw our
confirmations we saw the money flow
getting lower on these lower term time
frames we saw bearish divergences
okay and so that allowed me to get into
the short from up here now we came down
and we had a few targets below us one of
the targets was the weekly open one of
the targets was the daily i'm still kind
of hoping we come down to that daily all
right
now
when you have these levels on your chart
you can know what to look for so that
you can be prepared to take a trade
when we came down to the weekly open we
got ourselves a very nice pattern on the
12 minute time frame which is this the
uneven butt cheek pattern this is where
we get price making a lower low to a key
level and market cipher b is giving us
the coveted uneven butt cheek pattern
okay right here uneven butt cheeks guys
we have a left cheek nice and big and
juicy the right cheek not that big not
that juicy
this is
one of the most high probability trade
setups you will ever take in your life i
would say and this is not financial
advice but if we ever do come down to a
key level of support like this
okay this is the weekly open right here
that uh and you see clear divergences
especially if you have snake eyes on
market cipher b that is a very very high
probability trade setup now we come up
and we come to a key area of resistance
right here right this is a golden pocket
fibonacci retracement it's the monthly
level
and it's the v-lop now this allowed me
to compound my short trade and basically
give myself a really nice entry because
i had already taken a lot of profits
as you can see uh
at these lows and so i was able to then
take those profits put them back into
the trade and then take profit again
down here at this golden pocket now when
we came up to this area of resistance i
want to show you what we saw on the
chart because this will help you be able
to identify
areas where you can look for a trade
what did we see on coinalize.net we saw
that this bounce right here was
primarily a short squeeze because we
could see that the open interest was
decreasing big time
as we came up into this area of
resistance and if we're ever getting a
move and you see open interest is
decreasing
that is telling us that there is
absolutely no new money coming into the
market to drive the price up instead
this is a short squeeze and shorts are
closing out and or taking profits
um
and that's why we're getting the move to
the upside and we know it's a weak move
and if we come into a key area of
resistance which we did have on the
chart right here
we can expect a rejection now that's
exactly what we got we got our rejection
now
let's go back and understand the
framework here and the context in which
we're taking these traits we came down
to key support
after a day of dropping in price with
very clear bullish divergences on the 12
minute time frame clear bullish
divergences as well on the 24 minute
time frame we can see from here
to here we have bullish divergences as
the price is making a
lower low again we have those beautiful
butt cheeks okay
when you have those beautiful butt
cheeks it can make for a very healthy
potential reversal right very healthy we
want to see all these confluences how
many do we have one two three four five
six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
and i'm sure he has some on his rear end
as well right
and so
what happens is
when you see that we have very bullish
signs
at a very key level such as a weekly
open right this is a weekly level this
is not something that was formed just
today on the one minute timeframe this
is something that we got on the weekly
chart this is telling us that there's a
very strong possibility that we can get
a significant move to the upside
whenever we get a big bounce with
bullish divergences on higher term time
frames what we want to do is we want to
pull out our fib
from the low
to the high and take note of that
fibonacci golden pocket retracement
because if this is going to be a
significant move to the upside this is
where we're going to get our retrace
somewhere between the 618 and the 76 is
the area we look for
a retrace right and so if we come down
there this is where we want to enter our
law and what we want to see as we come
down to that area is we want to see now
bullish divergences on the lower time
frames like the one minute so do you see
what happened we got confirmation of a
major reversal here on the 12-minute
time frame we wrote it up to major
resistance which gave us a short
opportunity so we could short down to
the first major support and that's where
we can actually enter into our long
trade so what a lot of people do is when
they see prices pumping right after a
big dump they're hesitant to long
they're like nah heck no i ain't long
heck no i ain't longing heck no i ain't
long and we finally break out of
resistance they're like okay i'm longing
right boom what happens they get
liquidated
right okay we cannot we cannot chase
price we have to be calculated and we
have to plan in advance what we are
going to do now if you want to learn
this stuff you could check out the
course at
jasoncaspertrading.com this course will
give you the knowledge and skills you
need to become a confident profitable
trader by always having a game plan to
stay one step ahead of the market so you
know where you should be looking for
those high probability trade setups
there's a 25 discount in the description
of this video also if you do want to
join our technical analysis community
where we post multiple live streams a
week myself and other professional
traders giving the levels giving the
trade setups
you can go to patreon.com forward slash
jason casper we give the levels we give
the trade setups that we're looking for
for bitcoin ethereum other all coins
and starting to get into forex markets
as well patreon.com for slash jason
casper now
because we got the bounce from down here
this is the place to enter the long
trade right not up here we wait for the
retest and if the retest never comes we
simply just sit out or if we see that
we're getting a bounce we say where is
the next resistance and what bearer
signs can we look for to determine where
we can get into a short trade okay
this is how we're going to be successful
trading these markets staying one step
ahead
always understanding
where the next areas of support are
where the next areas of resistance are
understanding what confirmations to look
for
and then you can get into these good
moves like this guys and uh you know
it's been a very good day trading
bitcoin we haven't had too too much
volatility today
but nonetheless it is a profitable day
so i hope you guys found this video
informative
this is the kind of price action i love
you know key levels being respected i
mean look at this to the dollar
to the dollar to the dollar and now of
course we're finding local resistance
back at the v wap it just it works so
well guys and of course again starting
out this morning with the fibonacci uh
high volume node confluence to the
dollar okay
now trading like this i'm not gonna lie
guys it does take some time it does take
some experience absolutely it does
and um you know these are kinds of
things that you have to be able to come
up with these plans in a moment
now look at this my short has officially
been stopped out okay my shorts has
officially been stopped out
and uh my long trade is still open
okay and actually
because we just did get a chickens
drinking water
with a
bearish divergence we can even enter
another short trade right here because
look at what has just happened here okay
we see that we put in a high
right here
let's see
we put in a high right up here
oh actually we didn't take that hot we
did not take the high on usd
but on usdt you can see that we actually
did wick into that high right you can
see that we whipped into the high
and we did get some bearish divergences
here on the lower time frame look at the
one minute time frame right what is
happening we see
getting lower like this
and we also see over time
divergences getting lower we see the six
minute time frame as well
uh well actually not the six minute time
frame but we do see the three minute
time frame giving us this bearish
divergence
as we come and we take out that high
right so now we can get into another
short trade from this area of resistance
we're just trading it from support
to resistance that's how it works yo
so i hope you found this video
informative if you did make sure to like
the video make sure to subscribe to the
channel
let's see what happens here
as we come up one more time to approach
these highs
make sure to like the video guys make
sure to subscribe to the channel
let's see what happens here we're going
to come and see if we can get the
chickens drinking water right here
on this
um
this next little push to the upside here
we might not
get that push let's check out what's
happening on coinlines.net look at this
guy's big decrease in open interest here
showing us a sign of weakness
this is the usd but again
that is a sign of weakness we've got the
bearish divergences coming in here
okay
right see how that
see how these bearish divergences are
forming over time as we come back up to
the area of
resistance we are simply guys just
trading from support to resistance right
that is what we are doing and that is
how we are going to
be profitable
trading this way
all right
so hope you guys enjoyed the video make
sure to like the video make sure to
subscribe to the channel
and i will see everybody
in the next video
peace
all right y'all so i just wanted to
follow up on that trade that i took so
you can see the bearish divergences did
play out here lock it in for a quick
profit like that then we move our stop
loss to the entry to guarantee a win
right
and now this is a guaranteed winning
trade at least a hundred dollars
potentially more here
and so this is how we are going to be
scalping bitcoin throughout the day guys
so god bless everybody in the name of
jesus the messiah and i'll see y'all in
the next video peace